<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-09-20T20:21:26+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Delonghi Esam3300 Super Automatic Coffee Espresso Machinne Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/delonghi-esam3300-super-automatic-coffee-espresso-machinne-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delonghi Esam3300 Super Automatic Coffee Espresso Machinne Review" /><published>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/delonghi-esam3300-super-automatic-coffee-espresso-machinne-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/delonghi-esam3300-super-automatic-coffee-espresso-machinne-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I must admit that I wasn’t a coffee fan until recently. I couldn’t understand the hype about it until I tried this one coffee from this one local place, and now I’m a convert. I wanted to recreate the experience but then I found out that it’s pretty hard to make good coffee unless you have a solid machine to do the work for you. Disappointed, I turned to Google to help me out, and came across the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300 Super Automatic Espresso/Coffee Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Here, I will proceed to gather all the information and reviews I found in one neat little post so you can check it out and decide for yourself in case you’re in a similar spot as myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the first thing that people found attractive about this machine was its small size. It is compact at 14 inches and weighs in at 28.1 lbs, which I’ve come to learn is actually pretty modest for coffee machines. This is a great option for those with limited countertop space or small kitchens. It’s a good looking machine, with a silvery, metallic front side and black plastic sides and top. It gives off a very sleek and minimalistic home-style vibe. Now, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a large reservoir, able to hold 60 ounces of water at once. Remember that this machine was made to brew a cup at a time, rather than a whole pot. However, buyers note that the front panel controls give you the opportunity to adjust your cup size to 8 ounces, and you can then choose to add a “double shot”.
This will give you a double drink of 16 ounces. There is the ability to make 2 cups at the same time with the choice of one or two cup button. Now, most super automatic machines have their reservoir in the back. For the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, you can gain access to it from the front. This makes it more convenient to use. People who like to run on coffee day to day can appreciate this at-home coffee maker, thanks to the bigger reservoir size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Super automatic espresso machines utilize “beans-to-brew”, and this beast is no different. Its design is best suited for medium-roast coffee, as oily beans are reported by Amazon buyers to clog up the whole machine’s system. When it comes to the grinder, the bean hopper is described to hold around 7 ounces of coffee, which you refill from the top of the machine. 
Next to the hopper, you’ll find dials for grind setting, which enables you to adjust the coarseness of the grind to your liking. Most hardcore coffee drinkers already know that a good cup of coffee requires the perfect grind level, otherwise you just end up with subpar coffee. Apart from the grind setting and the “extraction rate” knob, there’s a “contact time” knob which lets you decide how long you want the water to be in contact with the grounds. As shared by users, the noise level of the machine is relatively on the lower side when  compared it to owners’ previously owned machines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part for people like me, who are not as well versed in the world of coffee yet, is the fact that this machine accommodates for ground coffee as well. There is a bypass doser on top of the machine, under a hatch you lift up, between the bean hopper and warming tray. The purchase comes with a scooper so all you need to do is put the grounds in, set the dials and press the brew button. Isn’t that awesome?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I can have traditional pick-me-up coffee in the morning, and ground decaf coffee in the evening. From the reviews I’ve gathered, some users have shared that using water that has been distilled is a top priority to keep your machine running smooth and living long. The unit is reported to require some maintenance to keep it running as it did on the first day and keep things moving. Once in a while, a light will blink to know you need to descale it, and if you use filtered water the time between descaling will increase drastically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only few cons reported were that you cannot see when the beans are running low, and hardcore coffee drinkers complained that the reservoir wasn’t big enough and required topping every so often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300 Super Automatic Espresso/Coffee Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has been noted as easy to use: just add water and the machine will automatically add beans to the hopper as needed. The whole coffee making process is said to take roughly 5 minutes. For people in a hurry in the morning, this is a pretty good feature to have. This unit has the ability to run a clean cycle when started and also when shutting down. Its head/filter unit is removable and hence easy to clean, and overall customers report this machine manages ground coffee better than most other models. 
People who self-described themselves as not so experienced with coffee making machines or even coffee in general were comfortable in choosing the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300 Super Automatic Espresso/Coffee Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; as their go-to. Professionals who had used manual machines in the past reviewed their satisfaction with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and appreciate they don’t have to fill filters, empty grounds and so on. The machine does all that for you and used grounds are deposited into a container present on the right side. It requires to be emptied about every 10 cups, and has no environment-harming pods to waste. With drip coffee machines, people report to usually end up with a lot more than they needed, which all then goes to waste. But the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is customizable to your tastes and requirements, has lesser waste, and has easy maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Coffee Machine" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gowise Usa 8 In 1 Electric Pressure Cooker Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/gowise-usa-8-in-1-electric-pressure-cooker-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gowise Usa 8 In 1 Electric Pressure Cooker Review" /><published>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/gowise-usa-8-in-1-electric-pressure-cooker-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/gowise-usa-8-in-1-electric-pressure-cooker-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast paced world, it’s no secret that most of us have no time to cook full meals from scratch, particularly if it requires intensive cooking times. College students, busy parents and the elderly are some people who are simply unable to give cooking the time it demands. When time is short and limited, some people even skip meals, which isn’t good for you if you keep doing it consistently. To remedy this, an investment into an electric pressure cooker should be considered. These staple items that should be present in every household makes sure meals are quick and easy to prepare, especially for those people who are into eating clean, made from scratch food. Investing in a capable electric pressure cooker is a great time saver and you will get delicious meals in return. You can’t go wrong with that!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE USA 8-Quart 8-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker/Slow Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one such cooker that caught my eye. So I’m on here gathering feedback and reviews for people who are considering investing in this amazing cookware. These days, you even get the option of having a “smart” pressure cooker that connects to WiFi, which is just crazy if you ask me. A solid electric pressure cooker that can do its job is what one needs, and you don’t have to go broke trying to get one. 
The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE 8-in-1 Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a programmable cooker with a stainless steel cooking pot that comes in with build-in presets to do your work for you. It has options available for a wide variety of meals, like rice, multigrain, porridge, stew or meat, poultry, veggies, seafood and so on. If you prefer more versatility in your cooking, this cooker comes with a manual mode that lets you decide between three different pressure settings. You can choose between low, medium and high. Buyers shared on amazon that this feature allows one to specify and customize the cooking experience. 
The biggest selling point of this pressure cooker is its versatility. It has a one of a kind design that gives you the functions of 9 different appliances in one place. The tasks this machine can do range from traditional pressure cooking, rice pudding, porridge, to yogurt maker, to egg maker, with only a push of a button! You can use this device as as warmer, slow cooker, steamer, browner. This wide spectrum allows this pressure cooker to be a suitable option for students or people who have basic knowledge of cooking and are just starting off. The safety mechanisms are in place to keep you safe from the build-up of steam. There is an in-built pressure release button on the lid, which makes it easier, safer and quicker to release the pressure build-up. This product boasts an ETL stamp for matching industry standards of safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most Amazon reviewers are quick to praise the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE USA 8-Quart 8-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker/Slow Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The lid is described as being easy to screw on, with one simple counter-clockwise move. The cooker will display the pressure gauge level, heat level, timer, and it also lets you know when the cooking is about to begin on an LED readout screen in the front. One nifty feature is the ability to delay start time. You might find that this comes in handy when you’re running late from the office and wish that dinner would cook itself. You can set the time and have dinner waiting for you when you get home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The user interface is simple: choose your cooking option and set the timer. The cook pot is made of stainless steel and with pressure cookers at a similar price point, competitors tend to use Teflon non-stick coating for their cooking pots, which speaks about the quality of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE 8-in-1 Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Most people choose to opt for stainless steel as Teflon is being phased out due to concerns about its effect on health. A steel rack comes inside the cooker, allowing you to cook multiple foods at once, for example, meat at the bottom and veggies at the top. For people who are completely new to using pressure cookers, one reminder left by a helpful reviewer states that you need to allow some time to pass for the pressure to build up and start the cooking process. Likewise, when it is done you need to let the pressure drop down before you open the pot. Replacement parts are easily available on Amazon for the cooking pots and sealing ring, ensuring your pressure cooker lasts you for years. Most reviewers stated they were new to cooking or pressure cookers and were impressed with the ease of usage and the quality of meals this pressure cooker has helped them make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cooker goes up to 8 quarts, with instructions saying you should fill the pot to about 60%, while buyers note that even 5 quarts is enough to feed a whole family, or 8-10 people if we’re being specific. All of that, with less stress and even less clean-up time.The only gripe some customers have complained about is that the manual is not very intensive, which isn’t a mark on the pressure cooker itself. Moreso, there is an owner’s manual available online, but the cooker’s simple design doesn’t require much know-how. As a bonus, Amazon reviewers have shared their experiences with GoWISE customer support, and they are reported to be responsive and prompt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, my verdict would be that if you’re often in a rush and would like to save some time as well as get a headstart on that healthy eating lifestyle you’ve been wanting, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE USA 8-Quart 8-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker/Slow Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; should fit your needs perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Electric Pressure Cooker" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Audeze Lcd X Over Ear Suspension Headphones</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-x-over-ear-suspension-headphones/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Audeze Lcd X Over Ear Suspension Headphones" /><published>2019-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-x-over-ear-suspension-headphones</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-x-over-ear-suspension-headphones/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who appreciate music in its various forms, it is imperative to have equipment that supports their passion and translates every musical note in its purest form. It holds true just as much for music creators and sound engineers as it does for audiophiles and music enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to high-quality equipment, it must ensure a trouble-free rendition and lifelike listening experience for its users. After all, every creator wants their work to translate accurately for the listener, and every listener wants the utmost quality from each second they devote to their music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is where professional-grade headphones come in. With their unique structure, premium materials, and exceptional craftsmanship, they provide a listening experience like no other. That is why they remain a sought-after piece of equipment for every music professional and audiophile alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X Over Ear Open Back Headphone with New Suspension Headband Creator Package – no Travel case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one such pair of superior quality headphones that stay true to the promises they make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important to note that while the Creator Package doesn’t come with a travel case or balanced cable, it still has the same pair of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headphones that are offered in the retail package. But this works to the advantage of those buyers who are looking for an affordable deal. It allows them to enjoy a discounted price for the same high-quality &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headphones that come with the retail package, just without a travel case and balanced cable (which you can purchase separately).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sporting what it calls a “crystal clear” midrange, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes equipped with ultra-thin diaphragms, double-sided magnetic arrays, and the company’s signature Fazor Elements. All of these features come packed within a modern design structure which is made out of memory foam earpads, premium leather, and an ergonomic design with suspension headband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to sound quality, it’s hard to surpass the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The ultra-thin yet large 106mm diaphragms do what they claim to do, and deliver a sound that is certainly true to life. Those who have used the headphones sing praises of the quality produced by the headphones, especially when it comes to the midrange. According to users, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides exemplary sound regardless of the acoustics or the room it is being used in, which makes it all the more perfect for creators and listeners alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s double-sided magnetic arrays prevent distortion and ensure the delivery of sound with realistic notes. It has been noted that this feature translates into providing a neutral, yet ultra-accurate sound, which brings out even the tiniest details of a recording to the forefront. This helps creators convert their sounds with a certain amount of confidence, while it provides listeners with an experience that remains unmatched by many other headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Audeze’s signature Fazor Elements are there to serve their own purpose. With double-sided magnetic arrays, these elements work to prevent resonance to a very impressive margin. As a result, the waveform delivered through the headphones shines through in terms of lifelike sound. This has been noted by users firsthand, who vouch for the headphones’ soundstage, bass, and realistic rendition, no matter what kind of recording they listen to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This clarity in sound quality, near-zero distortion, and accurate waveform all come together to make the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ideal for sound engineers, producers, and audiophiles alike. Whether someone wants to produce their own tunes for the world to listen to, or if they simply want to enjoy recordings developed by their favorite artists, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could prove to be the best fit for the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from its superior sound quality, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also lauded for its built. Users note that the quality of the headphones’ structure is as good as the sound that it produces. This build quality is possible due to the way Audeze produces these headphones. Each pair of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is handcrafted in Audeze’s California facility, which allows the company to ensure optimal build quality using premium materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This attention to developing the headphones is translated very well in the comfort that they provide to the wearer. The memory foam, premium leather, and suspension headband along with the ergonomic structure provide a very comfortable fit to the wearer, even if they use the headphones for hours at a time. Users have noted that the headphones are comfortable to wear, even if they are “built like a tank.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, the lack of a travel case is irksome to a few users, who say that it has affected the lifespan of their headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But these complaints remain limited, whereas most users swear by the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X Over Ear Open Back Headphone with New Suspension Headband Creator Package – no Travel case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s quality and durability. According to them, the headphones are as perfect for sound mastering and mixing as they are for simply enjoying your favorite tunes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With exceptional sound quality, comfortable fit, and stylish yet durable build, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X Over Ear Open Back Headphone with New Suspension Headband Creator Package – no Travel case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains a great fit for those music creators and listeners who do not see the lack of a travel case as an issue for portability or equipment safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as they are using the headphones carefully, they can enjoy the same sound quality and product benefits as the retail package, except for the travel case. The necessity to buy your own balanced cable actually provides you with the freedom to choose between options, which adds to the customization options for the headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are one to enjoy music as a creator or a listener and want the best out of your equipment investments, then the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; would prove to be a viable fit for you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Headphones" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/arsvita-car-audio-bluetooth-cassette-receiver-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/arsvita-car-audio-bluetooth-cassette-receiver-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/arsvita-car-audio-bluetooth-cassette-receiver-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you a music lover? Do you not like local radio stations, or get tired of not having music on demand? More importantly, does your car only have a tape player? Since most bands stopped putting out tapes sometime in the early 2000s, having the ability to play them in your car isn’t seen as such a big positive anymore. And, if you can’t afford to replace the entire stereo, it can seem like you’re stuck with the oldies and that random tape of the Oakridge Boys that somehow made its way into that one tucked-away box of junk that never gets thrown out. CDs, too, are going the way of the dinosaur, so those old adapters don’t work as well anymore. But the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07QSW6KNY?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; seems to be a good choice in overcoming this hurdle, and getting your favorite tunes playing again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it&quot;&gt;What Is It?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, it’s the modern equivalent of the adapters used to play CDs with only a tape deck. Here, the tape-shaped adapter is placed into the player, leaving the transmitter outside. Then, you can simply connect your device wirelessly via Bluetooth to play music, listen to podcasts, or even listen to audio-books as you drive! A tool like this is often a necessity for older cars, since they usually lack a hook up for modern technology. This works for practically all devices capable of a Bluetooth connection. Anything from iPods to smartphones, even to computers and tablets, can be used by this device. The cassette receiver is rechargeable, with an 8 hour long active battery time. That increases to over 160 when switched to standby mode. Being wireless, you’ll also be spared having cords running from your phone or device directly into your stereo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;who-should-use-it&quot;&gt;Who Should Use It?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two main categories of people who would do well with this product. The first are those who enjoy collecting and driving antique (or just older) cars. Often, dream cars from the 80s only came with a tape player, as nothing else was available at the time. Not only can changing out the entire stereo system be expensive, you also risk ruining any interior work during the process. If you’ve managed to preserve the original, that could be a nightmare. Instead, an adapter such as this can make it possible to play music in a modern way, using modern equipment. The second group of people are those who are driving an older car out of necessity. Whatever the reason, a complete stereo replacement is expensive, as mentioned above. Instead of completely replacing what already functions, you could simply use this product to overcome the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;interesting-features&quot;&gt;Interesting Features&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without a doubt, the most interesting feature of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07QSW6KNY?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is directly in its name:  Bluetooth. Unlike similar cassette adapters, this one is capable of connecting to your devices via Bluetooth. This saves a lot of hassle. Instead of having to manually plug in your phone or mp3 player every time you get into the car, it can automatically connect for you! Since your phone won’t have to leave wherever you normally store it while driving, such as your purse, a stand, or even just a cup holder, you’ll be less likely to leave it behind. You’ll also get rid of all of the bulky cords that seem to only clutter up the area and take up space. Do you take calls while driving? You can with this! Being hands-free is a safe way to keep up communication on the go, and this product offers it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-good&quot;&gt;The Good&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Amazon, a majority (70%) of the comments were very high, rating five stars for this product. It has been reported to work very well by quite a number of different customers. The cassette receiver seems to function as intended, giving users the ability to listen to music and other audio through older speakers in their car using this. One buyer in particular was happy to find that older speakers “can now be converted to Bluetooth speakers with this versatile tool.” The way that the product looked was highly praised, as well. It’s fairly small, and not bulky. The lack of wires means that it doesn’t clutter up the area around your stereo. Many have described it as “sleek”, which is something a lot of those who are proud of their cars aim for. On the whole, the product seems to function well, look nice, and please buyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-bad&quot;&gt;The Bad&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are a lot of good reviews, 13% of the reviews for the product are only one star. That, behind the five star ratings, is the highest percentage of the ratings. Many of the negative reviews seem to have similar problems. The most common of these are that the cassette simply ceases to work after a few weeks. They claim no damage to the product, only that it randomly died. Some have had the Bluetooth stop working on them. One user in particular mentions that, while it works well, he’s already had to buy two, because the others malfunctioned. A handful of people complain about the quality, saying that there was either a lot of background noise, or a constant humming while it was playing. A few of those who bought one have said that it was repeatedly ejected by their tape player, so couldn’t get it to work at all. To their credit, the company is prompt in discussing solutions, including full refunds, with those that had these problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what do we make of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07QSW6KNY?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;? With all of the facts, it seems to be a fairly nice choice for anyone who wants to listen to modern music in an antique car. The good reviews dwarf any of the bad ones. There are some problems with it, but the company seems to be on top of the matter when it comes to righting any wrongs. All-in-all, it’s a great purchase to make.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>12</name></author><category term="Bluetooth Adapters" /><category term="Car Accessories" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Concept2 Model D Indoor Rowing Machine Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/concept2-model-d-indoor-rowing-machine-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Concept2 Model D Indoor Rowing Machine Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/concept2-model-d-indoor-rowing-machine-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/concept2-model-d-indoor-rowing-machine-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have been looking into cardio as an approach to weight loss or fitness goals, the row machine is one low-impact option you should consider. Row machines are a great option for toning up as they work almost all parts of the body in minimal time. &lt;em&gt;Concept2&lt;/em&gt; is a name that dominates the row machine market, known as a brand that is built to last and a favourite in gyms and CrossFit Boxes. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NH9WEUA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Concept2 Model D Indoor Rowing Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is considered to be one of the best currently available. This row machine boasts quality and reliability. Let’s start with some facts. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NH9WEUA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Concept2 Rowing Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a rower that uses air-resistance instead of magnetic resistance, leading to a smoother row experience and is more similar to rowing in actual water. It has the ability to adjust its output, meaning if you row faster, it will give more resistance. This variable makes this row machine a great choice for HIIT workouts. You do not have to stop and change levels of resistance or other settings. The build of the machine is reported to last years even with regular usage. Most at-home gym users opt for a less stellar row machine and then are disappointed in the lack of value for money. If you’ve ever used a row machine in the gym, chances are that it was a &lt;em&gt;Concept2&lt;/em&gt;. The seat is reported as comfortable to sit on even for extended amounts of time. It is also adjustable, meaning it “slides” to give the sensation of rowing a boat. The LCD screen mounted in the front, called a Performance Monitor, will turn on automatically once you start to row, and turns off after a couple minutes of inactivity. It has all the typical features like calorie data, number of strokes per minute, amount of distance rowed, how long you’ve been rowing, and so on. A new functionality of the monitor is a “race boat” game where you are in competition with a boat on screen. You have the option to compete against yourself from a previous session as well, or online against other &lt;em&gt;Concept2&lt;/em&gt; users. These features are an upgrade from the old Performance Monitor 4, the current one uses PM5. The PM5 ensures you stay on track with your fitness goals and keeps you on your toes. The PM5 has the ability to connect to compatible RowPro software, a benefit only available with &lt;em&gt;Concept2&lt;/em&gt;. You can also connect via USB cable to your computer in order to download your workout data, or even project your workouts on the TV via the RowPro software. Out of all the raves about this machine, buyers enjoy the engaging programming of the PM5 the most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NH9WEUA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Concept2 Rowing Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in 2 colors, silver and black. The flywheel design makes sure there is minimal noise. The frame is designed to be separated in 2 blocks for transport or storing away as well as easy setup, the flywheel and the seat frame. The machine has “damper settings” on the wheel to change the amount of air moving into the flywheel, which has an impact of the “feel” on rowing. This is not the same as, for example, changing levels on a treadmill. This is more comparable to changing gears on a bicycle. For people who have had a knee injury of any sort or suffer from arthritis, Amazon users tout this machine as the best buy you can get. First of all, the machine is reported as being the easiest to set up, with only 2 parts you need to put together with 8 screws and screwdriver included. Batteries are already given in the console, so all one needs to do is put it together and it is ready to go. The design of the machine is very low-impact on the knees. The damper settings mean one can work up to rowing with a variety of difficulty modes. Another plus point for people who cannot participate in traditional cardio due to joint pains would be happy to read that Amazon users report this machine has the effect of enhancing your flexibility. This low impact row machine stretches out all major muscles and is a great way to combat sedentary sitting which weakens the muscles over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For people who share a living space, the noise emitted from the row machine is minimal, according to people who have bought and tested it out. It has no rumble and the only sound it makes is the fan used for air resistance. One can watch TV on a normal volume easily. Once you have it set up, the ease of a workout and time spent is a very big advantage most people appreciate. For people who work full time and can barely find time to fit in chores, this is a great alternative to joining a gym. You don’t have to pack a gym bag, put shoes on, no transportation, just hop on and in 15 minutes you have had a smooth workout on a smoother machine. Tall people can rejoice, for this machine comes with long rails. The only reported con amongst Amazon buyers and reviewers is that some people may not find the seat all that comfortable, as it is hard in design and not cushy. Some people who are overweight may find they cannot fit in the seat. The only competitor with this is their own model, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NH9WEUA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Concept2 Rowing Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, with the only difference being that the seat sits much higher for people who suffer from mobility issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, buyers unanimously agree that with this row machine, you get what you paid for. Most people are inclined to save money where they can, but for something you’d be using on the regular, it is a much better option to shell out those extra bucks to gain quality stuff that doesn’t fall apart in a short time. The difference in subpar machines vs the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NH9WEUA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Concept2 Rowing Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are reported to be huge and it pays off. If you buy something that is a perfect fit for you, you are inclined to use it more, and people are loving their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NH9WEUA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Concept2 Rowing Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; row machine.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Gym Equipment" /><category term="Workout Equipment" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cyberpowerpc Gamer Xtreme Vr Gaming Pc Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/cyberpowerpc-gamer-xtreme-vr-gaming-pc-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cyberpowerpc Gamer Xtreme Vr Gaming Pc Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/cyberpowerpc-gamer-xtreme-vr-gaming-pc-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/cyberpowerpc-gamer-xtreme-vr-gaming-pc-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The allure of PC gaming is stronger than ever in these subscription service ridden days. With free multiplayer, cheaper games, and better graphics there’s no surprise thousands of people are looking to make the switch to PC. However, building your own PC is not for everyone, as it requires some degree of research and preparation. Not everyone can spare their valuable time for researching and selecting components to eventually build a PC. This is why pre-built systems like the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; exist, they offer anyone a chance to get into PC gaming without the other hassles of building and testing your own computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; features 3 RGB fans mounted at the front. These are large 120mm fans capable of pushing serious air into your computer, keeping it cool under any amount of stress. The rear of the computer features a single RGB 120mm fan. You might assume that having only 1 fan at the back is for cost efficiency, but that is not the case. By having an imbalance of air pressure at the back, CyberPower manages to create negative air pressure, which greatly increases the cooling ability and speed of the air entering the system. All fans are customizable in colour, with a remote provided to go through the various lighting modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Appearance is important, and when you are priced just above 800$, you better show it. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is no stranger to aesthetics, with its RGB fans managing to blend seamlessly into the inky black of the case. Red trim around the case adds a layer of ‘class’ if you will. It features 1 stick of 8GB DDR4 ram, painted with a beautiful crimson to blend in with the build. The motherboard is a deep black, with everything connected to it following a similar colour pattern. Most computers are blessed with beautiful interiors, yet they are never shown. These beautiful interiors are locked inside a metal prison, with no eyes able to truly enjoy them. This case has a tempered glass side panel, allowing everyone to see the beautiful interior of your computer. This computer is beautifully designed and put together, something all users can agree on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connection is important, and the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; delivers. At the front, it features 2 super-fast USB 3.0 ports, mic and audio ports, and a power/reset button. This is an impressive array, yet it pales in comparison to what the computer holds in its rear. It has 6 USB 3.0 ports, 2 USB 2.0 ports, 7.1 audio ports, and an extremely fast ethernet port. You may be wondering what to fill up those USB ports with, well CyberPower has you covered! When you purchase the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you receive a free keyboard and mouse. The mouse has 4 programmable buttons and features variable lighting. The keyboard is also well made, with red accents on often used keys. In general, the ports peripherals on this PC were very well received by users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything I’ve discussed pales in comparison to what really matters, performance! This is the true test of whether the computer has enough power to meet the demand of its users. It features a 6 core I5-9400 CPU capable of handling just about anything you throw at it. The CPU has a base clock of a respectable 2.9 GHz, but the turbo is where it shows its true potential. This CPU manages to get up to 4.1 GHz, able to crush tasks like video rendering and gaming with ease. The graphics card is no weakling either, its a full-sized GTX 1660 with 6GB of video memory. This graphics card crushes all games at 1080p, however, you might have trouble running max settings above that resolution. The graphics card is by far the weakest point of this build, holding the CPU back in demanding tasks. However, most users will never face this as it becomes apparent in only the most demanding tasks. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; features a 120GB Solid State Drive that is many times faster than a traditional HDD, yet it also has a 1 Terabyte hard-drive for all your major files. This interesting storage setup allows for windows to run on a blazing fast low storage SSD, while all the large files stay on the huge hard-drive. The performance is easily the most well-received part of this computer, with almost every user prasing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PKXQBHN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberpowerPC Gamer Xtreme VR Gaming PC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a superb computer capable of handling almost anything its users throw at it. Everything including and under 1080p gaming is lightwork for this computer. The design of this computer and the free peripherals make it an eyecatcher in any room. CyberPower also gives a 1-year warranty on this computer, so you’ll always have peace of mind. Overall, this computer is definitely deserving of its 4.7-star rating on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Computers" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Doona Infant Car Seat And Latch Base Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/doona-infant-car-seat-and-latch-base-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Doona Infant Car Seat And Latch Base Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/doona-infant-car-seat-and-latch-base-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/doona-infant-car-seat-and-latch-base-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking care of a newborn can be hard and even more so with families that travel regularly. For most parents, they have to lug around bulky car seats and a separate stroller anytime they have to be on the go. This can get tiring pretty quick. It’s basically an upper body cardio workout! The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant Car Seat &amp;amp; Latch Base&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a nifty game-changer released by the company &lt;em&gt;Simple Parenting&lt;/em&gt;. This car seat is the first that can also transform into a stroller! Is that a dream come true or what? Well, maybe not quite, but it does seem to be the time and energy saving solution for parents. Customers report ease of usage with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, with mothers who frequent public transport heaving a sigh of relief over the foldability and portability of this car seat-stroller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in 10 colors and has a minimalistic design, transforming into a compact stroller with just a push of a lever. Parents who have busy lives and errands to run are absolutely smitten with this feature. Your purchase comes with the infant car seat base. It also comes with an extensive list on how to properly install and use the seat. Buyers shared that it also comes with a recall-list paper that you can get registered on and you can get notified in case of leaving your baby accidentally in the car. A car seat protector is also in the package, in case of spills or other accidents. The infant insert and the head supporting cushion are made with bamboo fabric. Youtube tutorials give you guidance on how to set it up and get started. It is recommended by customers to use it on your own before putting baby in it in order to get a feel for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also meets FAA standards, which means you can bring this with you on a plane. It saves you storage space in your car and your apartment. Buyers agree that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is simple and easy to maneuver, even one handed. This is a nice quirk for people who like to sip coffee on the go, or have to hold on to the sibling’s hand. Some people have commented on how heavy the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; weighs when you pick it up. It weighs 15 pounds. Most moms say they’d pick some extra strength expenditure for the benefit of having what equals to a convertible car seat. As a stroller, it is reported to be easily maneuvered through aisles, restaurants, city corners, and airplanes. It comes with an insert to support newborns, and the canopy over the head extends downwards. Wheels are reportedly durable for both sidewalk and grassland walks and the one-touch brakes are described to be smooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a car seat, which it is primarily, it comes equipped with some safety features in place. A 5- point safety harness makes sure your baby is good and secure in his crib. The handles also serve as anti-rebound bars. The wheel enclosure have a double-wall structure, which gives a 3 layer Side Impact Protection, with EPS foam layers. Once you decide to convert it into a stroller, you just pull up the handle and you’re good to go. The position of the handlebar is low enough that the older sibling can take over the duty of switching the seat into the stroller. The car seat is virtually impossible to fold accidentally. Neither will the handle pop out in carry mode. These safety features were designed keeping in mind both the parents as well as the baby. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Infant Insert was designed specially in order to support and cradle newborns in their first month of life, by engineers and medical professionals. It is an almost flat design which ensures that the baby’s neck and back are in alignment ergonomically. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is the only one to have been certified as a car seat and a stroller that provides complete safety for your little one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can handle up to 35lb of weight and up to 32 inches in height. It is rear facing, and not forward facing, which some customers wished it was. Buyers have reported that they need to buy separate accessories as it has no space, baskets, or under the stroller storage for milk and water bottles or other small things. Accessories that the company offers separately alongside the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HML1BT5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doona Infant car seat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; include rain covers, snap-on storage, sunshade, an essentials bag and an all-day bag. But if you want to bypass all of that, you can simply buy a bike bag as a quick fix to carry around your diapers and wipes, as shared by one mom in an Amazon review. The only other major setback with this handy seat is the price tag. Some people are skeptical of shelling out $500 for something their baby will outgrow. Some people don’t travel about enough for this seat to be handy. But the majority customers agree that the investment is worth it for those moments of ease, convenience, and flexibility. No separate travel system in place required, you just pop the wheels of the Doona and secure it in place. &lt;strong&gt;A must-have for parents that value their time and are on the go.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Parenting" /><category term="Baby" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Netgear Nighthawk Smart Wifi Router Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/netgear-nighthawk-smart-wifi-router-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Netgear Nighthawk Smart Wifi Router Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/netgear-nighthawk-smart-wifi-router-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/netgear-nighthawk-smart-wifi-router-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you like surfing the internet? - Of course, you do. So now you might be thinking, why ask such a redundant question? Well, do you like surfing the internet with slow or fast speeds? -  Okay, that answer should still be obvious, but to be truthful, it’s selective. Anybody can buy a new router and do a quick google search, then claim that said router is Sonic The Hedgehog when it comes to internet speed. But often enough, this is a ruse to give you a lower quality router, or sometimes even a used one. (Looking at you, Spectrum.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even older routers can process a simple search engine result with minimal difficulty. I mean, it barely takes any processing power to do it. So, with that in mind, where do you find the downfall in the common WIFI routers you’ll receive as part of your internet plan? Usually, anything that requires 5+ Mbps, which almost always includes downloading large files or playing even a basic 3D game. We can all remember the days when it took five minutes to boot up your Windows XP, and that persists today in the form of low-quality WIFI routers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, so after getting that little tidbit out of the way, what’s the solution? Yet another easy answer. Buy a third-party router with the specs you believe will satisfy your daily usage. However, even then, you still need to make sure you get what you’re buying; which is where this review comes in. So, without further ado, here is my review for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07C65K9H9/ref=s9_acsd_bw_wf_a_ACPCWF17_cdl_11?pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NETGEAR Nighthawk WIFI Router&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of design, it’s not bad at all. It’s a Smart WIFI router and is capable of running speeds up to 1900 Mbps; which, might make lightning look slow if you think about it. other than that, it has an expansive 1800 square feet of coverage and can support up to 30 devices on the network. With that in mind, it seems like a true speed racer for even the most bandwidth greedy geek out there. But let’s take a look at the ratings first and see whether or not it holds up to its advertised value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Released on April 25, 2018, this router sells for an interesting price of $109.99 and includes free shipping. It currently ships relatively fast too, so if you want it now, you’ll get it now. In terms of amazon ratings, it has an exceptional 4.2 out 5 stars. Making it seem like its too good to be true, right? Well, to confirm this, let’s take a look at the enormous 18,626 reviews that customers have left on this product. - Starting with Ivaneth, we already are seeing a little bit of suspicious activity. As he claims that the router advertised on the page is not the one you will likely receive, so keep this in mind if you’re skeptical. He gave this device a three out of five, so he must have liked something though!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving on, we learn that they may have some frustrating customer support. David B comments that while he did like several features of the router, he does have some severe gripes. For one, he says that their customer service is picky and a little greedy too. Why? Well, they supposedly want to charge you just to find out what’s wrong with your product! Crazy, right? Well, if that’s not bad enough, he later states that they were supposed to follow up with him via email; which would never arrive. If this is all true, then you’re in for a bad experience if your router ever breaks down. He gave them a 1 star out of 5, and rightfully so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more positive vibe, the user Matt Sayar says that he got the router he desired and that it truly delivers when it comes to speed. He goes on to rate this product 5 out of 5 stars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are only a few of the reviews left by a multitude of customers. Unfortunately, most of the recent ones do not seem to be very positive regarding the product. However, it does have an overwhelming 75% of 5-star reviews. So maybe they started with the right intentions, but have started to shift their focus to bigger and better products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want something fast and aren’t willing to pay TOO much money. This might be the device for you -  but beware of possible troubles that may lay ahead for you. They might not be worth it in the end. So choose wisely!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>10</name></author><category term="Routers" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nordictrack Tseries 65s 65si Treadmill Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/nordictrack-tseries-65s-65si-treadmill-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nordictrack Tseries 65s 65si Treadmill Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/nordictrack-tseries-65s-65si-treadmill-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/nordictrack-tseries-65s-65si-treadmill-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Running on a treadmill has remained the most popular choice for people looking for a quick cardio workout, whether at home or gym. It is a no-brainer to use, and requires no in-depth understanding apart from, well, running. When we talk about treadmills for home use, there is a wide variety out there ranging from awful to fantastic. That’s a broad spectrum. For someone who is looking around to buy one, this can get tedious very fast. This review is going to cover not one, but 2 treadmills of one of the most reliable brands out there, &lt;em&gt;NordicTrack&lt;/em&gt;. The 6.5S and 6.5Si are the current popular offerings and this review touches both briefly to help out a potential cardio bunny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NordicTrack fitness is a home equipment staple. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0193V3DJ6?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NordicTrack T Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one of the company’s least expensive home use treadmill, which makes it a great choice for home buyers. There’s a console that gives 20 workout programs for complete novices. This variety ensures you don’t get bored with the same old. It offers fat loss, LISS and HIIT programs, among others. If you have a subscription to the iFit program, it comes with access to the app, which opens the gateway to more workout programs. If you decide to purchase this treadmill, you get a free 30-day subscription to iFit. Features include heart rate monitoring, FlexSelect Cushioning, where you control the cushioning effect of the running belt, and is foldable. The LCD is backlit, has a music port and 2-inch speakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting off with some cons first, for seasoned runners, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0193V3DJ6?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NordicTrack T Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; only has an incline of 10%. Therefore, if you are a runner on the more advanced side, you might choose to skip this purchase. Coming to what Amazon reviewers think of this equipment, it seems that you cannot use the treadmill unless you sign up for iFit. To get around this, buyers report holding down the iFit logo for 30 seconds. This was one of the biggest disadvantage users had a problem with, as this feature is not made aware to you when purchasing. Other cons include treadmill not having a cool down fan, or space to put in your phone or keys, which some people found off-putting. However, there are cup holders on each side. It is a larger piece of equipment, hence it requires at least 2 people to assemble. Assemble time was reported at an average of 30 minutes. The machine is described as being heavy to handle, and cannot fit through doors, so consider setting up in a place you wouldn’t want to move from again. In case of faulty equipment, most people found the customer support services absymal. The hassle of cancelling an iFit subscription was not worth it to many people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming to some positives, the build of the treadmill is reported to be sturdy and not shaky, even at higher incline and speeds. It was described as not being hard to set up, even if you tried doing it alone, although that will take longer as per helpful reviewers. Speed changes can be increased in fractional speeds in 10ths for 10 levels. A hydraulic system is built into the machine. It locks in place once you push it high enough. To move the treadmill part, you will need to depress the lever. Once the descent starts, you can let it touch the ground gently on its own, thanks to the hydraulic system. It works the same way once you want to push it upwards. This is a great plus for people who do not want to, or cannot, struggle with a heavy treadmill every time they want to exercise. There is a wedge in the main console where you can set an iPad, should you need to. Regarding noise levels, the reviews are in the favor of not as noisy as you would expect such heavy, big equipment to be. If you are an avid runner or marathon trainer, or simply cannot find the time to go to gym or run, this piece of equipment is described to give you what you need, a solid cardio workout at a solid price point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0193V3DJ6?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NordicTrack T Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; series treadmill has similar features to the 6.5S, with the addition of a larger display screen serving as a console. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0193V3DJ6?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NordicTrack T Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a 10 inch screen that is interactive. With the purchase of this treadmill, you get a 1 year subscription to iFit, whereas the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;6.5S&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; gives you one month only. It also has a 2.6 CHP motor, which allows for more power than other treadmills in the range. A very neat feature allows the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;6.5Si&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; technology to show a trainer on screen that can control your machine’s incline level and speed. This one also has a library of 20 workout programs which feature world class level fitness trainers to guide you through. The treadmill belt length is 55’’. Another addition to this treadmill are non-flex rollers, along with the predecessor’s patented FlexSelect cushioning, which allows for non-jerky treadmill movements. This has a less harsh impact on your joints, causing them lesser strain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;6.5Si treadmill&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is much the same as the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;6.5S&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; with added features. This means that the cons for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;6.5S&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; apply to the &lt;em&gt;6.5Si&lt;/em&gt; as well. Compared to other treadmills in this price range under $1000, there is a balance between value for money and what features the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0193V3DJ6?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NordicTrack T Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; equipment offers. In a nutshell, it is quiet, sturdy, and has variety workouts, which is good enough for beginner runners and at-home cardio workouts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Gym Equipment" /><category term="Workout Equipment" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Oculus Rift S Pc Powered Vr Gaming Headset Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/oculus-rift-s-pc-powered-vr-gaming-headset-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oculus Rift S Pc Powered Vr Gaming Headset Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/oculus-rift-s-pc-powered-vr-gaming-headset-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/oculus-rift-s-pc-powered-vr-gaming-headset-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oculus is one of the top names in the category of  Virtual Reality. And it has changed how we experience entertainment in this new age. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PTMKYS7?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headset is what I’m going to be reviewing today. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PTMKYS7?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has been described more as a remastered version of the Rift, rather than a successor. It’s previous original version has been discontinued permanently.  The look of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PTMKYS7?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has evolved into something more sleek and not like the traditional Oculus look. This is because Oculus was not the designer of the Rift S, that job was given to Lenovo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PTMKYS7?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; connects to a PC via as 3.0 USB port and also uses a DisplayPort connection. Since it is a PC-powered headset, it gives you the experience of more powerful VR experiences. Similar to other VR headsets, you’ll find goggle-type lens over your eyes when you wear the headset. This enables you to view the VR world in 3D mode. It moves along real-world movements, for example if you look right, your VR companion will also turn right. At the back of the headset, the new design boasts innovation, where there is a curved, cushioned plastic mould that goes around the base of your skull and the forehead. As in all previous designs, there’s velcro for tightening, but is not the main feature. The package also includes two Oculus controllers that track movements. This is in contrast to the motion tracking sensors that required USB port connections and have you connect cables all around your room. These controllers are not rechargeable and are battery powered instead, with one controller using a single AA battery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another design difference is the audio system. There are no more over-the-ear-earphones but instead you find speakers inside the headband. This cuts off players from what’s happening outside in the real world. There is also a 3.5mm port on the side where you can choose to connect your own headset. Unlike the original Rift, which had cameras externally placed to figure out movements, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PTMKYS7?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has cameras on the headset where it figures out controller movements and uses that for your VR experience. This feature has been described as an “inside-out” approach, and Amazon buyers have reviewed this new system as more efficient, with reports of no breaks in motion in case of sensor losing the headset. It has been aptly described as a “plug-and-play” headset. There is a built-in microphone also included in this set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users report more ease in setting up the headset, including a shorter overall setup time. One advantage is also having lesser USB ports to worry about. For people who wear glasses, customers have reviewed the headset and found it is spacious enough to accomodate. A button on the side enables users to move the lenses towards or away from your face. Lenses themselves have been touted as being better at withstanding scratches. The IPD (interpupillary distance) adjustment, for people who require between-eye adjustment of the lens, has a range of 58-72mm. This cannot be changed mechanically and is instead software based. The display system is a marked improvement from the previous, with buyers reporting much sharper pictures and clarity. Text is also clearer and the “halo” effect around the edges is reported to be gone from this model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customer reviews were not happy with the addition of the one displayport cable, as people find it harder to connect to a laptop, which often uses traditional HDMI cable slots. And the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PTMKYS7?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; does not work with HDMI. Most gaming laptops also do not have DisplayPort. However, it does come with a mini DisplayPort adapter. Issues with audio are also frequently reported, with the lack of bass being the most recurring complaint among users. People have described the audio of this headset as being subpar compared to the model and price point. It uses directional audio to send sound towards the general direction of your ears. Thankfully, you can plug in your own Bose headphones to accomodate. However, some users do fear that some headphone models may not be able to fit over the bulky design. Foam rubber padding that is surrounded around the eye area is not removable, and hence makes it harder to clean. It is also reported to be tighter around the eyes, where you cannot peak out at all. For some people, this gets suffocating and things can heat up. The nose piece is also tight, letting no light come through, and is observed by users as being very hard to pop back in place if it pops out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we talk about the controllers, they are described as being lighter in weight and feel comfortable in your hand. They do not take a lot of time in getting used to, as mentioned by most Amazon reviewers. In only a couple hours of use, customers reported being able to manage the controllers efficiently. One important thing to take into consideration is the fact that the cameras present inside the headset are reviewed as not working in dim lighting. This should not come as a surprise since light is required for the sensors to detect movement. The “passthrough”, a feature many had been looking forward to, has been described as choppy and falling short of the mark. You should also be aware that this headset will also not work if you have Windows 7. It is designed to be compatible with Windows 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, it is recommended for first time VR users, but those who are looking to upgrade their existing setup may find they can do without.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Virtual Reality" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>