<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-10-15T10:16:27+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Alienware-M15-Gaming-Laptop-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Alienware-M15-Gaming-Laptop-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Alienware-M15-Gaming-Laptop-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the gamer circles, Dell’s &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a brand name well known for big and chunkier gaming systems, something that most people weren’t a fan of. But with the all-new &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, it’s quite evident to see Alienware tried to offer a portable gaming laptop on par with rival systems like Razer Blade 15 and MSI GS65 Stealth Thin. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is 18mm thick/0.7inch, making it their most slimmest gaming laptop to date. It’s no secret that the competition has a better hold over the market when it comes to powerful and portable game systems, but with the entry of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the market, you might find it on par with the current standing competitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we touch on the specs a little, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a heavy Intel Core i7 processor, Nvidia Max-Q GPU, and Windows 10 Pro operating system. If you prefer more GPU power, just plug in Alienware’s custom amplifier and a desktop graphics card. Weighing at 4.8 pounds, or 2.16kg, this gaming laptop is the most lightweight Alienware equipment ever, surpassing its predecessor. However, it is not the most lightweight in the overall gaming laptops category. The lid of the laptop is made from anodized aluminium, with the trademark backlit LED alien head logo in the middle. The top lid has a smooth downward slope and plastic vents adorn the back, as well as the bottom. The display boasts a 15.6-inch size with reports of the LED displaying high-quality colors and visuals. Alienware display has always been touted as one of the most vibrant experiences you can get, and the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; gives you a 150% reproduction of sRGB color gamut, which is on par with the Stealth Thin. The ports include 3 USB 3.0 connections, a gigabit Ethernet port, HDMI, mini display port, and a USB-C with Thunderbolt 3. All this with the addition of a Graphics Amplifier port, offering PCIe x16 bandwidth for external Graphics dock if gamers decide to go that path. The Alienware Graphics Amplifier (AGA) port is described to be a proprietary connection for Alienware’s proprietary eGPU system (meaning you can’t use it with non-Alienware computers). Standard SKUs come equipped with Killer 1550 with integrated Bluetooth 5, with advantages of having Killer Control Center software and customizable network prioritization features in the Alien Command Center program. Gamers that have used this laptop have reviewed that they have been able to adjust some things, like the keyboard backlit color, but not all settings. Overall, you get a much smaller profile with lesser weight, a new keyboard, and a full internal revamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enough about the specs, you came here for the reviews. People described it as “surprisingly light despite a burly-looking machine”. It was reported to have no flexing in the base and being solidly put-together. The lid and hinges were said to have no wiggles, creaks or flops and held reasonably stiff. Apart from gaming, buyers said it to be a good choice for other intensive tasks like photo/video editing. The screen has been touted as one of the best features of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, being anti-glare with a matte finish, which doesn’t require one to turn on the brightness level to the highest setting. With buyers who used it for lighter work like browsing the web or lightweight work, the battery lasts 4 hours on average, unplugged, screen set at minimum brightness. Some gamers appreciated the dual-channel RAM for a performance boost. Regarding keyboard, key travel was said to be decent, and size sufficient enough for most. Backlighting was touted to be great, with six RGB zones. However, most people found the keyboard’s rubber finishing to be off-putting due to being a “fingerprint magnet”, albeit easy to clean with a soft cloth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, some downgrades had to be made in order to present the masses with a bite-sized hardware version. There is no SD card reader present, which was absent in the larger models as well. The battery is on the smaller side, which means performance suffers about 30% when unplugged. Regarding weight, the m15 still lags with regards to competition. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has reports of utilizing a “connected” standby feature, which enables it to still receive updates. This also uses more battery life (approximately 1% per hour) and has been reported to waking up when it’s not supposed to, like when it’s in a backpack. To bypass this, gamers go for the hibernate setting instead. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has issues with heating, where the i7-8750H has a max temp of 100 degrees, the performance pushes it too close to that temperature for some people’s comfort. As a laptop too, well, put in your lap, it is not a good option because the air intake vents are present on the bottom. One person shared that the top area of their keyboard reached 130 degrees F, as measured by their infrared thermometer, and an internal temperature around 200F. Most users had to raise their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; about an inch off the surface to achieve good airflow. This seems to be a recurring issue in ultrabook-sized laptops, where there is not enough space for adequate airflow. That’s not too surprising, given that downscaling is a hard line to walk, where you lose some to win some.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To summarize, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Thin and Light 15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is well built with a competitive price point, although it can still vastly improve some flaws that come with downscaling. As long as Alienware continues to improve and build upon performance as well as aesthetics, they’re likely to be a sure-fire win amongst the gaming category sometime soon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Alienware" /><category term="Laptop" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bose Soundtouch 30 Wireless Speakers Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-SoundTouch-30-Wireless-Speakers-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bose Soundtouch 30 Wireless Speakers Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-SoundTouch-30-Wireless-Speakers-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-SoundTouch-30-Wireless-Speakers-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is that most of us can’t get enough of listening to our favorite music. Whether you are working in your private office or lounging in your living room, sounds can elevate the experience. If you enjoy music, then you might always need your favorite tunes for motivation, relaxation, or to enhance your overall ambiance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While expensive headphones promise the delivery of high-quality audio, they can only go so far in terms of relaxation and flexibility. That is where wireless speakers come in and provide a level of comfort and ease that remains unmatched by other devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Wireless Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises the same flexibility while also letting users enjoy high-quality audio. Sporting Bose’s waveguide technology with premium drivers, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; claims to spread rich sound in even the largest rooms by connecting to devices such as Amazon Echo, or just about any smartphone for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To deliver high-quality sound with clarity and depth, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports all popular audio formats, including AAC, Apple Lossless, MP3, and WMA. At the same time, it also comes with dependable wireless connectivity in terms of Wi-Fi and Bluetooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Wireless Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; connects with any Amazon Echo device, it offers full support for Amazon Alexa. All that users have to do to listen to their music is ask Alexa to play it for them. But those who don’t have an Amazon Echo device can still depend on the speaker’s Bluetooth and Wi-Fi connectivity.  The connectivity allows them to play their music manually through compatible devices. With it, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a built-in OLED display, and a separate remote with six presets, which makes it easier to manage playlists and skip through stations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such,  one can see that regardless of Amazon Echo availability, the Bose SoundTouch 30 could easily play music from different platforms. Through wireless connectivity and its intuitive remote, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could play tunes from popular streaming services including but not limited to Spotify, SiriusXM, iTunes, and Pandora.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is extremely easy to set up. It is so simple and to the point where it only takes a couple of minutes to connect it to a new device. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is built to work with other Bose SoundTouch family of speakers, it also connects with additional speakers seamlessly. This is possible due to its wireless network functionality, which connects to such devices through 802.11 b/g/n. Users note that this quality to grow the speaker collection as users see fit adds a ton of flexibility to the speaker’s utilization, while also delivering complete surround sound at the users’ terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speaker’s sound quality gets praised by those who look for deep, rich, yet clear audio. It has been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can deliver high volume sounds while still being able to retain the audio quality and clarity. This makes it a highly sought after device for audiophiles looking to fill their home or office with their favorite music. Some have gone as far as to term it as the best speaker that they have ever used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also note that it is quite easy to adjust audio levels in the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Those who like a certain amount of bass in their audio could quickly get it by tweaking a few settings. Those who want more clarity could also make their required changes rapidly. Users note that overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; delivers the desired quality of audio for any music enthusiast with just a few tweaks and changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While being used through Bluetooth devices, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports a 30 feet range when connected. Users have noted that this provides the listener with quite some flexibility. It has also been noted that this makes the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a great addition for larger rooms, where the devices being connected are far apart. The remote control only adds to this flexibility and allows users to enjoy changing their music even when they are at a certain distance from the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Measured at the dimensions of 7.1 x 17.1 x 9.7 inches, users praise the overall size of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Weighing 18.5lbs, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a bit heavy to carry around. But given that it is powered through an electric cord and is meant to be used as a stationary speaker anyway, the weight does not diminish its value proposition for its users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also praise the overall look of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Made with high-quality materials and sporting a modern design, the device projects a sleek style. One that is appreciated by those who are fans of this aesthetic. The OLED only enhances the speaker’s look, and the design itself lets the audio shine through whenever music goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bose claims that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is extremely easy to connect with other devices. But some users take issue with that promise. According to them, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is not very user-friendly when it comes to connecting with other Bose SoundTouch devices, and provides a delay in the audio. With that being said, they still agree that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; works great as a standalone device. At the same time, other users state no such issues and seem to have no problems connecting their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with other Bose speakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Wireless Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides its users with a rich and vibrant sound quality that is desired by every audiophile. With high-quality materials, multiple connectivity options, and support for Amazon Alexa, it could be a great addition to any enthusiast’s collection. Use it as a standalone speaker or as part of a surround sound system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Bose SoundTouch" /><category term="Wireless Speakers" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hp Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-590-Desktop-Computer-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hp Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-590-Desktop-Computer-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-590-Desktop-Computer-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to buying an affordable new computer for your home or business, having a limited budget gets you limited advancements in technology. If you want an advanced machine, then your budget has to be over a certain threshold. Otherwise, you have to compromise on the machine’s performance in exchange for affordability. But it doesn’t have to be that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With renewed or refurbished computers, you can enjoy faster performance and the latest technology without having to spend a fortune. This way, you can save money, but without having to choose the compromise route. These computers are good as new and often come with the seller’s guarantee, which gives you a safety net and plenty of time to test the machine before you decide to keep it for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The renewed &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises to fit those needs perfectly. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a 2.8 GHz Intel Core i5-8400 processor, 8 GB of RAM, and 16 GB of Intel Optane memory. It also has a 1 TB hard disk drive (HDD), which also comes with a 12-month offer of free 25 GB Dropbox cloud storage. To top it all off, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with Windows 10 as its operating system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To fit users’ multimedia needs, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; sports built-in Intel UHD Graphics 630. With it, it also comes with a DVD-writer. Connectivity is offered through Wi-Fi 802.11ac, Bluetooth 4.2, as well as multiple USB ports. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a headphone and microphone combo port, 5.1 surround sound output, and 1 HDMI plugin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elaborating on the connectivity ports, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has 3 USB 3.1 ports, with one of them being a USB Type-C port. But the connectivity options don’t end there since it also has 4 USB 2.0 ports. All of this is encased in a silver rig casing that has a modern, geometric patterned design with a brushed texture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to practical usage, these features translate into a potent machine at an affordable price point. Since the model is renewed, it comes with a massive price reduction for a product that is good as new and comes with Amazon’s 90-day Renewed Guarantee. Users have noted that while they had been worried about buying a refurbished computer, it turned out to be the right choice and provided excellent value for money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The refurbished status of this &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; had kept some users suspect about their purchase since the time of placing their order. But after receiving the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, they seem to have left their worries behind. Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; they received is indeed good as new and works like it is supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have also noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to its claims and provides the speed that it promises. It has been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; boots up fast and operates smoothly as well, which takes away the possibility of any lagging issues in operating applications. This is possible due to the 8th generation, 2.8 GHz Intel Core i5 processor, 8GB DDR4 RAM, and 16 GB Intel Optane Memory, which turns the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; into a powerhouse of a performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also makes for a good upgrade for those users who have been using older machines for a while. With the latest processor, increased memory, wireless connectivity options, and stellar graphics, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; fulfills the users’ work, study or entertainment needs quite well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also seem to be satisfied with the multimedia performance of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; offers multiple connectivity options with a DVD-writer and a 7200RPM SATA HDD, it allows users to enjoy their entertainment options through various mediums. The built-in Intel UHD Graphics 630 allows for smooth multimedia streaming and gaming, which serves the needs of those users who buy the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with entertainment in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with its built-in graphics, users have noted that those who want hardcore gaming could actually install another graphics card. To do so, they just need to change the power supply to allow for the addition of a more powerful graphics card that is specifically built for gaming. According to the users who have already done this, the action has upgraded their machine significantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have also praised how the machine looks in its dimensions of 10.9 x 6.69 x 13.3 inches. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in a shortened tower or rig shape, it projects a modern outlook to everyone. It’s silver-colored exterior, and just 16.2lbs of weight also add to its overall looks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to points that have created issues for users, it has been noted that the vertical built of the DVD-writer has caused some problems for users who wanted more comfort with a horizontally fit DVD-writer. Another issue that a couple of users have noted is how their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was dead on arrival. They returned the machine promptly, but it is still something that needs to be kept in mind for those who might face such issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; makes for a powerful machine that fits the need of the everyday user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one issue with renewed or refurbished machines is that they could be dead on arrival. But as users have noted, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could be returned promptly. In such cases, you should just know how to reach out to Amazon customer service, and they would be able to help you return the machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains a great choice for those who are looking for value for money. Those who want more performance out of their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could smoothly go the route of upgrading the RAM or the graphics card and use the machine according to their needs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="HP Pavilion" /><category term="Desktop Computer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pimax 5k Plus Virtual Reality Headset Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Pimax-5K-Plus-Virtual-Reality-Headset-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pimax 5k Plus Virtual Reality Headset Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Pimax-5K-Plus-Virtual-Reality-Headset-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Pimax-5K-Plus-Virtual-Reality-Headset-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world of digital entertainment is changing at a rapid pace. The once cutting edge 3D-gaming technology is quickly being replaced by virtual reality (VR), which lets users dive into gaming as they have never imagined before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With completely realistic environments and an experience that is close to life, VR gaming is leaving other gaming modes behind. Those who enjoy gaming and hold unique machines in terms of gaming desktops or laptops are now turning to VR-powered devices to get the most out of their gaming experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is built with these ideas in mind. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has been developed to deliver a seamless VR experience to the wearer. As such, this allows them to immerse themselves in digital entertainment. It is available in a special offer by Amazon and comes at an affordable price. Remember that controllers and base stations could be purchased separately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sporting dual custom low persistence liquid crystal panels with a combined resolution of 5120x1440 pixels and a 200° diagonal field of view (FOV), the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes equipped with the means to deliver VR content in a unique and indulging way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; uses premium quality materials, sturdy ergonomic build, and support for almost all Steam and Oculus Home VR content. It also supports VR controllers and technology by most other brands, such as other brand Steam controllers as well as the SteamVR Lighthouse 1.0 and 2.0 tracking technology&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also created with those in mind who wear prescription glasses. The headset has enough room to fit most prescription glasses frames, while it also provides IPD adjustment through hardware and software modes. This adjustment aspect ensures that everyone has a picture-perfect vision for their VR content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is compatible with most high-end gaming computers. Specifically, the minimum PC specifications are Nvidia GTX 1070 graphics card, with AMD equivalent accepted; 8 GB RAM; Windows 8 OS; Intel Core i5-4590 or AMD FX 8350; DP 1.4 video output; and 1 USB 2.0 port. The higher the user’s computer specifications are, the better it is in terms of the overall experience. For example, if you have a USB 3.0 port, then it is all the better to use it than strictly meet the minimum requirement of a USB 2.0 port.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is on par with other similar, VR headsets in terms of its size. Its dimensions are 11.1 x 4.3 x 5.4 inches, with a total weight of 1lb. These dimensions make it small and lightweight enough to wear comfortably for those who plan to immerse themselves in VR content now and then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in a single color choice, which is black with ambient blue light at the front. It is made with durable yet comfortable material that once again adds to the total wear time without taking its toll on the user. While the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; does not come with any base stations, it does support external equipment in the form of HTC Vive Lighthouse 1.0 or 2.0 base stations, as well as the Valve Index Lighthouse base stations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to actual use, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; gets rave reviews from its users. Dubbed as the “next generation” of VR headsets by one user, the gadget is praised for its smooth content delivery that comes without any choppy video. Users have also noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides the widest FOV that they have experienced in any other headset, which makes it all the more appealing to those gamers who do not want to miss out on even a single pixel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The superwide FOV is the crown jewel of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. As the feature that sets the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; apart from its competition, the FOV gets the headset its most positive reviews. This is possible due to the dual custom low persistence liquid crystal panels, and their combined resolution of 5120x1440 pixels, which provide ample support to the truly exceptional 200° diagonal FOV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the FOV makes sure that they are not missing out on anything during their gaming experience. The way that the wide FOV almost eliminates the screen door effect (SDE) and provides a high-quality VR experience is something that practically all users highlight about the headset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also praise the VR content support. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports over 95 percent of the content on Steam VR and Oculus Home, users have a plethora of options to choose from, including famous titles such as Fallout 4 VR and The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim VR. This is another quality that makes &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; a good option for avid gamers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, users have complained about the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5k plus VR Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; needing a very high-end machine to pull off its operations optimally. Some users also mention that the plastic strap attached to the headset seems cheap and out of line with the rest of the structure. But these complaints remain minimal, and users seem to like what they see in terms of the overall performance of the headset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JZL5QK3?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pimax 5K Plus Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; makes for a great VR device. While this offer comes with just the headset, it is considerably affordable and better in performance as compared to other devices in its class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, the superwide FOV, high-quality imaging, and an astounding content library make the headset an excellent choice for any gaming enthusiast.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Pimax" /><category term="Virtual Reality" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Braun Series 9 Men Electric Foil Shaver With Wet Dry Integrated Precision Trimmer Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Braun-Series-9-Men-Electric-Foil-Shaver-with-Wet-Dry-Integrated-Precision-Trimmer-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Braun Series 9 Men Electric Foil Shaver With Wet Dry Integrated Precision Trimmer Review" /><published>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Braun-Series-9-Men-Electric-Foil-Shaver-with-Wet-Dry-Integrated-Precision-Trimmer-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Braun-Series-9-Men-Electric-Foil-Shaver-with-Wet-Dry-Integrated-Precision-Trimmer-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems like every other shaver and razor manufacturer out there loves to brag about their new technological advancement and updated models, but disappointingly they come out no better than the old ones. Except for &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. A household staple name &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is well known across the globe for staying on top of their game. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; latest, the Series 9 Shaver models are one of the best you can invest in. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; history of using long and sometimes complicated descriptions of their technologies are always up to par. Did they succeed this time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one of the most advanced electric shavers out there. This model is a foil-type shaver, providing close shaves and features an extra cutting element, coming out to a total of 4 foil shaving elements. These 4 shaving components are flexible, making sure you get a comfortable touch and a smooth shave. Due to their flexibility, they can mould to any angle and face shape while shaving. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a pivoting head that moves in no less than 10 directions. This means no more struggling with trouble spots and facial cuts in the mornings while you’re in a hurry to get ready. Now, it is true that sometimes you need a steady, stable head and not a rotating one to deliver that optimal shave. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also incorporates a lock feature for the head in order to keep it in one place, in an angle you think fits. The motor the 9296cc model is equipped with uses Synchronized technology to create “40,000 cross-cutting actions per minute”. Compare this to the previous Series 7 models, which only provided 10,000 cuts per minute. This performance level ensures you get super-fast shaving in no time. As a bonus, users report minimal sound noise while using the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; electric shaver. However, the biggest touted feature of this electric razor is its wet/dry shave technology. You can either use this for fast, dry shaving or you can use gel, soap, water, or shaving foam. You can even use this in the shower, as the shaver is 100% waterproof. The body is made with both premium plastic and metal. The handle where you grab the shaver is made out of rubber, which makes it easier to not have it slip out of your hands while you’re using it in the shower, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the best feature of this shaver is the base that it comes with. This is the only electric razor that is equipped with lubricant for the blades and alcohol-based cleaning fluid as well as serving as the charging station. The base automatically takes care of cleaning, charging, lubricating and drying of the shaver for your next use. The shaver comes with Lithium-ion rechargeable batteries. Buyers report their shaver lasts 50 minutes on average when used cordless after being charged for an hour. A full hour is what it takes for a full cycle of recharge time. There is also the option of quick charging, giving you a 5-minute charging option for when you need it urgently but are short on time. Amazon reviewers say this feature is good enough for a full quick shave. An LED display is present on the shaver, showing battery remaining, indication of recharge, a travel lock feature, cleaning indication (eco, normal or deep clean) and so on. A slide-up trimmer has been integrated into this model for those precise shaving of sideburns or moustaches. The travel lock feature is for when you press the power button for 3 seconds in case of travel, preventing the head from automatically turning on. Lastly, this purchase comes with a travel case for your needs. A multi-volt charging adapter ensures you don’t need to worry about fitting into electrical outlets and such.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we talk about how the performance fared with buyers, customers loved that the dry shave option gave as good a shave as a wet one, with no skin irritations. The shaver is reported to give a fine, close-cut without leaving your face looking red, with most users saying they ended up ditching razor blades and rotary shavers for life after this purchase. One user described it as “the Rolls Royce of razors, the ultimate electric shaver”. The cleaning system is unanimously agreed to not be a marketing gimmick but work as intended, a quick wash underwater and you’re good to go. Manual cleaning is simple, popping off the foil head and brushing away excess hair. It is further described as not feeling like cheap plastic and feels the right amount of heavy in the hand. It even works out for people who are not fond of shaving or find themselves chronically short on time in the mornings, as many customers echo the sentiment that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver with Wet &amp;amp; Dry Integrated Precision Trimmer &amp;amp; Rechargeable and Cordless Razor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; does the job quickly and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Negative reviews were few and far between, still gaining an average rating of 3/5 stars. These reviewers were more partial to the Series 7, or even Series 5, and did not click well with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F7XYMNN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Braun Series 9 Men’s Electric Foil Shaver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; . Head size was reported to be a bit larger than average, making it difficult for some people to get a good, even shaving performance. Cleaning refills need to be brought regularly for the cleaning feature. The overwhelming consensus seems to be that with this device, even though the upfront cost seems to be high, you get what you paid for and is worth the price and investment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Electric Foil Shaver" /><category term="Trimmer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dhp Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk And Bookcase Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/DHP-Studio-Loft-Bunk-Bed-Over-Desk-and-Bookcase-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dhp Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk And Bookcase Review" /><published>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/DHP-Studio-Loft-Bunk-Bed-Over-Desk-and-Bookcase-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/DHP-Studio-Loft-Bunk-Bed-Over-Desk-and-Bookcase-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living in small houses, apartments, or rooms is not out of the ordinary for anyone who exists in this dense and populous modern world. This notion holds true for urban areas, where saving space is quite a significant issue. It is crucial to the point of being a priority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why wouldn’t it be? If you have a small area to live in, the first thing that you would want to do is to save some space by buying less furniture. But then, you would be void of necessities such as a desk, or even a bed. To make sure that you could decorate your home with the required furniture and still not feel like you are living in a cramped space, you could turn to specially crafted space-saving furniture. Both space and pocket-friendly, this furniture is a big hit for those living in small spaces or those who simply want a modern looking piece of furniture in their vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk and Bookcase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one such cost and space-saving option that doesn’t only stay light on your pocket but pulls off that feat while looking pretty as a picture. Made completely out of a metal frame, the bunk bed is built in a way that is both sturdy and stylish at the same time. It sports a striking design that features a desk on the left and a bookcase on the right, with a bunk bed going on top of them and completing the structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a size that accommodates a twin mattress and provides ample room for the desk and bookcase underneath, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk and Bookcase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides sufficient room for work and sleep at the same time. With that being said, even though the bunk bed combo is built as space-saving furniture, it promises to strike a perfect balance between utility and aesthetics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With sturdy metal, strategic design, and beautiful finish, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; combo is built to be an example of craftsmanship and claims to hold weight up to 200lbs. It comes in three colors, namely black, silver, and white. It also offers a sturdily-built, fixed ladder design that allows its users to hop on and climb down the bed with comfort and safety. The bed section of the structure also has safety rails and slats, while the remainder of the structure is also filled with strategically placed rails that add to its safety as well as its overall look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk and Bookcase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; offers easy assembly and doesn’t require any foundation to stand. The whole structure weighs about 146lbs while sporting the dimensions of 41.5 x 77.5 x 74 inches. This design makes the structure almost as tall as its length and makes it a real example of vertical-space furniture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to practical use, many users note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; combo holds up to its promises. Users have pointed out that it looks good in real life, and makes for a great piece of multi-purpose furniture for rooms that are in dire need of space-saving. This feature makes it ideal for kids and teenagers, while also being quite beneficial for college students who live in small apartments or dorm rooms. With that, the bunk bed combo also appeals to those adults who live in smaller spaces or who want to decorate their homes with modern and space-saving vertical furniture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several users note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk and Bookcase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is indeed easy to assemble. Users do not need an expert to install and fix their structure. From putting together the structure to finish the look with a mattress, users perceive the experience to be quite an easy task that could be handled by anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have also noted that the structure’s material is quite sturdy and could hold weight according to its manufacturer’s claims. Since the ladder is fixed into the bed frame through screws and preset holes to fit them in, it also stays in place even as larger adults climb on or off the bed. The overall aesthetic of the structure is also praised by users, who state that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was according to their expectations and made a good addition to their homes and rooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two issues that get noted by some users as being problematic are the roughness of the ladder rungs and the restriction on putting the ladder on the side of the preset holes. According to a few users, the ladder rungs feel quite rough against their feet. Whereas, others complain about not being able to choose a side to fix the ladder. Since the holes to fix the screws are already made in the bed frame, users have to install the ladder on the preset side by default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, other users feel pretty satisfied with the product. As for the ladder issue, some have gone as far as to fix it themselves by making holes in their preferred side of the structure to install the ladder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk and Bookcase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; earns quite a bit of praise from its users. It seems to be an excellent choice for those who want to save space while not compromising style and comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, if you are one to be aggravated by not being able to choose a side for the ladder, then you should be mindful of that restriction and take measures to fix it accordingly. Other than that, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; combo seems to be quite excellent in fulfilling users’ expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07K4424RZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DHP Studio Loft Bunk Bed Over Desk and Bookcase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is functional and beautiful. It is perfect for minimalists and those who like to keep things as simple as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Bunk Neds" /><category term="Bookcase" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hp Pavilion 24 Inch All In One Computer Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-24-Inch-All-in-One-Computer-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hp Pavilion 24 Inch All In One Computer Review" /><published>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-24-Inch-All-in-One-Computer-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-24-Inch-All-in-One-Computer-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this day and age where technology is more of a necessity than a luxury, having a desktop machine is highly crucial for any humble abode. Whether it is used as a communication tool, an entertainment center, or a research device, a computer could serve many purposes for each member of a typical household. A laptop can help connect one to a world of endless opportunities and provide significant value overall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since compact and modern options are now the norm in every technological device, desktop computers are no exception to the rule. Gone are the days where every household had to have a desktop rig. Now, those machines are only reserved for hardcore gaming or rendering purposes. An all-in-one computer where the engine is built into the screen is the new normal for home use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one such compact desktop machine that’s built for the whole family. Sporting a 1.8 GHz Intel Core i5-9400T processor, 12 GB of RAM, 512 GB Solid State Drive (SSD), Intel UHD Graphics 630, and Windows 10 Home OS, the computer promises to fit the needs of everyone, whether they want to watch Netflix, browse the web, or make video calls all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The desktop all-in-one station has a 1080p Full HD 23.8” diagonal IPS touchscreen, which allows users to enjoy their content to optimal clarity seamlessly. The FHD capability gives users the power to consume high-quality content in the comfort of their home, while the 10-point touch-enabled screen gives them the ability to operate the computer through their fingertips. With it, the desktop also comes with Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen (B&amp;amp;O) audio for its dual speakers, which elevates the multimedia experience to the next level with high-quality audio delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since everything is settled under the screen in a compact yet powerful machine, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; doesn’t have a separate desktop rig. Connectivity ports for USB 3.1, USB 3.1 Type-C, HDMI In, HDMI Out, and 3-in-1 media card reader are all available at the back of the screen - which remains ultra-slim despite its power. A port for microphone/headphone combo is also available next to them. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a built-in FHD webcam, which allows users to make video calls right off the bat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from these physical connectivity options, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with wireless connectivity in terms of Bluetooth 4.2 and Wi-Fi 802.11a/b/g/n/ac. The SSD makes sure that users could copy and transfer data within seconds instead of minutes and ensures complete efficiency in running the computer for everyday applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with built-in Intel UHD Graphics 630, which allows users to perform graphics-based tasks and play some of the most popular games with ease. If users need to upgrade the 12 GB RAM to meet their gaming needs, then they could opt for a 16 GB RAM option as well. For ultimate comfort, they could also go for wireless keyboard and mouse that connect through Bluetooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of practical use, users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to its claims of performance. With the six-core, 1.8 GHz Intel i5-9400T processor and 12 GB of RAM, users seem quite satisfied with performing their day to day work, study or entertainment-related activities on the computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many users also note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; seems to deliver in terms of the rich multimedia experience, which is due to its FHD support, B&amp;amp;O audio, and built-in graphics. With it, users have noted that the computer is quite elementary to set up once it arrives at their doorstep. Since there are minimal wires to be fixed especially when compared to a traditional desktop, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; gets settled on a desk within a few minutes. Users have noted that the computer itself walks them through the setup, and helps them initialize its first run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there, it has been noted that the computer fulfills every expectation that it advertises. Apart from fulfilling multimedia tasks, it does well on the communication front, and also seems to deliver on work-related tasks where users need to be using multiple applications during the course of their computer activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To top it all off, users seem to like the HP-powered tech support that comes with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a 1-year limited warranty, which is there to help users if their home computer stops working all of a sudden or presents significant performance issues&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one thing that some users have pointed out as being a slight issue with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is the limitation in terms of graphics. But that is understandable since the home computing machine is an all-in-one machine and not a gaming rig.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; fulfills every promise that it makes. With the ability to upgrade certain aspects, it could meet the expectations of some of the most technologically-savvy families or individuals who want the best value for money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put together, all of these qualities seem to set the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; as one of the most robust and most user-friendly products in its regard. Since the computer is new and comes with a 1-year limited warranty, it could be a good option for those who are looking for a safety net with each significant purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you are using it for work or play, this &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07SGH132Y?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 24-Inch All-in-One Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is sure to meet your every need.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="HP Pavilion" /><category term="Computer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Segway Ninebot Es2 Folding Electric Kick Scooter Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Segway-Ninebot-ES2-Folding-Electric-Kick-Scooter-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Segway Ninebot Es2 Folding Electric Kick Scooter Review" /><published>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Segway-Ninebot-ES2-Folding-Electric-Kick-Scooter-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Segway-Ninebot-ES2-Folding-Electric-Kick-Scooter-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a world where cars are growing more expensive than ever, more and more people are looking into alternative vehicles as a viable option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promising lesser costs than traditional cars and also being fun to ride, electric scooters have lately taken the transportation market by storm. From going out on rent to being sold for nominal prices, these scooters are genuinely appealing to those who want to adopt modern ways to fulfill their everyday travel requirements. But at the same time, who also intend to make their rides full of joy and comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Folding Electric Kick Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;follows the same notion of making the outdoors fun for everyone while making travel more cost-effective. Produced by the leading brand in electric scooters, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is powered through an electric battery of 187 Wh. It scooter can reach an impressive speed of up to 15.5 mph, while also sporting the ability to travel up to 15.5 miles on a single charge of 3.5 hours. For those wanting to be clear, that makes it about 25 km on a single charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At just 27.6lbs, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is lightweight. The quality of being foldable with only one click adds to its value and makes it easier to carry around than most other scooters in its class. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; demonstrates a minimal power of 300 W, with the maximum going up to 700 W. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also technologically up to date, with features such as an LED display, Bluetooth connectivity, and installation of upgrades through a dedicated app that could be operated through your smartphone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; scooter also comes with additional features such as an LED headlight and reflectors as well as customizable ambient lights, which make it look good while also adding to the safety of the rider. Also adding to the safety aspect are front and rear shock absorbers, which make riding a comfortable yet safe experience. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has a mechanical and electrical anti-lock braking system, which enhances the safety aspect. It can endure a maximum rider weight of up to 220lbs, which makes it a good choice for anyone who is interested in riding a scooter but have their doubts on whether it would hold their weight or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in a dark grey color. While this lessens the variety in its aesthetics, it looks quite impressive in its single color form. The material used throughout the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is high quality and durable, which provides the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with a premium quality structure that is built to last through consistent folds and trips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to users, this makes the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; a very good option in terms of value for money. It has also been noted that with its maximum power, electric kick start, and easy handling, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could be a good fit for many different lifestyles. Whether users are trying to ride their scooter to work, or simply taking a stroll around the neighborhood, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; serves various commute and recreational purposes optimally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is very easy to assemble. At the same time, it is just as simple to operate and update through its app connectivity. This makes it a great option for those who are riding a scooter of this class for the very first time. It has also been noted that despite its technological advancements, the scooter’s app interface is very user-friendly, and lets users go through the necessary settings with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing that gets a lot of praise is the comfortable ride provided by the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. With a smooth electric kick start, seamless speed control, and 7.5 inch large solid tires, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; steers clear of any uncomfortable jots and jumps for the rider. What adds to this ability are the front and rear shock absorbers that are installed within the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Users have also noted that the ambient lights serve their purpose optimally, and add to the scooter’s look while also taking care of safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that many users take the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; scooter over their daily commute, which is possible due to the scooter’s lightweight and one-click folding structure. The double-braking system assures them that no matter the amount of traffic that they face, they would get a safe braking distance to keep themselves as well as others out of harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to technological capabilities, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides various high-end options that conventional scooters don’t offer at all. Through their smartphones, users could learn how to ride the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, manage its speed limits, change cruise control settings, and lock their vehicles with anti-theft functions. As mentioned above, the scooter’s firmware could also be updated with ease by users who have downloaded the app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has earned generally favorable reviews from its users. Some allude to the battery time not giving a full 15.5 miles of ride distance. But that could be easily attributed to the manufacturer’s explanation about certain ride conditions affecting the battery time, such as riding on top of slopes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Folding Electric Kick Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains an excellent option for those who want an affordable vehicle of their own while also not having to worry about the safety aspect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one thing that users need to keep in mind is that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a speed limit. This is for their safety, but some users might not find it very appealing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; offers a compelling ride that is built through modern standards - while also being pretty affordable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The micro-mobility is just starting, and many people from young professionals to the older generation love to use it regularly. The technology is only getting better, and the experience should continue to improve each year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H8T9K9J?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Segway Ninebot ES2 Electric Scooter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a gift that is sure to please young and old alike.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Electric Kick Scooter" /><category term="Segway" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Xtremepowerus Mini Pocket Motorcycle Powered By Gasoline Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/XtremepowerUS-Mini-Pocket-Motorcycle-Powered-by-Gasoline-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Xtremepowerus Mini Pocket Motorcycle Powered By Gasoline Review" /><published>2019-10-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/XtremepowerUS-Mini-Pocket-Motorcycle-Powered-by-Gasoline-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/XtremepowerUS-Mini-Pocket-Motorcycle-Powered-by-Gasoline-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s day and age of smartphones and tablets, parents are more concerned about limiting their kids’ screen time than ever before. 
While being educated through these devices is important and getting familiarized with new technology remains crucial for the future progress of children, we all know that there is much more to life than tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also imperative that you get some outdoor playtime in the mix so they could get some physical exercise and thrive in a balanced environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But doing so is not easy. In a world where computer graphics could represent their imagination, kids are hardly interested in playing outdoor games. That is where parents’ creativity comes in, so they could introduce new ways to keep their kids involved in outdoor activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what’s the best way to accomplish this objective?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pocket bikes might be a straightforward solution. They are fun, safe, and enjoyable for kids, allowing parents to have peace of mind when their kids are out and about in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make sure that your kids get optimal playtime outside of their screens and the confinement of your home, you could turn to the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle Gasoline Bike Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the name suggests, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a smaller version of a conventional motorcycle. While it doesn’t literally fit into your pocket, it is of a size that is perfect for being a vehicle for kids. The motorcycle is powered by gasoline and provides the same riding experience that is offered by a conventional motorcycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comprises of a steel frame and chain drive transmission. It also has a 40cc 4-stroke engine, which is approved by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) due to being safe for the environment. The engine is also pull-start with a twist-grip throttle, which is reminiscent of a traditional motorcycle. The vehicle is powered by gasoline, which is reserved in its 1.2-liter tank. It claims to provide a mileage of 26 miles per filled tank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With one brake disc each in the front and rear, the motorcycle allows kids to make safe stops whenever they need them. To make sure that children stay safe during their drive, the motorcycle also provides automatic, one-speed transmission. Since the seat is padded and the handlebar angle is adjustable, the motorcycle also claims to give the kids a posture that makes riding the motorcycle a fun and comfortable experience for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to practical use, the 4-stroke, the gasoline-powered engine does its job quite efficiently and provides a real motorcycle riding experience to kids. It has been noted by users that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; emulates a conventional motorcycle perfectly, and lets kids enjoy the motorcycle riding experience in a way that’s suitable and safe for their age. Users also note that putting the motorcycle together from when it first gets delivered is too easy. All you need to do is to put the back tire on and adjust the handlebars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This feature of simplicity takes away from the worry of going to great lengths to put the motorcycle together. It is a busy world, you don’t have the time to sit down and figure out how to put a whole pocket bike motorcycle together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, the assembly of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one of those aspects that get lauded the most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motorcycle itself weighs 53lbs, while it supports rider weight of up to 165 lbs. With its high tensile steel frame, the motorcycle claims to have been built durably. Users have noted that the motorcycles are well-built and have proved quite durable with months of usage and consistent rides by their kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; uses a chain drive transmission along with its 4-stroke engine and needs gasoline for power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that its overall structure and operation is a wonderful way to teach kids about real motorcycles in terms of their functions and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, the motorcycle seems to be too small for kids over 10 to ride. Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; really takes to delivering the “mini” in its name, and proves to be too small for even 8-9-year-olds who are just a bit taller than their age. Seeing that most users who bought the motorcycle for older kids seem to be having this problem but those who have bought the motorcycle for smaller kids seem to be quite happy with it. It is best that you keep this in mind while making your purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in six different color combinations. From bright colors to neutral tones, the motorcycle provides you with the option to select something that would be an instant hit with your kid. Users have also noted that the motorcycle makes for a great gift item. Almost every kid it is gifted to goes over the moon with joy at receiving their own motorcycle that is specifically made for their size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075B1BM7M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;XtremepowerUS Mini Pocket Motorcycle Gasoline Bike Motorcycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains quite a great gift item for children because it provides plenty of fun, while also being an educational experience that would teach kids how to be responsible with their own vehicles when they reach adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, it should be noted that the small size of the motorcycle could be an issue if your child is taller than their age. However, that seems to be the only issue with the motorcycle. The other features seem to be extremely helpful for children who would be using their motorcycle every day without any problems.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Pocket Bike" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bose A20 Aviation Headset With Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-A20-Aviation-Headset-With-Bluetooth-Dual-Plug-Cable-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bose A20 Aviation Headset With Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable Review" /><published>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-A20-Aviation-Headset-With-Bluetooth-Dual-Plug-Cable-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-A20-Aviation-Headset-With-Bluetooth-Dual-Plug-Cable-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your work or hobby involves aviation by any chance, then you must know the importance of communication in the medium. In a medium where a single second’s delay or a slightly muffled sound could be life-threatening, your communication equipment must remain top of the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not having proper communication tools or experiencing poor audio while flying an aircraft can make you extremely anxious when the only feeling you should associate with the action is that of the utmost comfort, mixed with some adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, clear communication gives you the peace of mind that you require to fly correctly. It also enhances your experience in a way that leaves you feeling comfortable, and allows you to enjoy your flight the way that you are supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why you absolutely must choose a communication tool that you could rely upon no matter what. Doing so doesn’t only keep you safe, but it also takes care of the wellbeing of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to communication equipment that you can depend upon, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset with Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable, Black&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a class apart. When compared to traditional aviation headsets, it claims to provide higher active noise reduction, while also ensuring less clamping force. But it doesn’t stop there, and also offers active equalization along with customizable audio prioritization, as well as up to 45 hours of use from two AA batteries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When put together, these features provide the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with more than enough power to be identified as a strong communication tool, which could be very useful for those who are looking for a multipurpose headset to improve their flying experience. The fact that the headset is certified to FAA TSO-C139 and EASA ETSO-C139 standards further speak for its capabilities as an aviation communication tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headset also sports a comfortable design that is meant to make communications seamless during your flying experience. With an electret microphone that is built for clarity in relaying messages, the headset promises to be as reliable in transmitting outward communication as it is in delivering it. The microphone also comes with the ability to be plugged into either of the earcups, which adds yet another level of comfort for the user as they fly their plane or use the headset as a traditional communication device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it carries the traditional analog option, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has a strong feature in terms of Bluetooth wireless connectivity working for it. Since more and more communication and navigation devices now offer wireless connectivity, the Bluetooth feature improves the headset’s analog-only structure. With that being said, it is still available in an analog-only option, at a slightly lower price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Bose, its A20 headset provides 30 percent more active noise reduction and 30 percent less clamping force as compared to conventional aviation headsets. This quality makes the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; quite a favorable choice, since the more noise is reduced during aviation communication, the better it is for the pilot as well as the ones who are corresponding with them through the control tower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users, these features shine through in terms of their active communication, where the noise reduction and clarity in transmission are significantly noticeable. This holds true whether they are flying a small Cessna or a high noise helicopter. Users have also claimed that they can communicate very clearly even if their main volume is turned to a lower setting. This also makes the headset appeal to student pilots, who need to be extra-reliant on their communication during their training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also delivers on the aspect of sound quality and makes it so much easier to listen to music through a communication headset. While the Bose Active EQ feature adjusts the levels of audio notes in a communication or recording channel, the ergonomic control module lets you seamlessly switch between your communication and music. At the same time, it also lets you mix two audio channels at once. Multipoint connectivity enhances this feature and makes it easier to handle different communication channels. According to users, this feature adds to the ease of use that the headset promises to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is designed for extended use and utilizes high-quality materials, the headset is very comfortable to wear. Users have noted that the headset remains very lightweight, which is due to the high-quality plastic that it uses for its structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery life also provides great backup time whether you are communicating actively or just listening to music. This has been noted by various users, who term the headset as being worth every penny. They note how easy it is to communicate during each of their flights, while also ensuring that they don’t have to run around finding charging ports for their headset before every takeoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these qualities, users have gone on record to deem the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; as one of the best headsets for aviation that are currently available in the market. Nearly everyone who uses it is very happy with it, and their recommendations to others for buying their own pair of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; add to the overall credibility of the headset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, some users take issue with the material, since it is mostly plastic. But the lightweight and soft-touch add to the users’ comfort level, who argue against such complaints very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is safe to say that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset with Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable, Black&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a bold yet successful attempt by the company to strengthen its presence within the aviation industry further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With features that appeal to different levels of experience for various pilots, it remains an investment that could help you from learning to fly a plane to operating your small aircraft on your own with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pursue adventure and life with these headphones to accompany you and keep you in the know while you fly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Aviation Headset" /><category term="Bose Headset" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>