<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-10-27T15:28:26+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Real Life Joker Costume Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Real Life Joker Costume Review" /><published>2019-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review/">&lt;p&gt;We live in a society that loves Halloween. We all could agree that Halloween is easily one of the coolest parts of the year. You are getting free candy from your neighbors for no reason at all, freaking out because you don’t find the perfect idea for your costume this year, parents letting their children play with their friends, at night, with lots of disguised people all around. Michael Jackson’s private heaven. But this year, you don’t have to worry about which one could be the ideal costume for you. Costume &amp;amp; Customs is ready to help you be the laugh of your office’s Halloween Party this October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the world’s most highly regarded costume designer and manufacturer brings you the brand new Real Life Joker Costume Equipment. Taking advantage of the popularity of this year’s Joker movie starring Joaquin Phoenix, the people from Costumes &amp;amp; Customs has developed a hyperrealistic Joker costume.  That allows you to experience what Phoenix felt when he was performing as the Joker. Without overwhelming success, worldwide recognition, and undisputed wealth. This Halloween you can’t miss the chance to set aside the daily clown costume you call “my job’s uniform”, and replace it with this masterly girl-magnet-different-kind-of-clown costume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Real-Life Joker Costume comes equipt with everything you need to be in Joker’s skin for a night. This kit includes the whole Joker’s original outfit, a full set of professional makeup with a green-haired wig, and an ensemble of different authentic guns and knives to get the full experience. It also has a CD with a hardcore rock music playlist to listen to while you apply the makeup on your face. Because we know that protecting your masculinity is vital to you. And you can hide the weapons throughout different spots distributed all over the suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This costume is ideal for all those who want to express how hilarious, yet mysterious they really are. Also, giving you the chance to surprise everyone at the party with some unexpected dance moves, your quirky abrupt and contagious laughter, or killing everyone there when the alcohol runs out. If you’re really a Joker fan, we know you’ll manage to do all three at once! The additional ammo and the character’s charisma sold separately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is that time of the year to be enjoyed as you please. Kids run and hide all around the neighborhood doing tricks and mischiefs, teenagers have lovely parties where everyone has the same costumes, and everyone gets expired candy. Thanks to the Real Life Joker Costume Kit, the lonely straight men will have the opportunity to drain all of their insecurities and frustrations by committing crimes disguised as the Joker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The positive reception has been so overwhelming that Costumes &amp;amp; Customs is now selling an extra DVD that teaches you to be as real as the costume itself! It has dance lessons with the latest cool moves, a video guide on how to properly use your weapons with torture techniques, and a two hour documentary with descriptions of different traumas and illnesses you can choose from in case you have none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The demand for this hyper-realistic costume has been staggering. In some cities, there have reported incidents where large groups of men dressed as the Joker start to shoot and stab people in different locations such as movie theaters, shopping malls, and good stand-up comedy shows. Unfortunately, there is no record of people dressed as Batman saving anyone’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The increasing crime wave that followed the release of this product is an excellent reflection of the brilliant accuracy of this costume. These Jokers can run freely, having fun, causing mass homicides. Those who bought their outfits from other companies have to conform with the dull Superman attire that can’t even make them fly. Or their Lego character costumes that still won’t make them fit in anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allowing people to become their favorite character instead of just dressing up like them is what makes the work of Costumes &amp;amp; Customs so unique. But this is not the first time the company produced a costume that has turned out so realistic. For example, in the Costumes &amp;amp; Customs catalog, there are other hyperreal disguises. Like a Kylie Jenner costume containing expensive women clothes, an iPod full of “Rise and Shine” remixes with Travis Scott’s entire discography, and a baby girl dol. The costume kit doesn’t come with a father doll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sales of the Real Life Joker Costume are growing with every second. People are starting to get used to the appearances of people dressing up as the Joker, which are not always dangerous but sometimes are somewhat awkward. We asked Randall McCarthy, one of the latest buyers, why he likes this costume so much: “Are you nuts? This costume has given me all I’ve ever needed. If I wear my Joker clothes, people start to notice me. Girls are now laughing at my jokes! And if they don’t, I kill them. Having this disguise compensates having grown without parents, attention, or affection!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict: The Real-Life Joker Costume is out in your favorite stores now! Don’t give up the chance to show people that ignoring you in high school can have serious consequences. Or use it to go to a party. You don’t have to think about it twice, order yours now and finally get a reason to get out of your mother’s basement this Halloween!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>9</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">We live in a society that loves Halloween. We all could agree that Halloween is easily one of the coolest parts of the year. You are getting free candy from your neighbors for no reason at all, freaking out because you don’t find the perfect idea for your costume this year, parents letting their children play with their friends, at night, with lots of disguised people all around. Michael Jackson’s private heaven. But this year, you don’t have to worry about which one could be the ideal costume for you. Costume &amp;amp; Customs is ready to help you be the laugh of your office’s Halloween Party this October.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baby Taser Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/baby-taser-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baby Taser Review" /><published>2019-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/baby-taser-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/baby-taser-review/">&lt;p&gt;Are you tired of waking up at 3 AM because of the frantic cries of your lovely newborn? Exhausted by pretending that you don’t mind the constant weeping of your beautiful baby twins on that long road trip from Houston to Albuquerque? Fed up with the tough search for a miraculous answer to pacify the unbearable wailing of your angelical children? You don’t have to hide alone in your car to cry because of your miserable existence anymore! The brand-new Baby-Taser has arrived to help parents in need. Fixing your sleep schedule, and possibly save your marriage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baby Taser doesn’t work as a weapon, but as a tool that assists parents in soothing their children when they unexpectedly start bawling in the most inopportune situations; such as during a long flight, in the middle of your favorite movie, or when your spouse finally wants to get laid. This marvelous product is specifically designed to disrupt the incipient muscle functions of your children in different levels adapted to an infant’s body, meaning it could just calm them down for a while or immediately get them into a gentle sleep. Both using a moderate amount of electric shocks with the same care as a light slap in the face, and without causing any significant physical harm to your baby. Ironically, some inquisitive parents have also discovered that the Baby-Taser can also be set up to quickly wake your toddlers up if you want to spend some quality time with them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This product has been designed, developed, and distributed by SoftWeaponry TM. Todd N. Truman, the CEO of the company and the genius behind the Baby Taser, took a little time away from his multiple demonstrations and congratulation ceremonies to tell us a little bit about what inspired him to develop this life-changing product: “Well, we were actually working on a special electroshock weapon for aggressive dogs, you know. Back in those days, I used to sleep at my office because my newborn twins used to wake me and my wife up constantly in the middle of the night. One day, after a long meeting we all agreed it would’ve been really cruel to do such a thing to a poor dog, even if it’s out of control. I didn’t know what to do, and at that point, we already spent a lot of money and resources on the product. But that same day, my wife called me while I was clearing my desk for a nap to tell me she was pregnant again. I took one of our prototypes, aimed it to my head and tried to kill myself. Instead of ending my agony, it got me shocked into the sweetest of dreams until my secretary woke me up the next morning, I already had the concept in my head: A Taser for my bab… for babies, in general!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The attractiveness of the Baby Taser goes beyond its simplicity and its effectiveness: It has many pleasing features. The Baby Taser comes in many different presentations such as the classic stun gun and the simple and elegant baton with cartoon prints. There are some more friendly designs with the shape of your children’s favorite characters like Spongebob, Mickey Mouse or Bob Dylan.  If it wasn’t enough, the SoftWeaponry team recently launched a new Elmo-shaped Baby Taser that can be left in your child’s cradle to accompany your baby, sing some lullabies overnight and if your child wakes up for any reason, this sophisticated Baby-Taser will carefully shock them back to sleep while it plays Rock-a-bye Baby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acceptance rate of the Baby Taser has been impressively high since its first batch launch. William Silverstone, a single father whose wife passed away one year ago, gave us some feedback about it: “It’s awesome. I mean, I can’t talk for my baby girl but, you know. They fall asleep, how bad can it be? I don’t have to pay for a daycare anymore, I wake up, have my coffee, Baby-Tase my little girl, put her in my suitcase and go to work!”. The numbers are crazy! Stores are selling out of their stock within 72 hours of receiving a shipment. Babysitters are so pleased with this invention that some of them are not charging for their services anymore. They’re are doing it for fun. Studies show that the principal buyers of the Baby Taser are daycare centers, nanny agencies, and single mothers. Many who have also requested SoftWeaponry for products with a longer range and more cadence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite its many advantages and how much it has improved the lives of many, the Baby Taser has naturally received some criticism. When they heard about it, the UN began a study of the product which resulted in a harsh denouncement of the manufacturers for the inhuman, cruel and excessive use of plastic in the fabrication of the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baby Taser development team is currently working to deliver a new environmental-friendly line. Also, the PR department of SoftWeaponry has stated that they are constantly receiving letters with complaints asking why they took so long to invent the Baby Taser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict: Don’t judge the brand-new Baby Taser before trying it. This product is so durable that you can use it for years even into your child’s teens, and even electroshock your unemployed 27-year-old baby from the house once you get tired of them. Don’t miss this chance to be part of a better parenting experience!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>9</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">Are you tired of waking up at 3 AM because of the frantic cries of your lovely newborn? Exhausted by pretending that you don’t mind the constant weeping of your beautiful baby twins on that long road trip from Houston to Albuquerque? Fed up with the tough search for a miraculous answer to pacify the unbearable wailing of your angelical children? You don’t have to hide alone in your car to cry because of your miserable existence anymore! The brand-new Baby-Taser has arrived to help parents in need. Fixing your sleep schedule, and possibly save your marriage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Garmin Forerunner Gps Running Watch Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Garmin-Forerunner-GPS-Running-Watch-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Garmin Forerunner Gps Running Watch Review" /><published>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Garmin-Forerunner-GPS-Running-Watch-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Garmin-Forerunner-GPS-Running-Watch-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone knows that exercising is excellent for you. The common refrain, “Use it or lose it,” certainly applies to the human form. We live in a sedentary lifestyle inducing world. From our offices where we sit in a chair and work, to our homes where we sit on our couches and play video games or browse through Netflix shows, we usually sit still. This life leads to an increase in health issues and cascades into overall lower quality of life. No one wants that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, most people can do simple exercises like walking or running, which can massively increase their quality of life. Running helps to tone the body and refine the mind. It is something that can minimize daily stress, help with cardiovascular health, and relieve depression. A few experts in the matter even think that running is something that propels humans forward because of its role in our evolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running was not in fashion for a while, but it has come back. This is evidenced by the success of the Shoe Dog, people like Phil Knight and his company, Nike. Runners now have a large community, more tools, and an increasing number of tracks to do what they love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are planning on joining the running population, a &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; watch might be right for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s find out what this provides to its wearer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can easily hold up to 500 songs. That’s something that many runners would want to have and can appreciate as they go for their run. Individuals can add a pair of Bluetooth headphones to their purchases to minimize the need for their mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One fantastic feature might be the fact that you don’t have to be online to listen to music. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; syncs your favorite songs from different streaming providers to allow you to listen offline. Users should note that this might require another premium purchase from the third party music streaming company. Yes, you can connect it to Spotify and download the Spotify app without the need for a smartphone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next feature is for those who like to keep it simple and modern while they shop. The Garmin Pay contactless payment feature lets users pay easily with the Garmin watch. The contactless pay feature works with select companies allowing runners to travel light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another compelling component of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is the set of running features it provides to its user base. The watch is known for its “advanced running dynamics” that encompasses information such as stride length, and additional information. Through these features, you could get more information on your heart rate and use that to up your running and training game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner 645 Music and GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; watch lasts for quite a while and can work for up to 7 days when using smartwatch mode, and at least 5 hours with GPS mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else can you expect from the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; while you start or continue your quest to build strength, and add psychological value to your life? A sleek design. Users find that the watch can even be passed off as a dressy and more formal watch because of its metal accents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner 645 Music and GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is simple, durable, and made for runners. The watch comes with a simple five-button touch interface that helps you record and keep track of your running workout, and can meet your running needs. Seeing that the watch has a water rating of 5 ATM, runners can also move around in rainy weather so they can always be on the go and take efforts to stay fit and healthy whenever the sky turns the precipitation route&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The watch is optimized for viewing in any type of weather and time of day. If you like to switch things up, replacing bands is simple and time-effective. The company promises that this is one item that doesn’t disappoint in design or durability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with GPS/GLONASS, Wi-Fi connectivity, smart notifications, training load, wrist heart rate, Garmin Pay, and music storage. In other words, it has everything you might need while you try to stay active. It weighs only 1.4 ounces and is a delight to wear according to users. It comes with preloaded activities including but not limited to running, treadmill running, biking indoors, and cardio. You will need to keep in mind that 1 CR2 battery is needed with this watch for it to perform its functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than 55% of users agree that it is a value buy and that it is well worth the purchase. The people who use this watch range from the tenured runner who follows their set trail every day, to the amateur who just started their running and cardiovascular journey. Those that run for 20-25 miles per week find that the watch proves to meet their stringent needs. Since they don’t want to have to run around with their phones, they would rather have a light device and let it help them in their run - the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a perfect fit for those needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users find that setup is easy and they can quickly input music before heading outdoors. But it might not be as easy for all users if they have never conducted the process of opening up a Garmin account, have not used Garmin Connect, or other components of Garmin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has only been tested with a few types of earphones. As such, make sure to look at complimentary headphones (like the Trekz Titanium) to this Garmin watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Runners find that the watch is a perfect size and that it comes with a fantastic overall design. Nifty features like the vibration alarm do users a great deal of good and help them to wake up on time for their work or running activities. From GPS to running activity, and from display to functionalities like activity tracking, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has helped many users on their running journeys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been minimal complaints with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It has served many different types of runners who most overwhelmingly support and find significant value in the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing the positive reviews that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has garnered from users, it might prove to be a good fit for you if you identify as a fitness enthusiast and run on an almost daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Garmin Forerunner" /><category term="Watch" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tufts And Needle Queen Mattress Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Tufts-and-Needle-Queen-Mattress-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tufts And Needle Queen Mattress Review" /><published>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Tufts-and-Needle-Queen-Mattress-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Tufts-and-Needle-Queen-Mattress-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is something that you need more of (besides money) and can’t really seem to get enough of each day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s proper rest and sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, sleep is useful in more ways than one and adds significant value to many people’s lives. But the unfortunate reality is that many are quite likely sleep-deprived. Mr T would quite likely pity the increasing number of sleepless people within the world today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sleep allows the mind to rest and relax for the next full day ahead. When one neglects sleep, they prevent their brain from working as efficiently as possible. Because a lot truly happens during times of rest. Even if we don’t know all about the inner workings of our brain, it’s still working for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know that while you sleep, your brain conducts processes that help you store, retain, and utilize the information that can be used in your next full working day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One can argue that sleep doesn’t only add value to the individual; it adds value to a collective society. When everyone rests well, they can make better decisions that will bring about more progress. Sleep is essential in an increasingly complex world where a good night’s sleep can help enhance problem-solving capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feeling like you’re not creative and as elated as you once were?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good night’s rest on a &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might be in the cards for you. Coming home to hit your comfy mattress might be just what you need. By simply resting well, you might find that you can get out of that slump and overall fatigue that’s been accumulating over time, and say hello to a more active and refreshed state of mind with a smile on your face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not limited to mental rejuvenation either. Proper sleep on a &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might even help you reduce your physical health problems that range from diabetes to blood pressure, and muscular issues to heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at how the widely popular &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; helps people sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with adaptive foam. This adaptive foam is said to be important because it emphasizes comfort. The firm incorporates T&amp;amp;N adaptive foam to give users a more flexible yet supportive experience. This provides individuals with the ability to get the rest they need regardless of how they move around in their sleep. Tuft and Needle foam also provides for simple and easy shipping as it is contained in a regular shipping unit and sent to your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brand boasts of its superior quality by stepping up its game in terms of materials. They optimize for a fresh and comfortable sleep with the aforementioned T&amp;amp;N Adaptive foam. It’s the T&amp;amp;N Adaptive foam that provides you and your partner a relaxed state of sleep in a convenient manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mattress is made up of 2 layers of “a high-density high-quality polyurethane foam” that is checked and certified by a third party known in the bedding industry as CertiPUR-US. As such, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can state that they don’t have adverse chemicals or other factors that might be harmful to individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users will be happy to note that the mattress was created by scientists with a passion for enhanced sleep. As such, the bed is adaptive and pressure-relieving — further, it’s soft, comfortable, cool, and durable. The brand also pays close attention to the alignment of the spine and neck. The addition of the cooling gel and graphite provides for a better sleeping experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are worried about taking on more risk with their purchase, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; state that they will provide a full refund, in addition to a 100 Night Sleep Trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provide a 10-year limited warranty on this product, allowing for full peace of mind on your part. The company also mentions that users should be aware of one important note, which is that the mattress will take at least 72 hours to progress into its full adaptive form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; fits all frames ranging from box springs, slatted frames, and adjustable frames. What’s most compelling for users is the fact that they don’t have to take on any risk, they simply order the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, test it out and return it within 100 days if they don’t like it. They can even order through an authorized reseller like Amazon for simplicity, security, logistics, and free shipping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many users note that this bed will hold up for people who are over the average weight. People who are 6” 4 and weigh 280 pounds have reported that they slept amazingly well with this mattress. More than 70% of customers love this product and rate it very highly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A critical component in the bedding industry is customer service, and the customers of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are very happy with the company’s customer service operations. Users note that the customer service listens to their problems and provides them with the help they need. One customer felt that there was more need for firmness and suffered from hip pain. After speaking with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; customer service team, the customer got a free topper that solved the problem. They didn’t have to wait for a response and were able to resolve their problem promptly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; users note that the bed is comfortable to set up, where one can simply cut the plastic, unroll and let the mattress breathe. They note that factory smell is minimum and isn’t a problem. The localized motion is what many like about the mattress. They don’t have to worry about disturbing their partner or vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, customers feel that they get great value for their money and are overwhelmingly happy with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The company minimizes risk with their trial and provides excellent customer service to resolve problems as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in the market for a new mattress, you might want to give one a try.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Tufts and Needle" /><category term="Mattress" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Zivix Jamstik Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Zivix-Jamstik-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Zivix Jamstik Review" /><published>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Zivix-Jamstik-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Zivix-Jamstik-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who enjoy music want to experience it in all its glory. Whether they are listening to their favorite artists through headphones, blasting their favorite tunes on speakers, or jamming their hearts out with friends or family, these different aspects let them get the most out of their music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While listening to music is quite common and a very affordable hobby, it gets difficult to hold jamming sessions if you don’t have the right equipment with you. But seeing that guitars are expensive and not accessible to everyone, those who want to indulge into jamming often have to leave that plan behind due to lack of resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a portable, electric guitar, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; claims to make jamming more accessible and playing a guitar more affordable. Sporting a sleek design, the instrument connects to your smartphone, tablet or computer through Bluetooth 4.0. From there, it is all a matter of pairing it up with any compatible MIDI app, and you can emulate the experience of playing a real guitar in the comfort of your home. All of this comes at a very affordable price, which promises to provide great value for money while also paying attention to the quality of music you are about to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; boasts of real strings and frets that provide the feeling of playing a real guitar. With a Smart Fretboard, it also promises to provide the user with instant feedback to enhance their playing experience. It comes with multiple modes that make playing the guitar more fun for users, whether they are going solo on a practice session or jamming it out with a friend or family member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is MIDI compatible, which makes it easier to create and mix music with tunes that are produced directly from the guitar device. For those who have not played a guitar before, the device also comes complete with tutorials and games to add to their learning experience. The magnetic pickup technology in the device picks up even the lightest touch and effectively promises to emulate an experience that is as close to playing a real guitar as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The device is available in two packages, with the Black package only having the guitar in it. Whereas, at a slightly higher price, the Case Bundle has a handy travel case or gig bag that lets users carry their guitar around while keeping it safe from dust and grime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of carrying the guitar around, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises to be travel-friendly. Weighing only 1.9lbs with dimensions of 16.5 x 3.5 x 2.5 inches, the device puts portability front and center. But that doesn’t mean that it compromises on design or style by any means. The guitar boasts of a sleek design that is comprised of clean lines, a black frame and silver strings. At the same time, multiple buttons on the side provide additional control to the user. At first look, it is instantly reminiscent of a modernized version of a traditional electric guitar, which is exactly the look that it is going for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes actually to use the guitar, users have found it to be delivering on its promises for the most part. It has been noted that the guitar’s overall functions work as advertised, with its fretboard and strings being quite helpful in composing new tunes while also playing old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is fairly easy to use, with the connectivity and setting adjustments being an improvement on its predecessor, the original &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. With that, the device also comes with the ability to add multiple &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to a single device, which paves the way for true to life jamming sessions with friends or family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the native app for &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also fairly simple and has an intuitive design, which makes it easy to make adjustments to the device’s sound delivery and play quality. This is especially praised by users who have not used a device like the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; before, or who have simply never had a chance to test the real-world functionality of an actual guitar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acoustics delivered by &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also earn high praise from those who have used the device. This is possible due to the true to life sound quality that is emulated through the carefully developed strings, fret, and form-factor. Overall, users believe that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is exactly the jamming device they needed to belt out jamming sessions with their loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the native app for &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also fairly simple and has an intuitive design, which makes it easy to make adjustments to the device’s sound delivery and play quality. Available for iOS and Android, the app and its functionality is especially praised by users who have not used a device like the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; before, or who have simply never had a chance to test the real-world functionality of an actual guitar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But seeing that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is specifically built for beginners, this complaint could be brushed aside quite easily. That is why other users have noted that the device fits their needs seamlessly and provides an experience that they had been looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a great piece of technology that makes the task of learning to play guitar or simply jamming with likeminded people a more joyful process. If you are someone who is on the learning curve for guitar playing or enjoy busting out the tunes occasionally, then you might find the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to be a great purchase.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Zivix Jamstik+" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Alienware-M15-Gaming-Laptop-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Alienware-M15-Gaming-Laptop-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Alienware-M15-Gaming-Laptop-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the gamer circles, Dell’s &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a brand name well known for big and chunkier gaming systems, something that most people weren’t a fan of. But with the all-new &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, it’s quite evident to see Alienware tried to offer a portable gaming laptop on par with rival systems like Razer Blade 15 and MSI GS65 Stealth Thin. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is 18mm thick/0.7inch, making it their most slimmest gaming laptop to date. It’s no secret that the competition has a better hold over the market when it comes to powerful and portable game systems, but with the entry of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the market, you might find it on par with the current standing competitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we touch on the specs a little, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a heavy Intel Core i7 processor, Nvidia Max-Q GPU, and Windows 10 Pro operating system. If you prefer more GPU power, just plug in Alienware’s custom amplifier and a desktop graphics card. Weighing at 4.8 pounds, or 2.16kg, this gaming laptop is the most lightweight Alienware equipment ever, surpassing its predecessor. However, it is not the most lightweight in the overall gaming laptops category. The lid of the laptop is made from anodized aluminium, with the trademark backlit LED alien head logo in the middle. The top lid has a smooth downward slope and plastic vents adorn the back, as well as the bottom. The display boasts a 15.6-inch size with reports of the LED displaying high-quality colors and visuals. Alienware display has always been touted as one of the most vibrant experiences you can get, and the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; gives you a 150% reproduction of sRGB color gamut, which is on par with the Stealth Thin. The ports include 3 USB 3.0 connections, a gigabit Ethernet port, HDMI, mini display port, and a USB-C with Thunderbolt 3. All this with the addition of a Graphics Amplifier port, offering PCIe x16 bandwidth for external Graphics dock if gamers decide to go that path. The Alienware Graphics Amplifier (AGA) port is described to be a proprietary connection for Alienware’s proprietary eGPU system (meaning you can’t use it with non-Alienware computers). Standard SKUs come equipped with Killer 1550 with integrated Bluetooth 5, with advantages of having Killer Control Center software and customizable network prioritization features in the Alien Command Center program. Gamers that have used this laptop have reviewed that they have been able to adjust some things, like the keyboard backlit color, but not all settings. Overall, you get a much smaller profile with lesser weight, a new keyboard, and a full internal revamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enough about the specs, you came here for the reviews. People described it as “surprisingly light despite a burly-looking machine”. It was reported to have no flexing in the base and being solidly put-together. The lid and hinges were said to have no wiggles, creaks or flops and held reasonably stiff. Apart from gaming, buyers said it to be a good choice for other intensive tasks like photo/video editing. The screen has been touted as one of the best features of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, being anti-glare with a matte finish, which doesn’t require one to turn on the brightness level to the highest setting. With buyers who used it for lighter work like browsing the web or lightweight work, the battery lasts 4 hours on average, unplugged, screen set at minimum brightness. Some gamers appreciated the dual-channel RAM for a performance boost. Regarding keyboard, key travel was said to be decent, and size sufficient enough for most. Backlighting was touted to be great, with six RGB zones. However, most people found the keyboard’s rubber finishing to be off-putting due to being a “fingerprint magnet”, albeit easy to clean with a soft cloth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, some downgrades had to be made in order to present the masses with a bite-sized hardware version. There is no SD card reader present, which was absent in the larger models as well. The battery is on the smaller side, which means performance suffers about 30% when unplugged. Regarding weight, the m15 still lags with regards to competition. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has reports of utilizing a “connected” standby feature, which enables it to still receive updates. This also uses more battery life (approximately 1% per hour) and has been reported to waking up when it’s not supposed to, like when it’s in a backpack. To bypass this, gamers go for the hibernate setting instead. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has issues with heating, where the i7-8750H has a max temp of 100 degrees, the performance pushes it too close to that temperature for some people’s comfort. As a laptop too, well, put in your lap, it is not a good option because the air intake vents are present on the bottom. One person shared that the top area of their keyboard reached 130 degrees F, as measured by their infrared thermometer, and an internal temperature around 200F. Most users had to raise their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; about an inch off the surface to achieve good airflow. This seems to be a recurring issue in ultrabook-sized laptops, where there is not enough space for adequate airflow. That’s not too surprising, given that downscaling is a hard line to walk, where you lose some to win some.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To summarize, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MP4LK82?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Alienware M15 Thin and Light 15 Gaming Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is well built with a competitive price point, although it can still vastly improve some flaws that come with downscaling. As long as Alienware continues to improve and build upon performance as well as aesthetics, they’re likely to be a sure-fire win amongst the gaming category sometime soon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Alienware" /><category term="Laptop" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bose Soundtouch 30 Wireless Speakers Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-SoundTouch-30-Wireless-Speakers-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bose Soundtouch 30 Wireless Speakers Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-SoundTouch-30-Wireless-Speakers-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-SoundTouch-30-Wireless-Speakers-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is that most of us can’t get enough of listening to our favorite music. Whether you are working in your private office or lounging in your living room, sounds can elevate the experience. If you enjoy music, then you might always need your favorite tunes for motivation, relaxation, or to enhance your overall ambiance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While expensive headphones promise the delivery of high-quality audio, they can only go so far in terms of relaxation and flexibility. That is where wireless speakers come in and provide a level of comfort and ease that remains unmatched by other devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Wireless Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises the same flexibility while also letting users enjoy high-quality audio. Sporting Bose’s waveguide technology with premium drivers, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; claims to spread rich sound in even the largest rooms by connecting to devices such as Amazon Echo, or just about any smartphone for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To deliver high-quality sound with clarity and depth, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports all popular audio formats, including AAC, Apple Lossless, MP3, and WMA. At the same time, it also comes with dependable wireless connectivity in terms of Wi-Fi and Bluetooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Wireless Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; connects with any Amazon Echo device, it offers full support for Amazon Alexa. All that users have to do to listen to their music is ask Alexa to play it for them. But those who don’t have an Amazon Echo device can still depend on the speaker’s Bluetooth and Wi-Fi connectivity.  The connectivity allows them to play their music manually through compatible devices. With it, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a built-in OLED display, and a separate remote with six presets, which makes it easier to manage playlists and skip through stations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such,  one can see that regardless of Amazon Echo availability, the Bose SoundTouch 30 could easily play music from different platforms. Through wireless connectivity and its intuitive remote, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could play tunes from popular streaming services including but not limited to Spotify, SiriusXM, iTunes, and Pandora.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is extremely easy to set up. It is so simple and to the point where it only takes a couple of minutes to connect it to a new device. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is built to work with other Bose SoundTouch family of speakers, it also connects with additional speakers seamlessly. This is possible due to its wireless network functionality, which connects to such devices through 802.11 b/g/n. Users note that this quality to grow the speaker collection as users see fit adds a ton of flexibility to the speaker’s utilization, while also delivering complete surround sound at the users’ terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speaker’s sound quality gets praised by those who look for deep, rich, yet clear audio. It has been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can deliver high volume sounds while still being able to retain the audio quality and clarity. This makes it a highly sought after device for audiophiles looking to fill their home or office with their favorite music. Some have gone as far as to term it as the best speaker that they have ever used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also note that it is quite easy to adjust audio levels in the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Those who like a certain amount of bass in their audio could quickly get it by tweaking a few settings. Those who want more clarity could also make their required changes rapidly. Users note that overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; delivers the desired quality of audio for any music enthusiast with just a few tweaks and changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While being used through Bluetooth devices, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports a 30 feet range when connected. Users have noted that this provides the listener with quite some flexibility. It has also been noted that this makes the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a great addition for larger rooms, where the devices being connected are far apart. The remote control only adds to this flexibility and allows users to enjoy changing their music even when they are at a certain distance from the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Measured at the dimensions of 7.1 x 17.1 x 9.7 inches, users praise the overall size of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Weighing 18.5lbs, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a bit heavy to carry around. But given that it is powered through an electric cord and is meant to be used as a stationary speaker anyway, the weight does not diminish its value proposition for its users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also praise the overall look of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Made with high-quality materials and sporting a modern design, the device projects a sleek style. One that is appreciated by those who are fans of this aesthetic. The OLED only enhances the speaker’s look, and the design itself lets the audio shine through whenever music goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bose claims that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is extremely easy to connect with other devices. But some users take issue with that promise. According to them, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is not very user-friendly when it comes to connecting with other Bose SoundTouch devices, and provides a delay in the audio. With that being said, they still agree that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; works great as a standalone device. At the same time, other users state no such issues and seem to have no problems connecting their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with other Bose speakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B011IKGT46?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose SoundTouch 30 Wireless Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides its users with a rich and vibrant sound quality that is desired by every audiophile. With high-quality materials, multiple connectivity options, and support for Amazon Alexa, it could be a great addition to any enthusiast’s collection. Use it as a standalone speaker or as part of a surround sound system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Bose SoundTouch" /><category term="Wireless Speakers" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hp Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-590-Desktop-Computer-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hp Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-590-Desktop-Computer-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/HP-Pavilion-590-Desktop-Computer-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to buying an affordable new computer for your home or business, having a limited budget gets you limited advancements in technology. If you want an advanced machine, then your budget has to be over a certain threshold. Otherwise, you have to compromise on the machine’s performance in exchange for affordability. But it doesn’t have to be that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With renewed or refurbished computers, you can enjoy faster performance and the latest technology without having to spend a fortune. This way, you can save money, but without having to choose the compromise route. These computers are good as new and often come with the seller’s guarantee, which gives you a safety net and plenty of time to test the machine before you decide to keep it for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The renewed &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises to fit those needs perfectly. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a 2.8 GHz Intel Core i5-8400 processor, 8 GB of RAM, and 16 GB of Intel Optane memory. It also has a 1 TB hard disk drive (HDD), which also comes with a 12-month offer of free 25 GB Dropbox cloud storage. To top it all off, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with Windows 10 as its operating system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To fit users’ multimedia needs, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; sports built-in Intel UHD Graphics 630. With it, it also comes with a DVD-writer. Connectivity is offered through Wi-Fi 802.11ac, Bluetooth 4.2, as well as multiple USB ports. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with a headphone and microphone combo port, 5.1 surround sound output, and 1 HDMI plugin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elaborating on the connectivity ports, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has 3 USB 3.1 ports, with one of them being a USB Type-C port. But the connectivity options don’t end there since it also has 4 USB 2.0 ports. All of this is encased in a silver rig casing that has a modern, geometric patterned design with a brushed texture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to practical usage, these features translate into a potent machine at an affordable price point. Since the model is renewed, it comes with a massive price reduction for a product that is good as new and comes with Amazon’s 90-day Renewed Guarantee. Users have noted that while they had been worried about buying a refurbished computer, it turned out to be the right choice and provided excellent value for money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The refurbished status of this &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; had kept some users suspect about their purchase since the time of placing their order. But after receiving the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, they seem to have left their worries behind. Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; they received is indeed good as new and works like it is supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have also noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to its claims and provides the speed that it promises. It has been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; boots up fast and operates smoothly as well, which takes away the possibility of any lagging issues in operating applications. This is possible due to the 8th generation, 2.8 GHz Intel Core i5 processor, 8GB DDR4 RAM, and 16 GB Intel Optane Memory, which turns the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; into a powerhouse of a performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also makes for a good upgrade for those users who have been using older machines for a while. With the latest processor, increased memory, wireless connectivity options, and stellar graphics, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; fulfills the users’ work, study or entertainment needs quite well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also seem to be satisfied with the multimedia performance of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; offers multiple connectivity options with a DVD-writer and a 7200RPM SATA HDD, it allows users to enjoy their entertainment options through various mediums. The built-in Intel UHD Graphics 630 allows for smooth multimedia streaming and gaming, which serves the needs of those users who buy the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with entertainment in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with its built-in graphics, users have noted that those who want hardcore gaming could actually install another graphics card. To do so, they just need to change the power supply to allow for the addition of a more powerful graphics card that is specifically built for gaming. According to the users who have already done this, the action has upgraded their machine significantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have also praised how the machine looks in its dimensions of 10.9 x 6.69 x 13.3 inches. Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in a shortened tower or rig shape, it projects a modern outlook to everyone. It’s silver-colored exterior, and just 16.2lbs of weight also add to its overall looks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to points that have created issues for users, it has been noted that the vertical built of the DVD-writer has caused some problems for users who wanted more comfort with a horizontally fit DVD-writer. Another issue that a couple of users have noted is how their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was dead on arrival. They returned the machine promptly, but it is still something that needs to be kept in mind for those who might face such issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; makes for a powerful machine that fits the need of the everyday user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one issue with renewed or refurbished machines is that they could be dead on arrival. But as users have noted, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could be returned promptly. In such cases, you should just know how to reach out to Amazon customer service, and they would be able to help you return the machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP Pavilion 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains a great choice for those who are looking for value for money. Those who want more performance out of their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07MDYZW37?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HP 590 Desktop Computer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could smoothly go the route of upgrading the RAM or the graphics card and use the machine according to their needs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="HP Pavilion" /><category term="Desktop Computer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lenovo Flex 14 2 In 1 Convertible Laptop Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Lenovo-Flex-14-2-in-1-Convertible-Laptop-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lenovo Flex 14 2 In 1 Convertible Laptop Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Lenovo-Flex-14-2-in-1-Convertible-Laptop-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Lenovo-Flex-14-2-in-1-Convertible-Laptop-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; companies power and versatility in a sleek laptop body. This robust laptop can handle anything from content creation to gaming. In this review, I’ll show you why this laptop has an impressive 4.1 stars on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; boasts a powerful Ryzen 5 3500U with the most advanced APU graphics available on the market. Inside the Ryzen 5 3500U processor, it has 4 powerful cores aided by 8 threads. A powerful base clock of 2.1GHz allows this computer to handle almost anything on the market, but its boost clock is where the laptop shines. 3.7GHz is an impressive clock amongst desktop-grade processors, but it is mind-boggling when you pack it onto the super sleek &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The processor has 8 dedicated graphics cores, allowing your &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to handle gaming and content creation. The Radeon Vega 8 in this laptop is clocked at an impressive 1200Mhz. All in all, the sheer power of this laptop is unquestioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blazing fast CPU isn’t all you need for a speedy laptop, other parts play a critical role in it. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes packed with a 256GB NVMe SSD, transforming your laptop into a blazing fast machine. SSD’s are much faster than traditional hard drives and can reduce boot up times drastically. 256GB is more than enough for normal use, allowing you to store games, and word documents. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes packed with 8GB of DDR4 memory, allowing you to create content and even game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general, the performance of this laptop is revered amongst users. It’s super-fast and can handle many of the things you would often need a desktop for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; sports the most recent version of Windows, Windows 10. This version of Windows comes with many useful features, including an easy to use start menu, and the virtual assistant Cortana. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; allows you to use an exclusive feature called “Tablet Mode”. This mode of Windows 10 allows you to interact with the laptop without needing a mouse or keyboard. This is achieved by virtually transforming the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; from a standard PC to a touchscreen device. So instead of needing to use these two standard peripherals, you just need your two hands. This “mode” allows you to conserve space, whilst maintaining versatility. This configuration of Windows works hand in hand with the pen which is included with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. This pen is useful for taking notes with style, or doodling on the screen whenever you feel the need to release your surges of creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; retains its advantage over its competitors in the realm of portability. The sleek design allows for easy transportation, with its weight of 3.5 LBS, and its small form factor, it can fit into any travel bag with ease. This minimalist design is visually appealing and meshes perfectly with the beautiful backlit keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; possess a new and improved iteration of their renowned, “Flex” display. The flex display allows the user to flip and turn the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 1920x1080 Full High Definition display up to almost 360°. The flex display is really useful for achieving maximum productivity while using “Tablet Mode”, which is an augmented version of Windows 10 designed to increase productivity in hand-related and touch-based tasks. Tablet Mode works hand in hand with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Flex display to increase the user’s productivity with the increase of workflow output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; precision touchpad isn’t something we should look past as it is a crucial part of use in travel, a category in which this &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is designed to excel in. The precision touchpad is designed to work with gestures, which allows you to perform simple tasks easily and elegantly. The security offered through Windows 10 topped off with the&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; built-in touchpad offers the comforting guarantee of security on your laptop. The convenience of using a fingerprint sensor over a traditional password is quick, easy and efficient. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; offers a whopping 8 hours of battery life usage which is perfect for travel. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports quick charge technology which will power your laptop up to 80%. This is perfect for usage on short and even long commutes, creating a virtually perfect work experience while in commute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;is extremely powerful, capable of handling anything you throw at it. It has a crisp 1920x1080 Full High Definition display, with enough battery power to power through a day. The unique flex ability allows for increased versatility and uses cases. In general, this is a superb laptop for students and travellers alike. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07PB5M8DS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenovo Flex 14 2-in-1 Convertible Laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is deserving of its 4.1-star rating on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Lenovo" /><category term="Convertible Laptop" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">P.mai Premium Leather Laptop Backpack With Wristlet Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/P.MAI-Premium-Leather-Laptop-Backpack-with-Wristlet-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="P.mai Premium Leather Laptop Backpack With Wristlet Review" /><published>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/P.MAI-Premium-Leather-Laptop-Backpack-with-Wristlet-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/P.MAI-Premium-Leather-Laptop-Backpack-with-Wristlet-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the professional world, women executives must work quite hard on a regular basis. Whether they are fighting this battle from their desk or in the field, in the boardroom or over a videocon, they mostly need to work rigorously to present themselves as a confident, assertive and knowledgeable personality. If you are a woman in any sector of business, you might have already gone through the same experience, or at least witnessed it with some of your coworkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides sporting business acumen, women also need to make sure that they are dressed in a way that doesn’t let someone undermine their hard-earned value due to the way they look. That is why power suits, sharp shoes, and a no-nonsense expression is always attributed to a necessary team player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But seeing that pulling off such a look is not easy, there’s a lot of work put in by various designers and stylists to ensure that women look their most confident while navigating their way through various sectors of business. One such design house is P.MAI, which specializes in making fashion accessories for women execs. While the label has many offerings, its &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; stands out due to many reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; doesn’t look like your typical messenger bag. Instead, it is designed as a sleek backpack that has space for a 15-inch laptop, four insert pockets, a water bottle holder, and a zipper pocket at the front. These features ensure that the laptop bag projects a powerful yet non-jarring look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is made from premium Nappa leather as well as high quality 2520D nylon. Due to the usage of these materials, it boasts of being both luxurious and durable. In addition to aesthetics and strength, the bag also claims to be comfortable for its users. With padded backstraps, a luggage strap, and adjustable webbing, the bag is built to be worn or carried easily without taking its toll on its owner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sporting three different color options with two-tone colors and golden zippers, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; looks sleek and stylish to project a look of finesse with its dimensions of 12.5 x 6 x 15.5 inches. Made specifically for women, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has the aesthetic to match high fashion in many aspects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add to its value, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a separate dust bag as well as a wristlet. While the dust bag is to be used whenever someone is storing their bag away for the night, the matching wristlet provides more convenience in handling any cards or equipment they need on hand while carrying the bag around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to practical usage, the first thing that users note about the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is its stylish design. Users have mentioned that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; looks quite impressive in the way that it has been crafted, and the premium materials used in it bring out the most appealing elements in its design. Since the bag uses a mix of Nappa calf leather and premium quality 2520D nylon, the contrast of material and the chosen colors for each element give the bag a multi-dimensional look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, users have also noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides them with a roomy yet organized space inside the bag, which could fit a variety of their needs besides carrying a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that they have been able to carry legal papers inside the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, while the pocket sleeves have helped them arrange their additional documents with ease. Since the bottle holder pocket is inside the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and provides a steady hold on most commonly sized bottles, it prevents the possibility of spills while also keeping users’ bottles safe from any dust or external contaminants during their travel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have also noted that the bag’s ability to hold various things at once doesn’t require them to bargain the storage of one thing for another. Such users mention that even with a laptop, they can fit their required paperwork and power cords into the bag easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But even with all these features in terms of looks and functionality, users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains quite sturdy and durable. This, once again, is due to the materials that are used within the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, which allow it to hold its own against regular wear and tear. With that, the size of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; serves as a critical component. It ensures that its strength doesn’t play against it. Also, it doesn’t make it look too big for women executives, who need to maintain a particular aesthetic with their accessories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that these qualities come together to present a laptop bag that doesn’t look like one remarkably. But which still has all the functionalities that one could expect from a traditional laptop or messenger bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only a couple of users take issue with the quality of the material. This is by far the only complaint that is voiced by a minimal number of users. A vast majority of other users cannot simply stop singing praises of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, users note that the&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Backpack with Wristlet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is something that provides excellent value for money. Some have gone as far as to state that it is everything that they need in a laptop or executive bag, with utilities and functionality packed in a nicely wrapped exterior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a woman in business who needs the most out of her accessories, then the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01DPNMCGI?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P.MAI Premium Leather Laptop Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might prove to be an excellent fit for you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="P.MAI" /><category term="Laptop Backpack" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>