<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-10-11T09:07:01+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bose A20 Aviation Headset With Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-A20-Aviation-Headset-With-Bluetooth-Dual-Plug-Cable-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bose A20 Aviation Headset With Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable Review" /><published>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-A20-Aviation-Headset-With-Bluetooth-Dual-Plug-Cable-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Bose-A20-Aviation-Headset-With-Bluetooth-Dual-Plug-Cable-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your work or hobby involves aviation by any chance, then you must know the importance of communication in the medium. In a medium where a single second’s delay or a slightly muffled sound could be life-threatening, your communication equipment must remain top of the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not having proper communication tools or experiencing poor audio while flying an aircraft can make you extremely anxious when the only feeling you should associate with the action is that of the utmost comfort, mixed with some adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, clear communication gives you the peace of mind that you require to fly correctly. It also enhances your experience in a way that leaves you feeling comfortable, and allows you to enjoy your flight the way that you are supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why you absolutely must choose a communication tool that you could rely upon no matter what. Doing so doesn’t only keep you safe, but it also takes care of the wellbeing of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to communication equipment that you can depend upon, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset with Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable, Black&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a class apart. When compared to traditional aviation headsets, it claims to provide higher active noise reduction, while also ensuring less clamping force. But it doesn’t stop there, and also offers active equalization along with customizable audio prioritization, as well as up to 45 hours of use from two AA batteries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When put together, these features provide the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with more than enough power to be identified as a strong communication tool, which could be very useful for those who are looking for a multipurpose headset to improve their flying experience. The fact that the headset is certified to FAA TSO-C139 and EASA ETSO-C139 standards further speak for its capabilities as an aviation communication tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headset also sports a comfortable design that is meant to make communications seamless during your flying experience. With an electret microphone that is built for clarity in relaying messages, the headset promises to be as reliable in transmitting outward communication as it is in delivering it. The microphone also comes with the ability to be plugged into either of the earcups, which adds yet another level of comfort for the user as they fly their plane or use the headset as a traditional communication device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it carries the traditional analog option, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has a strong feature in terms of Bluetooth wireless connectivity working for it. Since more and more communication and navigation devices now offer wireless connectivity, the Bluetooth feature improves the headset’s analog-only structure. With that being said, it is still available in an analog-only option, at a slightly lower price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Bose, its A20 headset provides 30 percent more active noise reduction and 30 percent less clamping force as compared to conventional aviation headsets. This quality makes the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; quite a favorable choice, since the more noise is reduced during aviation communication, the better it is for the pilot as well as the ones who are corresponding with them through the control tower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users, these features shine through in terms of their active communication, where the noise reduction and clarity in transmission are significantly noticeable. This holds true whether they are flying a small Cessna or a high noise helicopter. Users have also claimed that they can communicate very clearly even if their main volume is turned to a lower setting. This also makes the headset appeal to student pilots, who need to be extra-reliant on their communication during their training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also delivers on the aspect of sound quality and makes it so much easier to listen to music through a communication headset. While the Bose Active EQ feature adjusts the levels of audio notes in a communication or recording channel, the ergonomic control module lets you seamlessly switch between your communication and music. At the same time, it also lets you mix two audio channels at once. Multipoint connectivity enhances this feature and makes it easier to handle different communication channels. According to users, this feature adds to the ease of use that the headset promises to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is designed for extended use and utilizes high-quality materials, the headset is very comfortable to wear. Users have noted that the headset remains very lightweight, which is due to the high-quality plastic that it uses for its structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery life also provides great backup time whether you are communicating actively or just listening to music. This has been noted by various users, who term the headset as being worth every penny. They note how easy it is to communicate during each of their flights, while also ensuring that they don’t have to run around finding charging ports for their headset before every takeoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these qualities, users have gone on record to deem the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; as one of the best headsets for aviation that are currently available in the market. Nearly everyone who uses it is very happy with it, and their recommendations to others for buying their own pair of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; add to the overall credibility of the headset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, some users take issue with the material, since it is mostly plastic. But the lightweight and soft-touch add to the users’ comfort level, who argue against such complaints very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is safe to say that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010FTYIUS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bose A20 Aviation Headset with Bluetooth Dual Plug Cable, Black&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a bold yet successful attempt by the company to strengthen its presence within the aviation industry further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With features that appeal to different levels of experience for various pilots, it remains an investment that could help you from learning to fly a plane to operating your small aircraft on your own with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pursue adventure and life with these headphones to accompany you and keep you in the know while you fly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Aviation Headset" /><category term="Bose Headset" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Dyson-Supersonic-Hair-Dryer-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer Review" /><published>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Dyson-Supersonic-Hair-Dryer-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Dyson-Supersonic-Hair-Dryer-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most hyped hair dryers of 2019 is the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Dyson is a company that has brought many engineering innovations to the market, in time that spans 4 years of research and 600 prototypes before reaching the ideal finished product. 
Now, you’re probably wondering if it’s possible to have such remarkable innovations on a basic hair dryer. The majority of buyers seem to share the opinion that Dyson has managed to re-invent and innovate the basic hair dryer, but the question at hand is specifically about whether or not the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has changed the playing field. With a price tag of $399, this is one of the most expensive hair dryers available, and people want to know if it’s worth its value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we get to the pros and cons, let’s talk about the design. The design is sleek and smooth, and uses a small and efficient V9 digital motor, which is the smallest the company has to offer. This enables Dyson to get rid of the bulk that is usually at the top rear of dryers, and shift the manpower into its handle. That’s right, the handle conceals the motor that runs the dryer and shifts the weight into a more proportionate and even distribution, as well as making it have an overall compact look and feel. Buyers everywhere collectively expressed their relief by not having to hold a heavy weight over their head for an extended period of time, as is standard with most hair dryers.
 This dryer comes equipped with sensors that regulate the temperature 20 times in a second and relays the data back to a microprocessor to ensure the level of heat remains constant. This microprocessor keeps airflow temperature smooth and stable, with the temperature being kept under 150 degrees, so no more burning hair smell and hair damage is kept at a minimal. You get 3 heat settings and 3 airflow power settings to pick from, present on the back of the dryer. Temperature settings can be found on the left, and fan speed on the right side. Power and cool mode air buttons are found to be positioned on the handle, easy to reach with a thumb.
 The effort of engineering the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; utilized shines through when you find out the 3 nozzles (standard wide, narrower for precise styling, and a diffuser) attach to the dryer magnetically. 
On the edges of the nozzles, there are “lips” that keep the flow cool and ensure that hot air doesn’t blow through, making the changing of attachments quick, easy and effortless.  While other companies offer technological advancements involving the pairing of a gadget with an app, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; really shows us how tech advancements can be made to better things in ways that were never considered to need improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, onto the pros. Most users of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; believe it does not get as hot as other dryers. Thanks to that, they also report their hair being much smoother, and less prone to falling as often happens when using a professional blowout, rather than a burnt, frizzy look. This is because of the microprocessor regulating temperature process detailed above.
If heat above 150 degrees Celsius is applied, it can end up damaging the hair badly, which is what happens with most traditional hair dryers. Most customers gleefully report that they didn’t need to style their hair after blow drying due to the effectiveness of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. 
Buyers also report being able to hold normal conversations while the dryer is running. Moreover, this is where you see the engineering of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in effect: by adding 2 extra blades in the fan present in the handle, the noise generated by the motor is at a frequency that is outside of the normal range of hearing. Pretty cool, don’t you think? The design of the dryer is compact, and straighter compared to traditional L-shaped dryers, which makes it easy to fit into smaller drawers and cupboards, and squeeze into hand carries if needed. 
Reviews also show that on average, it cut down hair drying time by half, even for people with thicker hair. That’s thanks to Dyson testing in their own lab and finding out that the speed with which the air is pushed out matters more than the amount of heat it took. Thus, the motor is around 8 times more powerful compared to competitors, and the heat is kept at a lower level to minimize the amount of unnecessary hair damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cons may outweigh the pros for some people. Some Amazon buyers report their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; did not last a long time, at an average of 6 months. That’s a deal breaker for people who would otherwise be willing to shell out near $400 for a hair dryer, and it is also the biggest recurring complaint among customers. Even when the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; worked perfectly, most people seem to agree that even with all the revamp, this dryer is a bit too expensive to justify buying it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The verdict seems to be that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; falls into the “luxurious” category rather than an upgrade. The design and performance are new and improved, but let’s be honest, it’s still a hair dryer. So if you are looking to splurge, use a dryer regularly or a professional wanting the most expensive dryer that money can get you, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01F6XZ6BS?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a gadget reviewed to be worth it for those who have the means, but it is not seen as the next big must-have product.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Hair Dryer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nintendo Switch Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Nintendo-Switch-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nintendo Switch Review" /><published>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Nintendo-Switch-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Nintendo-Switch-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Video games are one of the most popular ways to unwind after a long day of work, a stressful few hours at school, or after a particularly tough time of running chores. From expensive consoles to affordable apps, everyone plays their games on their terms, with some opting for exclusively single-player games and others going for options with multiplayer support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But no matter what kind of games you play, you must be aware of a certain few brands that are synonymous with the very idea of gaming. Just one mention of these brands bring images of their most popular games to mind, and you cannot help but resonate with the feeling everyone has while playing those games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to popular gaming, Nintendo’s name doesn’t need any introduction. From Gen X to Millennials, and now to Gen Z, everyone’s childhood seems to be rife with the gaming giant’s offerings. With various games from its library now being household names, the mere mention of Nintendo is sure to spark joy in anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why, when you can see that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a Neon Red and Neon Blue Joy-Con, you have a pretty good idea of what to expect. Sporting support for some of the label’s most endearing titles such as Super Smash Bros and Mario Kart, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch – Neon Red and Neon Blue Joy-Con - HAC 001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a Switch console, Switch Dock, left and right Joy-Con, Joy-Con grip and straps, and an AC adapter with HDMI cable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with everything that you might need for a mobile-to-console gaming experience, with all the accessories being light enough to carry around regularly. With multiple play modes, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could also be an excellent fit for someone who wants the most value for money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could be used as a handheld console with both Joy-Con attached. It also could be used in its tabletop mode with each detachable Joy-Con acting as its separate controller for multiple players. With it, it could also be docked to connect with a TV and have two or more players join in on the fun. In this docked mode, each Joy-Con also acts as its separate controller, and you could buy additional Joy-Con in case you want your multiplayer experience to involve more than two people. This extended multiplayer support means that you can play your favorite titles with family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; handheld device by itself sports a 6.2” screen. According to users, the display of the Switch device is bright and crisp and provides a great visual experience to those who enjoy high-quality gaming. Since the screen is used both in its handheld mode and the tabletop mode, this makes &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; an excellent fit for those who enjoy mobile gaming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, the ability of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to be transformed into a full console and connect to a TV through its dock adds to its value proposition. Many users note that the device translates its games and graphics to the screen beautifully, and provides a gaming experience that is both high quality and fun for the players involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; itself provides up to 3 hours of battery time in handheld mode. The battery life is quite decent under the high-quality gaming experience that it offers to its users. While the battery goes out in a few hours in the handheld mode, users could charge their &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; while using it in its docked mode. Users have noted that this solves the battery problem as long as you are comfortable in playing games while having your Switch docked. This also means that if you are playing with family and friends on your TV, you won’t have to worry about the battery running out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Joy-Con connectivity in multiplayer mode is wireless, which makes each Joy-Con a delight to play with according to users. The battery life for each Joy-Con is said to be around 20 hours of playtime, but some users mention that it seems to last longer. Since the Joy-Con are charged whenever they are put over their own dock or attached with the handheld during its charging, it has been noted that getting them ready for multiplayer game time is not difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One issue that only a handful of users have seemed to notice in the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; appears to be its battery time. According to them, the battery runs out too soon for their single-player or handheld mode enjoyment, after which they have to charge the product. However, this complaint remains limited to a select few users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has had multiple versions released over the years, with the most recent one being released in July 2019. You can get your own for $269, which is a very affordable price tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains a perfect match for those who enjoy casual gaming. With multiple play modes to choose from, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MUAGZ49?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could provide the ideal gaming experience to users - especially those who enjoy multiplayer games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a multi-functional gaming device that comes with support for some of the most popular gaming titles in the world, the Nintendo Switch with Neon Red and Neon Blue Joy-Con might be exactly what you need.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Nintendo Switch" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Parrot Pf728000 Anafi Drone Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Parrot-PF728000-Anafi-Drone-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Parrot Pf728000 Anafi Drone Review" /><published>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Parrot-PF728000-Anafi-Drone-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Parrot-PF728000-Anafi-Drone-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the recent advancements in technology, various new tools have come to the forefront to improve the work processes of the everyday professional. With that, these tools have proven to be an excellent way for casual users to have fun with technology. These new technologies have opened doors to a multitude of professional and recreational opportunities, which make the lives of users so much better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drone technology is a prime example of that. While highly used by surveillance and law enforcement agencies, they also prove to be an excellent fit for professionals such as photographers, researchers, engineers, and rescue operators. But they are not limited by that application. They also prove to be just as equally suitable for those who want to use the technology for fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promising to be a great fit for a variety of applications, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, equipped with a 4K HDR Camera claims to be one such addition to the unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) technology market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sporting a 4K HDR camera with a 21 MP Sony sensor, the drone can film in 4K, Full HD or 2.7K videos, as well as 21MP photos. It also boasts up to 2.8 times digital zoom with a f/2.4 wide angle ASPH lens. The drone is a quadcopter that can be folded easily, all while sporting a 180° vertical swivel camera. It also claims to have wind resistance of up to 31 mp/h and a Wi-Fi connection range of up to 2.5 miles (4 km).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from these features, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also comes with special applications to make UAV flying easier. With FreeFlight 6 and Parrot Skycontroller 3, the drone claims to make the act of flying this UAV simple yet safer for pilots of any skill level. It also boasts of a weight of 320g, which makes it quite mobile-friendly. It also provides 25 minutes of in-flight battery time, with the ability to be charged with external batteries through a USB-C port.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is built to be helpful to novice UAV pilots. For instance, its software is programmed to take off or land with just a single button, with the function to return to its starting point in case of signal loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With optimized exposure control and the ability to expand the memory using micro SD cards, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; claims to be the perfect drone for those who are delving into UAV flying for the first time. The drone is also available in four packages, which all come with a standard 16 GB micro SD card for memory, and additional software according to the package selected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Base package comes with just the drone, a remote controller, and a battery. But the Extended package also has a carrying case, two batteries, and two months of access to Adobe Creative Cloud. The Work package contains the feature of creating 3D models using Pix4Dmodel, while also having a carrying case and four batteries. Whereas, the Thermal kit comes with two cameras in the drone for thermal imaging, as well as a carrying case, three batteries, and software support for thermal imaging applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is relatively easy to use, which makes it an excellent fit for those who are still learning to fly UAVs. With that, those who have used it professionally also seem to like how simple it is to fly. Some praise the software, which makes it very easy to understand and operate the Anafi Drone, while others point towards the drone’s compact and virtually noiseless operation as its best quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As explained above, the battery life of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is supposed to last for 25 minutes in-flight time. With external batteries that could charge the Anafi Drone for another 25 minutes each, it gets easier to get more flight time out of the drone when you do not have access to a direct power source. Users have noted that this ability, combined with the accurate assessment of backup time makes the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; pretty comfortable to operate as compared to other drones that need owners to find power outlets here and there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With its 4K camera that comes with a Sony sensor and an f/2.4 wide-angle ASPH lens, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; claims to take high-quality videos and images. According to users, this claim is not far off the mark, since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; actually does capture clear images that are suitable for commercial applications, such as checking heightened structures for construction issues or taking aerial videos or images for promotional media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 320g weight, as well as its compact structure, also work in the drone’s favor, with users noting that they perhaps remain the best features of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone, Foldable Quadcopter Drone with 4K HDR Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Since the drone is extremely light and foldable, it could be carried by any professional or UAV enthusiast on their travels easily - all without adding any significant weight to their existing equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone, Foldable Quadcopter Drone with 4K HDR Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes at an affordable price of $700, users also praise its overall value proposition as compared to its total cost. With the ability for expandable storage, external batteries, and return to home feature in the face of signal loss, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; proves itself to be a multi-purpose UAV that could easily hold its own within a variety of sectors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, some users have complained about how the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone, Foldable Quadcopter Drone with 4K HDR Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; doesn’t hold up to its promises of being able to hold against windy conditions. Other than that, the drone seems to be getting pretty good reviews by those who use it casually or who indulge in aerial photography regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone, Foldable Quadcopter Drone with 4K HDR Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; seems to be the right choice for those who want to use it for aerial imaging that serves a variety of commercial purposes. With that being said, it might cause a few issues for those who use it in windy conditions, since the lightweight feature might prove to be a disadvantage in such situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D5R2JKL?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrot PF728000 Anafi Drone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is great for taking high-quality images and being a good fit for easy UAV flying, as well as a suitable option for those who want a drone to provide aerial visuals for their primary professional responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, it could also be an excellent option for those who wish to use an affordable yet high-quality drone for casual UAV flying.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Drone" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vmoda Xfbt2 Crossfade Wireless Headphones Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/vmoda-xfbt2-crossfade-wireless-headphones-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vmoda Xfbt2 Crossfade Wireless Headphones Review" /><published>2019-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/vmoda-xfbt2-crossfade-wireless-headphones-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/vmoda-xfbt2-crossfade-wireless-headphones-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to striking a balance between comfort and high-quality audio, nothing fulfills these requirements for an audiophile the way that Bluetooth-powered headphones do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains understandable as well since Bluetooth headphones are specifically built to provide wireless playback while still maintaining a certain standard of audio quality. While the sound quality in most Bluetooth-only headphones is constrained by their technology, they always offer quite an impressive soundstage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But all of this is further enhanced if these headphones also come with wired playback - which allows them to compete with superior quality headphones in terms of delivering clear, impressive sound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, finding such a pair of headphones could be difficult. This is especially true when looking for one that fits a specific price point while also being respectful of sustainability and lifestyle choices. Choices may include those such as a product that does not use animal leather in its structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is where this offering by V-MODA comes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For audiophiles who respect a particular lifestyle and want to abide by it in every shape and form, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA XFBT2-MBLACK Crossfade 2 Wireless Over-Ear Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; seem to be a perfect fit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to being sold at an affordable price, the headphones come with a structure that is built with high quality, vegan leather. This makes them one of the few options in high-quality headphones that are made for vegans while also being respectful of budgetary constraints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But being wireless or using sustainable and vegan materials are not the only qualities exhibited by the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The headphones also comprise of 50mm dual-diaphragm drivers, hi-resolution CCAW coils, and hi-res audio certified by the Japan Audio Society (JAS). They also come with Analog Purist Zero Latency, which claims to prevent any latency issues that are often encountered with gaming, videos, and music performances such as those of DJs. As noted by users, all of these features result in a seamless, precise, and distortion-free listening experience, which remains impressive on all accounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Available in black, white, and rose gold colors, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also sports a high-quality structure that uses a Steel Flex headband along with the vegan leather specified above. To enhance the value proposition of this structure, the headphones are also foldable to a very impressive extent through V-MODA’s Cliq Fold feature. This makes them a perfect fit for the unique, Exoskeleton case that comes with them. It has been noted that these structural elements provide optimal durability for these headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headphones also come with a built-in microphone, which is integrated into the headset as a stealth-like feature. This hidden microphone allows users to make clear and hassle-free phone calls, while also providing them with support for voice command and recognition features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you might have guessed already, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; come equipped with a hybrid feature, which lets them connect to other devices via Bluetooth or analog cable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with Bluetooth wireless connectivity, they come with their own battery backup. Here, the headphones demonstrate an impressive 14 hours of battery life, with the FastCharge ability offering up to 4 hours of battery backup against a 30-minute charge. Of course, this battery backup is only reserved for playback over Bluetooth. If users chose to use the headphones with a wire rather than its battery, they could enjoy unlimited hours of playback. Users have noted this feature to be a strong selling point for the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Hi-Resolution audio is only available in wired mode and not on Bluetooth, those opting for the Rose Gold version of the headphones could enjoy the Qualcomm aptX feature, which promises to provide CD-like quality even over Bluetooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these features make up for a great pair of multi-function headphones, they don’t let the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; turn away from sound quality, the one element that is the most important aspect of any headphones. Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides an impressive soundstage with distinct clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the sound produced by the V-MODA XFBT2 Crossfade 2 remains quite clear and translates the notes of any recording to real-life quite well. This alludes to how the 50mm dual-diaphragm work their magic in keeping bass, mids, and highs separate, with the difference being heard in the sound quality delivered by the headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Features such as hi-resolution CCAW coils, JAS certified hi-res audio, and Analog Purist Zero Latency only add to the effectiveness of the sound quality, and provide an ideal soundstage. In fact, users have noted that the sound delivered by the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is so impressive that it makes the upgrade from their previous headphones feel absolutely worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The durability and comfort also play a big part in making users recommend the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to others. Since the headphones use high-quality materials with nearly-indestructible Steel Flex, they prove to stand the test of time. With that, the materials used during the creation of these headphones make them exceptionally comfortable for extended wear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, some users take issue with the way that the highs and mids sound within the headphones. But for the most part, even those critical of the sound quality agree that using the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was definitely an impressive experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA XFBT2-MBLACK Crossfade 2 Wireless Over-Ear Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains an excellent choice for those who are looking for extremely comfortable and durable headphones while also being mindful of sound and environmental quality as well as budget. In fact, it wouldn’t be incorrect to state that the headphones prove to be an all-round fit to the needs of the typical audiophile, but without burdening their pockets with high prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a high-quality pair of headphones that don’t break the bank for you, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;V-MODA Headphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could prove to be a great fit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the product and see if it meets your specific needs. It just might do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Headphones" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Darkphone By Darkweb Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/new-darkphone-by-darkweb-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Darkphone By Darkweb Review" /><published>2019-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/new-darkphone-by-darkweb-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/new-darkphone-by-darkweb-review/">&lt;p&gt;Every day, we see more and more people complain about how hard it is to access their favorite ISIS execution videos, buy drugs from their preferred online marketplace, or hire a professional Hitman to kill unpleasant members of their family. But after countless hours of evading justice and thinking in a reliable solution for their customers’ problems, the DarkWeb people decided to come up with an ambitious idea: the Darkphone. The Darkphone is the newest proposal that takes away all of the obstacles standing between you and what is considered inappropriate, disgusting or even illegal. You can finally have quick and secure access to the world’s most twisted content, kindly condensed in the form of an elegant smartphone, with a 12MP camera, 64GB of storage space and many different colors available!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Darkphone contains the same functions of a normal smartphone, but its attractiveness is completely based on its operating system. This phone’s software works directly with the DarkWeb and all of its apps without the need for an alternate processor. The possibilities are endless! If you’ve had enough of driving to the grocery store to buy a gun, by using the new GunHub you can order it and receive it directly in your home. If the delivery guy takes over thirty minutes to arrive with your package, he will be executed on a private streaming session with you, which you can instantly share with your friends!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tired of waiting for that old-fashioned dealer to arrive with your precious drugs? Try UberDrugs. Can’t find a decent Hitman to finally kill the person who fired you from your last job, even if that was completely your fault because you couldn’t stop laughing out loud at ISIS execution videos? Try Murder.io. Or maybe you’ll want to relax a little after a hard day of work and watch a free movie. No worries: Pirateflix has the best movie catalog available, and 80% percent chances of finding a poorly recorded version with Chinese subtitles of your favorite films. And of course, here’s something for the little ones: Methlab, a useful tool to learn step-by-step how to cook your first meth batch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A significant number of renowned investors have collaborated in the developing of this product, and many of them have shared how pleased they are with the results. We got a few words from one of the most outstanding contributors of the Darkphone project, who asked to keep his name a secret as he is a public personality, so to protect his identity we decided to call him Marcos Kuczerberg. “There are many groups and communities that have always looked for a commonplace to share their lives and interests. We have created a product that offers an awesome meeting space for the outcasts, to successfully cover all the necessities they might have. Nevertheless, this phone also has room for those who have boring hobbies or regular lives. For example, you can download Facebook!” said Kuczerberg just before plugging himself into the wall and turning himself off to charge what looked like a big pair of batteries poking from his back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acceptance rate of the Darkphone has been sensational. The public has not stopped sending positive comments and reviews, where they praise the wonders of the Darkphone. XXXR4inbowD4shXXX, an early user of the product, has already bought eight of them and wrote on his personal blog: “My colleagues and I have felt the disgusting glances upon us our whole lives. We have been exiled to the darkest part of society. Aren’t we supposed to enjoy life as well? What about us? No one pays us any attention. All of the big companies have always kept us away, only focusing on the market segment they love the most: the rich white people. And now, with this phone, someone finally thought about us: the weirder rich white people.”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GPS system incorporated into the phone was specially designed by the best computer engineers of the world and a full team of professional stalkers —which were the same people—. You can set up the GPS functions to let you know when the cops are around, find the best places to hide a body in your area or even help you to point out the most ideal spots to start a mass shooting. This particular feature can also indicate efficient ways to visit the schools in your region, suggesting the best options to approach their students, from candies to drugs (and where to buy them, naturally). In case of emergency, the GPS automatically elaborates different escape routes to other countries, using its friendly and sophisticated maps system. It also recommends some creative and funny new names for your new life at the edge of the law!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this phone’s functions are not entirely based on things that are beyond legality. The DarkWeb has been used as a refugee for activists that have been persecuted for defending and spreading their ideas, therefore, you can also stand up for your beliefs! The Darkphone gives you a platform to start forums without having the fear of being pursued by the authorities. You can initiate important conversations against vaping prohibition, defend gun ownership, white supremacy, or why you liked the last season of Game of Thrones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our verdict: Pure awesomeness. Contact your nearest street vendor to get your hands on the new Darkphone by DarkWeb.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>9</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">Every day, we see more and more people complain about how hard it is to access their favorite ISIS execution videos, buy drugs from their preferred online marketplace, or hire a professional Hitman to kill unpleasant members of their family. But after countless hours of evading justice and thinking in a reliable solution for their customers’ problems, the DarkWeb people decided to come up with an ambitious idea: the Darkphone. The Darkphone is the newest proposal that takes away all of the obstacles standing between you and what is considered inappropriate, disgusting or even illegal. You can finally have quick and secure access to the world’s most twisted content, kindly condensed in the form of an elegant smartphone, with a 12MP camera, 64GB of storage space and many different colors available!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Delonghi Esam3300 Super Automatic Coffee Espresso Machinne Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/delonghi-esam3300-super-automatic-coffee-espresso-machinne-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delonghi Esam3300 Super Automatic Coffee Espresso Machinne Review" /><published>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/delonghi-esam3300-super-automatic-coffee-espresso-machinne-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/delonghi-esam3300-super-automatic-coffee-espresso-machinne-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I must admit that I wasn’t a coffee fan until recently. I couldn’t understand the hype about it until I tried this one coffee from this one local place, and now I’m a convert. I wanted to recreate the experience but then I found out that it’s pretty hard to make good coffee unless you have a solid machine to do the work for you. Disappointed, I turned to Google to help me out, and came across the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300 Super Automatic Espresso/Coffee Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Here, I will proceed to gather all the information and reviews I found in one neat little post so you can check it out and decide for yourself in case you’re in a similar spot as myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the first thing that people found attractive about this machine was its small size. It is compact at 14 inches and weighs in at 28.1 lbs, which I’ve come to learn is actually pretty modest for coffee machines. This is a great option for those with limited countertop space or small kitchens. It’s a good looking machine, with a silvery, metallic front side and black plastic sides and top. It gives off a very sleek and minimalistic home-style vibe. Now, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a large reservoir, able to hold 60 ounces of water at once. Remember that this machine was made to brew a cup at a time, rather than a whole pot. However, buyers note that the front panel controls give you the opportunity to adjust your cup size to 8 ounces, and you can then choose to add a “double shot”.
This will give you a double drink of 16 ounces. There is the ability to make 2 cups at the same time with the choice of one or two cup button. Now, most super automatic machines have their reservoir in the back. For the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, you can gain access to it from the front. This makes it more convenient to use. People who like to run on coffee day to day can appreciate this at-home coffee maker, thanks to the bigger reservoir size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Super automatic espresso machines utilize “beans-to-brew”, and this beast is no different. Its design is best suited for medium-roast coffee, as oily beans are reported by Amazon buyers to clog up the whole machine’s system. When it comes to the grinder, the bean hopper is described to hold around 7 ounces of coffee, which you refill from the top of the machine. 
Next to the hopper, you’ll find dials for grind setting, which enables you to adjust the coarseness of the grind to your liking. Most hardcore coffee drinkers already know that a good cup of coffee requires the perfect grind level, otherwise you just end up with subpar coffee. Apart from the grind setting and the “extraction rate” knob, there’s a “contact time” knob which lets you decide how long you want the water to be in contact with the grounds. As shared by users, the noise level of the machine is relatively on the lower side when  compared it to owners’ previously owned machines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part for people like me, who are not as well versed in the world of coffee yet, is the fact that this machine accommodates for ground coffee as well. There is a bypass doser on top of the machine, under a hatch you lift up, between the bean hopper and warming tray. The purchase comes with a scooper so all you need to do is put the grounds in, set the dials and press the brew button. Isn’t that awesome?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I can have traditional pick-me-up coffee in the morning, and ground decaf coffee in the evening. From the reviews I’ve gathered, some users have shared that using water that has been distilled is a top priority to keep your machine running smooth and living long. The unit is reported to require some maintenance to keep it running as it did on the first day and keep things moving. Once in a while, a light will blink to know you need to descale it, and if you use filtered water the time between descaling will increase drastically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only few cons reported were that you cannot see when the beans are running low, and hardcore coffee drinkers complained that the reservoir wasn’t big enough and required topping every so often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300 Super Automatic Espresso/Coffee Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has been noted as easy to use: just add water and the machine will automatically add beans to the hopper as needed. The whole coffee making process is said to take roughly 5 minutes. For people in a hurry in the morning, this is a pretty good feature to have. This unit has the ability to run a clean cycle when started and also when shutting down. Its head/filter unit is removable and hence easy to clean, and overall customers report this machine manages ground coffee better than most other models. 
People who self-described themselves as not so experienced with coffee making machines or even coffee in general were comfortable in choosing the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300 Super Automatic Espresso/Coffee Machine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; as their go-to. Professionals who had used manual machines in the past reviewed their satisfaction with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and appreciate they don’t have to fill filters, empty grounds and so on. The machine does all that for you and used grounds are deposited into a container present on the right side. It requires to be emptied about every 10 cups, and has no environment-harming pods to waste. With drip coffee machines, people report to usually end up with a lot more than they needed, which all then goes to waste. But the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000N2YKQ0?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DELONGHI ESAM3300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is customizable to your tastes and requirements, has lesser waste, and has easy maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Coffee Machine" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gowise Usa 8 In 1 Electric Pressure Cooker Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/gowise-usa-8-in-1-electric-pressure-cooker-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gowise Usa 8 In 1 Electric Pressure Cooker Review" /><published>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/gowise-usa-8-in-1-electric-pressure-cooker-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/gowise-usa-8-in-1-electric-pressure-cooker-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast paced world, it’s no secret that most of us have no time to cook full meals from scratch, particularly if it requires intensive cooking times. College students, busy parents and the elderly are some people who are simply unable to give cooking the time it demands. When time is short and limited, some people even skip meals, which isn’t good for you if you keep doing it consistently. To remedy this, an investment into an electric pressure cooker should be considered. These staple items that should be present in every household makes sure meals are quick and easy to prepare, especially for those people who are into eating clean, made from scratch food. Investing in a capable electric pressure cooker is a great time saver and you will get delicious meals in return. You can’t go wrong with that!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE USA 8-Quart 8-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker/Slow Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one such cooker that caught my eye. So I’m on here gathering feedback and reviews for people who are considering investing in this amazing cookware. These days, you even get the option of having a “smart” pressure cooker that connects to WiFi, which is just crazy if you ask me. A solid electric pressure cooker that can do its job is what one needs, and you don’t have to go broke trying to get one. 
The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE 8-in-1 Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a programmable cooker with a stainless steel cooking pot that comes in with build-in presets to do your work for you. It has options available for a wide variety of meals, like rice, multigrain, porridge, stew or meat, poultry, veggies, seafood and so on. If you prefer more versatility in your cooking, this cooker comes with a manual mode that lets you decide between three different pressure settings. You can choose between low, medium and high. Buyers shared on amazon that this feature allows one to specify and customize the cooking experience. 
The biggest selling point of this pressure cooker is its versatility. It has a one of a kind design that gives you the functions of 9 different appliances in one place. The tasks this machine can do range from traditional pressure cooking, rice pudding, porridge, to yogurt maker, to egg maker, with only a push of a button! You can use this device as as warmer, slow cooker, steamer, browner. This wide spectrum allows this pressure cooker to be a suitable option for students or people who have basic knowledge of cooking and are just starting off. The safety mechanisms are in place to keep you safe from the build-up of steam. There is an in-built pressure release button on the lid, which makes it easier, safer and quicker to release the pressure build-up. This product boasts an ETL stamp for matching industry standards of safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most Amazon reviewers are quick to praise the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE USA 8-Quart 8-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker/Slow Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The lid is described as being easy to screw on, with one simple counter-clockwise move. The cooker will display the pressure gauge level, heat level, timer, and it also lets you know when the cooking is about to begin on an LED readout screen in the front. One nifty feature is the ability to delay start time. You might find that this comes in handy when you’re running late from the office and wish that dinner would cook itself. You can set the time and have dinner waiting for you when you get home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The user interface is simple: choose your cooking option and set the timer. The cook pot is made of stainless steel and with pressure cookers at a similar price point, competitors tend to use Teflon non-stick coating for their cooking pots, which speaks about the quality of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE 8-in-1 Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Most people choose to opt for stainless steel as Teflon is being phased out due to concerns about its effect on health. A steel rack comes inside the cooker, allowing you to cook multiple foods at once, for example, meat at the bottom and veggies at the top. For people who are completely new to using pressure cookers, one reminder left by a helpful reviewer states that you need to allow some time to pass for the pressure to build up and start the cooking process. Likewise, when it is done you need to let the pressure drop down before you open the pot. Replacement parts are easily available on Amazon for the cooking pots and sealing ring, ensuring your pressure cooker lasts you for years. Most reviewers stated they were new to cooking or pressure cookers and were impressed with the ease of usage and the quality of meals this pressure cooker has helped them make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cooker goes up to 8 quarts, with instructions saying you should fill the pot to about 60%, while buyers note that even 5 quarts is enough to feed a whole family, or 8-10 people if we’re being specific. All of that, with less stress and even less clean-up time.The only gripe some customers have complained about is that the manual is not very intensive, which isn’t a mark on the pressure cooker itself. Moreso, there is an owner’s manual available online, but the cooker’s simple design doesn’t require much know-how. As a bonus, Amazon reviewers have shared their experiences with GoWISE customer support, and they are reported to be responsive and prompt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, my verdict would be that if you’re often in a rush and would like to save some time as well as get a headstart on that healthy eating lifestyle you’ve been wanting, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GTU2UQM?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GoWISE USA 8-Quart 8-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker/Slow Cooker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; should fit your needs perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Electric Pressure Cooker" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Audeze Lcd X Over Ear Suspension Headphones</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-x-over-ear-suspension-headphones/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Audeze Lcd X Over Ear Suspension Headphones" /><published>2019-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-x-over-ear-suspension-headphones</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-x-over-ear-suspension-headphones/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who appreciate music in its various forms, it is imperative to have equipment that supports their passion and translates every musical note in its purest form. It holds true just as much for music creators and sound engineers as it does for audiophiles and music enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to high-quality equipment, it must ensure a trouble-free rendition and lifelike listening experience for its users. After all, every creator wants their work to translate accurately for the listener, and every listener wants the utmost quality from each second they devote to their music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is where professional-grade headphones come in. With their unique structure, premium materials, and exceptional craftsmanship, they provide a listening experience like no other. That is why they remain a sought-after piece of equipment for every music professional and audiophile alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X Over Ear Open Back Headphone with New Suspension Headband Creator Package – no Travel case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is one such pair of superior quality headphones that stay true to the promises they make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important to note that while the Creator Package doesn’t come with a travel case or balanced cable, it still has the same pair of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headphones that are offered in the retail package. But this works to the advantage of those buyers who are looking for an affordable deal. It allows them to enjoy a discounted price for the same high-quality &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; headphones that come with the retail package, just without a travel case and balanced cable (which you can purchase separately).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sporting what it calls a “crystal clear” midrange, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes equipped with ultra-thin diaphragms, double-sided magnetic arrays, and the company’s signature Fazor Elements. All of these features come packed within a modern design structure which is made out of memory foam earpads, premium leather, and an ergonomic design with suspension headband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to sound quality, it’s hard to surpass the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The ultra-thin yet large 106mm diaphragms do what they claim to do, and deliver a sound that is certainly true to life. Those who have used the headphones sing praises of the quality produced by the headphones, especially when it comes to the midrange. According to users, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provides exemplary sound regardless of the acoustics or the room it is being used in, which makes it all the more perfect for creators and listeners alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s double-sided magnetic arrays prevent distortion and ensure the delivery of sound with realistic notes. It has been noted that this feature translates into providing a neutral, yet ultra-accurate sound, which brings out even the tiniest details of a recording to the forefront. This helps creators convert their sounds with a certain amount of confidence, while it provides listeners with an experience that remains unmatched by many other headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Audeze’s signature Fazor Elements are there to serve their own purpose. With double-sided magnetic arrays, these elements work to prevent resonance to a very impressive margin. As a result, the waveform delivered through the headphones shines through in terms of lifelike sound. This has been noted by users firsthand, who vouch for the headphones’ soundstage, bass, and realistic rendition, no matter what kind of recording they listen to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This clarity in sound quality, near-zero distortion, and accurate waveform all come together to make the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ideal for sound engineers, producers, and audiophiles alike. Whether someone wants to produce their own tunes for the world to listen to, or if they simply want to enjoy recordings developed by their favorite artists, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; could prove to be the best fit for the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from its superior sound quality, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also lauded for its built. Users note that the quality of the headphones’ structure is as good as the sound that it produces. This build quality is possible due to the way Audeze produces these headphones. Each pair of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is handcrafted in Audeze’s California facility, which allows the company to ensure optimal build quality using premium materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This attention to developing the headphones is translated very well in the comfort that they provide to the wearer. The memory foam, premium leather, and suspension headband along with the ergonomic structure provide a very comfortable fit to the wearer, even if they use the headphones for hours at a time. Users have noted that the headphones are comfortable to wear, even if they are “built like a tank.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, the lack of a travel case is irksome to a few users, who say that it has affected the lifespan of their headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But these complaints remain limited, whereas most users swear by the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X Over Ear Open Back Headphone with New Suspension Headband Creator Package – no Travel case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s quality and durability. According to them, the headphones are as perfect for sound mastering and mixing as they are for simply enjoying your favorite tunes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With exceptional sound quality, comfortable fit, and stylish yet durable build, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X Over Ear Open Back Headphone with New Suspension Headband Creator Package – no Travel case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains a great fit for those music creators and listeners who do not see the lack of a travel case as an issue for portability or equipment safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as they are using the headphones carefully, they can enjoy the same sound quality and product benefits as the retail package, except for the travel case. The necessity to buy your own balanced cable actually provides you with the freedom to choose between options, which adds to the customization options for the headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are one to enjoy music as a creator or a listener and want the best out of your equipment investments, then the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0765KJ5CB?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Audeze LCD-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; would prove to be a viable fit for you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Headphones" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/arsvita-car-audio-bluetooth-cassette-receiver-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver Review" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/arsvita-car-audio-bluetooth-cassette-receiver-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/arsvita-car-audio-bluetooth-cassette-receiver-review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you a music lover? Do you not like local radio stations, or get tired of not having music on demand? More importantly, does your car only have a tape player? Since most bands stopped putting out tapes sometime in the early 2000s, having the ability to play them in your car isn’t seen as such a big positive anymore. And, if you can’t afford to replace the entire stereo, it can seem like you’re stuck with the oldies and that random tape of the Oakridge Boys that somehow made its way into that one tucked-away box of junk that never gets thrown out. CDs, too, are going the way of the dinosaur, so those old adapters don’t work as well anymore. But the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07QSW6KNY?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; seems to be a good choice in overcoming this hurdle, and getting your favorite tunes playing again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it&quot;&gt;What Is It?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, it’s the modern equivalent of the adapters used to play CDs with only a tape deck. Here, the tape-shaped adapter is placed into the player, leaving the transmitter outside. Then, you can simply connect your device wirelessly via Bluetooth to play music, listen to podcasts, or even listen to audio-books as you drive! A tool like this is often a necessity for older cars, since they usually lack a hook up for modern technology. This works for practically all devices capable of a Bluetooth connection. Anything from iPods to smartphones, even to computers and tablets, can be used by this device. The cassette receiver is rechargeable, with an 8 hour long active battery time. That increases to over 160 when switched to standby mode. Being wireless, you’ll also be spared having cords running from your phone or device directly into your stereo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;who-should-use-it&quot;&gt;Who Should Use It?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two main categories of people who would do well with this product. The first are those who enjoy collecting and driving antique (or just older) cars. Often, dream cars from the 80s only came with a tape player, as nothing else was available at the time. Not only can changing out the entire stereo system be expensive, you also risk ruining any interior work during the process. If you’ve managed to preserve the original, that could be a nightmare. Instead, an adapter such as this can make it possible to play music in a modern way, using modern equipment. The second group of people are those who are driving an older car out of necessity. Whatever the reason, a complete stereo replacement is expensive, as mentioned above. Instead of completely replacing what already functions, you could simply use this product to overcome the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;interesting-features&quot;&gt;Interesting Features&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without a doubt, the most interesting feature of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07QSW6KNY?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is directly in its name:  Bluetooth. Unlike similar cassette adapters, this one is capable of connecting to your devices via Bluetooth. This saves a lot of hassle. Instead of having to manually plug in your phone or mp3 player every time you get into the car, it can automatically connect for you! Since your phone won’t have to leave wherever you normally store it while driving, such as your purse, a stand, or even just a cup holder, you’ll be less likely to leave it behind. You’ll also get rid of all of the bulky cords that seem to only clutter up the area and take up space. Do you take calls while driving? You can with this! Being hands-free is a safe way to keep up communication on the go, and this product offers it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-good&quot;&gt;The Good&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Amazon, a majority (70%) of the comments were very high, rating five stars for this product. It has been reported to work very well by quite a number of different customers. The cassette receiver seems to function as intended, giving users the ability to listen to music and other audio through older speakers in their car using this. One buyer in particular was happy to find that older speakers “can now be converted to Bluetooth speakers with this versatile tool.” The way that the product looked was highly praised, as well. It’s fairly small, and not bulky. The lack of wires means that it doesn’t clutter up the area around your stereo. Many have described it as “sleek”, which is something a lot of those who are proud of their cars aim for. On the whole, the product seems to function well, look nice, and please buyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-bad&quot;&gt;The Bad&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are a lot of good reviews, 13% of the reviews for the product are only one star. That, behind the five star ratings, is the highest percentage of the ratings. Many of the negative reviews seem to have similar problems. The most common of these are that the cassette simply ceases to work after a few weeks. They claim no damage to the product, only that it randomly died. Some have had the Bluetooth stop working on them. One user in particular mentions that, while it works well, he’s already had to buy two, because the others malfunctioned. A handful of people complain about the quality, saying that there was either a lot of background noise, or a constant humming while it was playing. A few of those who bought one have said that it was repeatedly ejected by their tape player, so couldn’t get it to work at all. To their credit, the company is prompt in discussing solutions, including full refunds, with those that had these problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what do we make of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07QSW6KNY?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Arsvita Car Audio Bluetooth Cassette Receiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;? With all of the facts, it seems to be a fairly nice choice for anyone who wants to listen to modern music in an antique car. The good reviews dwarf any of the bad ones. There are some problems with it, but the company seems to be on top of the matter when it comes to righting any wrongs. All-in-all, it’s a great purchase to make.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>12</name></author><category term="Bluetooth Adapters" /><category term="Car Accessories" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>