<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-17T15:19:13+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet. 
</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Apple iMac 27-inch Retina 5K</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/apple-imac-27-inch-retina-5k-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple iMac 27-inch Retina 5K" /><published>2019-08-17T05:00:45+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-17T05:00:45+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/apple-imac-27-inch-retina-5k-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/apple-imac-27-inch-retina-5k-review/">&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that Apple products are always a safe option. In terms of functionality, Apple is known for their user-friendly products, easy to use but continuously evolving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As technology continues to advance, Apple has remained consistent in what they offer: a clean modern look and feel for all their products, while also providing quality and durability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not a surprise, then, that Apple has become a symbol that stands out in between other leader brands. What started as a computer company, is now famous for its phones, music, TV, and even watch technology. They are a solid and reliable, and consumers know they can trust in them to provide fresh yet outstanding products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07Q1NBCVB/ref=fs_a_md_0&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;27” iMac&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; whose main feature is a &lt;strong&gt;Retina 5K&lt;/strong&gt; display, has been in the market since 2014, for almost five years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the last iMac product released by Apple (not counting the iMac Pro, released in 2017). However, this doesn’t mean that the 27” iMac Retina 5K is outdated. Far from it, Apple is a company known for a slow approach when designing new hardware. They are notable for spending years trying to perfect their products to make sure that they are the best they can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, one of their Apple designers was quoted in saying: &lt;em&gt;“Our goals are very simple — to design and make better products. If we can’t make something that is better, we won’t do it.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the birth of the company, many models have been scrapped and deemed not good enough for release. Apple makes sure their products meet all the requirements and are perfect for release, taking the time (years) before finally releasing them. Therefore, you can be sure that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07Q1NBCVB/ref=fs_a_md_0&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mac Retina 5K&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is created with the best technology Apple can offer to this day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This model was designed with professional photographers and video editors in mind, with the 5K resolution allowing 4K video to be played at its native resolution in Final Cut Pro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of storage, it offers the best option in the market so far: space &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; speed. A Fusion Drive, faster and more efficient than its predecessors. The processor is a new seventh-generation Intel Core, offering more speed than any iMac has reached before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course, what gives this iMac the name: the Retina 5K Display. With a pixel density so high you can’t detect a single one, to the color accuracy and vibrancy, it’s clearly the best addition so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the reviews have been positive, allowing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07Q1NBCVB/ref=fs_a_md_0&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;27” iMac Retina 5K&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to reach a rating of 4.5 stars out of 5, with particular interest in the screen quality (rated unanimously 5 stars).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users commented that this model is able to run many apps at the same time without degradation over time. The screen size and resolution has been said to be perfect. The colors are brilliant and sharp. The increased size of the screen allows for the user to have many windows open at the time and switch easily between them. The greater width gives allows for more dock space to keep the user’s most preferred programs available at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speed of the processor has been the focal point of many reviewers, which were left amazed by the upgrade when compared to previous models. The combination of both a good operative system (the High Sierra OS optimizes storage and performance), and the processor both contribute to make the iMac faster and enhance the user’s experience. Graphic designers have commented that the performance is the best they’ve ever worked with. The core processor and Radeon Pro 570x graphics card make both 4K and VR video possible to both view and edit.  The operative system — High Sierra OS — is said to work flawlessly and meet the user’s expectations. The built in speakers have been praised as well for their quality and the vibrant sound they produce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iMac comes with a rechargeable Magic Mouse and a rechargeable Magic Keyboard. They charge via lightning cable. The keyboard can be used while it’s charging, but the mouse has received negative comments because the port is underneath and therefore, cannot be used when connected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this, a few users said the keyboard is too small and uncomfortable, while the wide majority claimed the keyboard was extremely useful and praised the compact design. The mouse was “too flat” to some reviewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were some negative comments regarding the features, or lack thereof. Some commented the SuperDrive is no longer part of the machine, and the purchase of an external DVD drive is needed if the user wants to read or write DVDs or CDs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other thing to pay attention to, is that the new iMac comes with Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) as opposed to older models that used Thunderbolt 2. In this case, an adapter is needed in order to connect and operate the hard drives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, this model has been said to be an excellent Apple product. Despite the minor complains, users agree that iMacs are the most reliable desktops. Since their hardware and software are designed by the same company, there are no compatibility problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To attest to the quality of the product, there are also some reviews from users who purchased the iMac five years ago, commenting on the performance and durability, and how it keeps working flawlessly despite the passage of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most buyers go as far as to call the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07Q1NBCVB/ref=fs_a_md_0&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;iMac Retina 5K&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, “the best computer they’ve ever owned.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Victoria Blanco</name></author><category term="ReviewHuntr" /><category term="Product Reviews" /><category term="Reviews" /><category term="Review Website" /><summary type="html">It’s no secret that Apple products are always a safe option. In terms of functionality, Apple is known for their user-friendly products, easy to use but continuously evolving.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Audeze Mobius Premium 3D Gaming Headset with Surround Sound - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-mobius-premium-3d-gaming-headset-with-surround-sound-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Audeze Mobius Premium 3D Gaming Headset with Surround Sound - Review" /><published>2019-08-15T05:00:45+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-15T05:00:45+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-mobius-premium-3d-gaming-headset-with-surround-sound-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-mobius-premium-3d-gaming-headset-with-surround-sound-review/">&lt;p&gt;From playing games to enjoying high definition movies and TV shows on your screen, sound quality is everything. When streaming new tracks from your favorite artist, the experience remains incomplete without excellent sound quality. I, for one, have never been able to enjoy a game, watch Netflix or listen to Spotify with traditional speakers – and judging by the many reviews I read every day, I am not the only one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, we all have the right proper solution of headphones to save us from the plight of traditional speakers. After all, who doesn’t like to enjoy their games, movies and TV shows in privacy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With technologies such as Bluetooth, AAC, and Sony’s new LDAC that shares wireless sound on higher quality, connecting to a phone, computer, or TV with compatible technology is easier than ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t mind the presence of wires, then you could also enjoy surround sound with compatible headphones. All that you need to do is to connect them to your device, and you have your very own auditorium right at your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are just a few of the reasons why wireless headphones with surround sound are becoming so popular among home users who enjoy their games, video, and audio entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius Premium 3D Gaming Headset with Surround Sound&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is made to serve the needs of those very entertainment aficionados; people like you and I who wouldn’t want anything but the best when indulging in their favorite pastimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius headset&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; boasts a premium design that is reminiscent of traditional overhead headphones, complete with large over-the-ear speakers padded with memory foam. But that design is perhaps the only thing that is traditional about these headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s because they come with AAC, Bluetooth, and LDAC technology for wireless connectivity, while also having the ability to connect via USB or analog wires and providing 5.1 and 7.1 surround sound to the listener. Another quality that differentiates them is the ability to set up the adaptive sound on computers. This feature is possible by entering your HTRFs and the room size into the application provided by Audeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius headphones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; also come with the feature of being optimized for calls. They are “Discord Certified,” which makes them ideal for multiplayer gaming. With that, they also come with the ability to connect with popular consoles such as PlayStation 4 and Xbox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developed using head tracking technology by WAVES Nx, the headsets could provide an immersive gaming experience while playing titles like PUBG - where moving your head lets you explore the map or change your view like never before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users, the most sought after feature of the Audeze Mobius headphones is definitely the sound quality. With the ability to provide surround sound that offers an immersive gaming, visual entertainment, and music experience, the headphones are a must-have for those who want to unwind after a long day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bluetooth and LDAC connectivity ensures that users can roam around the house with ease while enjoying the content they have decided to watch or hear. As mentioned by users, the wireless connectivity also seems to be on par with what the price and manufacturer’s claims state it to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another feature that gets high praise is the comfortable material that is used to craft &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Since gamers, as well as audiophiles and Netflix bingers, all wear their headphones for a long time, they must meet all the requirements of comfort. Many users comment that these headphones meet this crucial need quite well. The memory foam covering the speakers adds to the support, and it’s replaceable too. Whereas, the headband also boasts a layer of comfortable yet durable memory foam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some users complain that despite being a gaming headset, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; isn’t for a PS4 or Xbox. Even those who speak highly of the sound quality are quick to mention that the headphones’ surround or 3D feature does not work with their consoles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They note that they are unable to detect directional sounds in games such as Black Ops 4, where it is essential to know where the opponents’ are. With that, other users have gone as far as to term them as the ultimate gaming headset and seem to have no problems using them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On both accounts, nearly all users agree that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is excellent for being an entertainment headset due to their sound quality. Some have gone as far as to note that even though they bought the headset for gaming, they have kept it to use as an audio and video experience device. Many note that the headphones are easy to connect via all modes and provide excellent passive noise cancellation. All made possible by compelling design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius Headset&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; seems to be a great purchase even at a high price tag for those who want superior sound quality in their entertainment experiences. Their comfort level and multiple connectivity options, especially the surround sound and LDAC, add to their value proposition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But questions arise when it comes to these headphones’ compatibility with PS4 and Xbox, which is strange considering that they are marketed as overall gaming headphones instead of being made just for PC gaming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, if you are looking for headphones that are optimal for PC gaming and provide fantastic sound quality, then the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-Immersive-Cinematic-Headphones-Bluetooth/dp/B07BDQZ52Z/ref=sr_1_10?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze Mobius&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; might be for you. Available in copper and blue, these could be an excellent addition to the home of any entertainment enthusiast.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Alan</name></author><category term="ReviewHuntr" /><category term="Product Reviews" /><category term="Reviews" /><category term="Review Website" /><summary type="html">From playing games to enjoying high definition movies and TV shows on your screen, sound quality is everything. When streaming new tracks from your favorite artist, the experience remains incomplete without excellent sound quality. I, for one, have never been able to enjoy a game, watch Netflix or listen to Spotify with traditional speakers – and judging by the many reviews I read every day, I am not the only one. Thankfully, we all have the right proper solution of headphones to save us from the plight of traditional speakers. After all, who doesn’t like to enjoy their games, movies and TV shows in privacy?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nuraphone - Wireless Bluetooth Over Ear Headphones With Earbuds - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/nuraphone-wireless-over-the-ear-headphones-with-earbuds-reivew/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nuraphone - Wireless Bluetooth Over Ear Headphones With Earbuds - Review" /><published>2019-08-15T05:00:45+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-15T05:00:45+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/nuraphone-wireless-over-the-ear-headphones-with-earbuds-reivew</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/nuraphone-wireless-over-the-ear-headphones-with-earbuds-reivew/">&lt;p&gt;If you have a busy schedule like me, then you might relate to the things you miss out on daily. You don’t have time to Netflix and chill. You can’t find time to schedule a spa appointment for a little R&amp;amp;R. You don’t even have spare time to give yourself a pep talk. Thankfully, the need for recreation, relaxation, and motivation is met by good music. Those who have a jam-packed calendar would agree sometimes all you must do is play some music and relax. Lose your worries and zone out- or in - for a specific timeframe. But given that you can’t blast your favorite tracks through your commute, at the gym, and work or class, even listening to music could be a difficult task. You’ll need the right equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is where headphones come in. Many people turn to these nifty devices to make sure that they have great music getting them through different parts of their day – all without disturbing anyone. For such professionals and students, having headphones that fulfill the need for privacy without compromising on quality is of the utmost importance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/nuraphone-Bluetooth-Headphones-Personalized-Cancellation/dp/B076X4KH11/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;qid=1565733161&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-7&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=7aef8cbdeb3b4e885180ce5ce611884a&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nuraphone Wireless Bluetooth Over Ear Headphones with Earbuds&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; promise to fulfill that requirement – with a little twist of their own. Even at sporting an overhead design, they have earbuds fitted into the place where a traditional headphone’s speakers are supposed to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ss&amp;amp;ref=as_ss_li_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=B076X4KH11&amp;amp;asins=B076X4KH11&amp;amp;linkId=c6d828b550b58eb27003278a87b7afb7&amp;amp;show_border=true&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result? A promise of superior quality active noise cancellation (ANC), personalized sound delivery to cater to your hearing needs, a whopping 20-hour of battery time, and a 12-month limited warranty. Seeing the price tag that the headphones carry, I decided to look into them to save fellow audiophiles the trouble of finding out whether these claims are valid or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For starters, I noted that the one thing customers have praised the most about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/nuraphone-Bluetooth-Headphones-Personalized-Cancellation/dp/B076X4KH11/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;qid=1565733161&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-7&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=7aef8cbdeb3b4e885180ce5ce611884a&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nuraphone Wireless Headphones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is their sound quality. Now, that is to be attributed to two things. First, it’s the very structure of the headphones, which uses earbuds instead of overhead speakers. Second, it’s the adaptive sound feature that seems to amaze most of its users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the effectiveness of the design of the earbuds is self-explanatory, it is vital to understand how it works. As noted by most users, the earbuds make sure that the headphones stay in place and delivers consistent quality by being in a fixed position. They also prevent any room for outside noise while offering clear high and low-frequency sounds. This feature makes them ideal for those students or professionals who want consistency in sound quality even as they make their way from one place to the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even more than the innovative design, it’s the adaptive sound feature that sets &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/nuraphone-Bluetooth-Headphones-Personalized-Cancellation/dp/B076X4KH11/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;qid=1565733161&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-7&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=7aef8cbdeb3b4e885180ce5ce611884a&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nuraphone Wireless Headphones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; apart from its counterparts. While other headphones try to deliver the same sound to every person, the &lt;em&gt;nuraphone headphones&lt;/em&gt; come with a built-in customization feature and a native app by the name of NURA. The headphones determine how to deliver sound to each listener according to how they respond to different sound frequencies. As a result, each user of these headphones can get the sound delivery adjusted to the way their ears perceive different sound frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, this feature is similar to some headphone adjustment apps available in the market. The EQ in iPhone popularly adjusts the equalizer, while Samsung’s Music app provides adaptive sound similar to nuraphone’s app. But given that the ability to make these changes in nuraphone comes directly from the manufacturer, it gives an edge to the headphones’ hardware and functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/nuraphone-Bluetooth-Headphones-Personalized-Cancellation/dp/B076X4KH11/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;qid=1565733161&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-7&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=7aef8cbdeb3b4e885180ce5ce611884a&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nuraphone Wireless Headphones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, it provides listeners with a customized sound quality unparalleled by most headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The active noise cancellation (ANC) feature means that the mobility shouldn’t affect the sound quality. The ANC is expected to block out external noise by adding noise-canceling frequencies actively. For example, it blocks out the incessant chatter of your coworkers or classmates jabbering endlessly about something that doesn’t relate to you, as well as keeping out the sounds of traffic, the constant ringing of office phones, or the clangs and beeps of printers and keyboards around you. As noted by users, this feature also works as intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users comment that the 20-hour battery time also works as expected. As such, whether you have a busy day full of being in front of your computer at work or putting together multiple assignments for school, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/nuraphone-Bluetooth-Headphones-Personalized-Cancellation/dp/B076X4KH11/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;qid=1565733161&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-7&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=7aef8cbdeb3b4e885180ce5ce611884a&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nuraphone Wireless Headphones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; would last you more than the full day against a single charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headphones weigh a mere 11.7 ounces, which makes them quite lightweight despite their traditional design. It has been noted that users who wear them throughout the day feel great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that is where opinions start to differ. Those who are not used to earbuds have complained that the design is not very comfortable. Whereas, those who got acclimated with the feeling of wearing earbuds say that they are very much at ease with wearing them all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another slight disadvantage mentioned by users is that the headphones don’t connect to multiple devices at once. While the headphones have Bluetooth, they don’t have a multipoint connection. But this doesn’t seem to bother most users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/nuraphone-Bluetooth-Headphones-Personalized-Cancellation/dp/B076X4KH11/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=high+end+headphones&amp;amp;qid=1565733161&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-7&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=7aef8cbdeb3b4e885180ce5ce611884a&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nuraphone Wireless Bluetooth Over Ear Headphones with Earbuds&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; seem to be an excellent choice for those who are looking for innovative design, excellent sound quality, and fantastic battery life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, it is essential to keep in mind that wearing earbuds all day might be stressful for you if you are not used to it. You might need to give the headphones a few hours before you get comfortable wearing them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ss&amp;amp;ref=as_ss_li_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=B076X4KH11&amp;amp;asins=B076X4KH11&amp;amp;linkId=c6d828b550b58eb27003278a87b7afb7&amp;amp;show_border=true&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Alan</name></author><category term="ReviewHuntr" /><category term="Product Reviews" /><category term="Reviews" /><category term="Review Website" /><summary type="html">If you have a busy schedule like me, then you might relate to the things you miss out on daily. You don’t have time to Netflix and chill. You can’t find time to schedule a spa appointment for a little R&amp;amp;R. You don’t even have spare time to give yourself a pep talk. Thankfully, the need for recreation, relaxation, and motivation is met by good music. Those who have a jam-packed calendar would agree sometimes all you must do is play some music and relax. Lose your worries and zone out- or in - for a specific timeframe. But given that you can’t blast your favorite tracks through your commute, at the gym, and work or class, even listening to music could be a difficult task. You’ll need the right equipment.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ruputas Wowstick 1F+ Electric Screwdriver and Repair Kit - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/ruputas-wowstick-1f-electric-screwdriver-and-repair-kit-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ruputas Wowstick 1F+ Electric Screwdriver and Repair Kit - Review" /><published>2019-08-15T05:00:45+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-15T05:00:45+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/ruputas-wowstick-1f-electric-screwdriver-and-repair-kit-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/ruputas-wowstick-1f-electric-screwdriver-and-repair-kit-review/">&lt;p&gt;A tool kit, sewing kit, and first aid kit are all necessities in any household. You may not need them right now, but you’ll certainly do at some point. This is somewhat of an unspoken rule everybody subconsciously learned growing up. Lately, with everyone and their grandma having a ton of devices, having a good repair kit has quickly started to become one of those necessities. You never know when one of your devices will break down and you must fix it. Perhaps you want to replace your phone screen or reattach loose components inside a gaming console (both things I’ve had to do just this year). Even if your devices never break (&lt;em&gt;they will&lt;/em&gt;) you might need to assemble something like a custom-built PC. Whatever the case may be, having a repair kit is a no-brainer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally I’ve been using a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iFixit-Pro-Tech-Toolkit-Electronics/dp/B01GF0KV6G/ref=as_li_ss_tl?keywords=Pro%27s+kit&amp;amp;qid=1565873996&amp;amp;s=gateway&amp;amp;sr=8-3&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=8e0008b07dcac72597d418b46d799704&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;repair kit from iFixit&lt;/a&gt; since 2015 and I’ve been super happy with it… until a couple of days ago when I stumbled upon the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07DB7ZT5P/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=f6de5cd21708a10262731d2024be56e3&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ruputas Wowstick 1F+ Electric Screwdriver and Repair Kit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. It’s an &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;electric screwdriver repair kit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; with an incredibly stylish design. I. Need. This. In. My. Life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ss&amp;amp;ref=as_ss_li_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=B07DB7ZT5P&amp;amp;asins=B07DB7ZT5P&amp;amp;linkId=1a3c23ca2d53dcc8a133f06297d1e605&amp;amp;show_border=true&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-screwdriver&quot;&gt;The Screwdriver&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07DB7ZT5P/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=f6de5cd21708a10262731d2024be56e3&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ruputas Wowstick 1F+ Electric Screwdriver&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is an electric screwdriver. But not one of those big electric screwdrivers made for building that you’re probably thinking of. This tool is made specifically for device repair. Because of this it doesn’t have to be any larger than your average whiteboard pencil. Unlike any other tool that you put away after use and then have to dig up when you need it, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07DB7ZT5P/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=f6de5cd21708a10262731d2024be56e3&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ruputas Wowstick 1F+&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has such a sleek, modern design that you might as well leave it on your desk as decoration. In-fact, since &lt;em&gt;Ruputas&lt;/em&gt; include an equally stylish stand for the tool I’m pretty sure that’s what they intend for you to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, let’s be honest. You’re probably not buying an electric screwdriver for the looks. You’re buying it because of its usefulness. So, how good is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07DB7ZT5P/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=f6de5cd21708a10262731d2024be56e3&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ruputas Wowstick 1F+&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;? It has a rated speed of 200rpm and a rated torque of 0.15/3N.M which basically translates to: it’s definitely powerful enough. On top of that, the tip of the tool is equipped with three LED lights which means there’s no need to try get that stupidly far in screw out while simultaneously trying to balance your phone with flashlight on between your chin and chest because the light won’t reach. No, I’m not still salty from the last time this happened. Not at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To top it all off the tool is not only useful, powerful, and stylish but also incredibly easy to use. Just pick it up, slip in the bit (or &lt;em&gt;screwhead&lt;/em&gt; as some insist on calling them) and you’re good to go. There’s only one key for you to press. Pressing the bottom part of it will rotate the bit forwards and pressing the top part rotates it back. Now, I’m really only mentioning this because &lt;em&gt;Ruputas&lt;/em&gt; lists this as one of their selling points but, honestly, have you ever seen an electric screwdriver that isn’t this easy to use?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving on, the screwdriver itself isn’t the only thing you get with this product…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;but-wait-theres-more&quot;&gt;But wait! There’s more…&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right. Besides getting the screwdriver itself, you’ll get an entire repair kit with everything you’ll ever need. Let’s go through what’s in the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right upon opening the box you’ll be greeted with a &lt;em&gt;magnetic mat&lt;/em&gt; that you can put your screws on to prevent them from rolling away. I cannot stress enough how useful having something like this is. I remember the first time I built a PC and lost more than half the screws because they discretely rolled away. Guess what, I never found them either. Since then I’ve learned my lesson and now I use the good old bowl trick. The problem with putting all the screws in a bowl is that they all get mixed together and it’s difficult to find the screw you need. Placing them flat on a magnetic surface makes it much easier to stay organized when repairing and you won’t need to chase fleeing screws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After removing the magnetic mat you’ll find the screwdriver itself, the stand for the screwdriver, and the other accessories perfectly arranged. Like Tetris blocks. What are these other accessories? As I said, it’s practically all the tools you need in a repair kit. You’ve got a suction cup, a guitar-pick-shaped pry tool and a magnetizer / demagnetizer tool. You’ll also get a storage case where you can throw accessories into when you’re not using them, or you could use it as a traveling case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I know what you’re thinking. “That’s cool and all but wouldn’t the screwdriver be useless without bits (screwheads)”? You’re right, it would. That’s why the screwdriver comes with a whopping &lt;strong&gt;56 bits&lt;/strong&gt;. That’s more than you’ll probably ever need. I’m looking through the list now (which you can find in the Amazon description) and I honestly don’t even know what all of these are. And I’ve done my fair share repairs. They come in three super neat storage tubes that look more practical and definitely takes up less space than the rectangular boxes they tend to come with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, you’ll also receive a charging cable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-are-other-people-saying&quot;&gt;What are other people saying?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking at the Amazon reviews, customers seem to be satisfied with the product. They’ve been praising the design and the practically of the device as well as the include accessories. It seems like the most praised aspects (except the convenience factor) of the kit is the included magnetic mat, the LED lights on the tip of the screwdriver, and the sheer number of bits included in the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only real complaint about the product itself I could find was that some feel it is underpower. They want to tighten screws harder than the motor is capable of. Personally, I think this is by design. Quite often when dealing with sensitive components you don’t want to tighten the screws too hard because that could cause damage. Therefore, the screwdriver tightens hard enough for most cases and if you want it to be extra tight then you need to tighten it more manually. That being said, I’ve seen several reviews of the device as well as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FSBFCx59fF8&quot;&gt;videos where the device has been used&lt;/a&gt; and it looks like the screwdriver will be able to tighten screws hard enough in 99% of cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another complain I’ve seen is the fact that the device charges using Micro USB instead of USB-C and… yeah that sucks. But in all honesty, it doesn’t really matter. It fully charges in 40 minutes anyway. My Kindle and Bluetooth speakers all charge using Micro USB and while it is slightly annoying having to have an extra cable for devices like this, you’ll get used to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One odd quirk I haven’t seen mentioned in any reviews is the fact that the stand for the screwdriver doesn’t charge it. It’s just a stand. Again, it’s just a minor inconvenience and doesn’t make it any less of an amazing tool but it’s odd and worth mentioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having a repair kit at home for all your devices is quickly becoming as much of a necessity as having a tool kit, sewing kit, and first aid kit. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07DB7ZT5P/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=f6de5cd21708a10262731d2024be56e3&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ruputas Wowstick 1F+ Electric Screwdriver and Repair Kit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is seemingly the perfect one. Not only do you get and extremely stylish electric screwdriver, but you also get essential repair tools as well as 56 different bits (screwheads).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I highly recommend picking this kit up. Even if you don’t need it now you &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; need it in the future. Best to be prepared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ss&amp;amp;ref=as_ss_li_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=B07DB7ZT5P&amp;amp;asins=B07DB7ZT5P&amp;amp;linkId=1a3c23ca2d53dcc8a133f06297d1e605&amp;amp;show_border=true&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Simon</name></author><category term="ReviewHuntr" /><category term="Product Reviews" /><category term="Reviews" /><category term="Review Website" /><summary type="html">A tool kit, sewing kit, and first aid kit are all necessities in any household. You may not need them right now, but you’ll certainly do at some point. This is somewhat of an unspoken rule everybody subconsciously learned growing up. Lately, with everyone and their grandma having a ton of devices, having a good repair kit has quickly started to become one of those necessities. You never know when one of your devices will break down and you must fix it. Perhaps you want to replace your phone screen or reattach loose components inside a gaming console (both things I’ve had to do just this year). Even if your devices never break (they will) you might need to assemble something like a custom-built PC. Whatever the case may be, having a repair kit is a no-brainer.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Yamaha P45 - Digital Piano Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/yamaha-p45-digital-piano-reivew/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Yamaha P45 - Digital Piano Review" /><published>2019-08-14T05:00:45+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-14T05:00:45+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/yamaha-p45-digital-piano-reivew</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/yamaha-p45-digital-piano-reivew/">&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re just taking your first steps into the music world, or you already own a keyboard but you’re considering upgrading to a better one… there are some things you might want to consider before purchasing a new digital piano. First, the size of the keyboard, or more precisely, the number of keys. This will determine the higher and lower notes you’ll be able to reach. If you’re a beginner, you might be tempted to buy a small one, thinking you won’t be reading notes way above or below the middle staff. However, you’ll soon find yourself somewhat limited if your keyboard has less than five full octaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A full-size keyboard has 88 keys (52 white keys and 36 black keys), like a real piano. At first, a beginner might not use the top or bottom octave much, but in time they’ll be extremely useful. For the small increase in price, the extra notes are well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another important factor is the size of the keys themselves. A standard piano key is about 2.3cm wide, but cheaper or smaller keyboards will usually have narrower keys as well. This might seem not important, but if you get used to smaller keys, it’ll be harder to play other pianos that have different-sized ones. By making sure the keys in your keyboard are standard, you’ll be able to apply your talent in other pianos, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But perhaps the most crucial thing to look for in a digital piano, is the way it feels when pressing down on the key. You’ll probably want to feel the key similar to that of a traditional piano. Even though there are no hammers or strings inside a digital instrument, most manufacturers will design the mechanism of the keys in order to compensate for the lack of leverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good pivot will determine the amount of force it takes to press the keys and produce the sound. Most &lt;strong&gt;Yamaha&lt;/strong&gt;’s models have been praised for this, as they usually have the pivot point in a position that’s comfortable for the pianist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To imitate the feel of an acoustic piano, manufacturers use some variation of what is known as weighted action. It basically makes the keys feel more like the keys on a traditional piano.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Yamaha-88-Key-Weighted-Digital-P45B/dp/B00UJ9LNDK/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=efb39a70206386fe095dc917afd29e46&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yamaha P-45B&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in particular, is a weighted hammer-action simulated piano, heavier in the low end and lighter in the high end, just like an acoustic piano. This allows it to respond best, especially to velocity variation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ss&amp;amp;ref=as_ss_li_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=B00UJ9LNDK&amp;amp;asins=B00UJ9LNDK&amp;amp;linkId=5311f18d385181f51a641f8641da4a0a&amp;amp;show_border=true&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more, without weighted action, the keys on the keyboard would be “easier” to play, since it would feel more like an organ and less like a piano. This will give you an advantage, since it’s easy to move to an organ when you’re used to weighted action keys, but not so much in reverse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this, most reviewers said that the weight of the keys and response feels like a real piano. Similar to this, other users said that the weighted action keys are great, and couldn’t tell any difference from a real piano. However, they also commented that the sound is good, but not great. The dynamic range has also been a point for concern. Although the keys are touch sensitive, the difference in volume between pounding on them and lightly touching them has been noted to be different to what you find on a real piano.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other buyers had a different view on this aspect, and commented that the sound you can obtain with the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Yamaha-88-Key-Weighted-Digital-P45B/dp/B00UJ9LNDK/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=efb39a70206386fe095dc917afd29e46&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yamaha P-45B&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is very realistic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The minimalist approach of the keyboard has also been praised. The reduced number of buttons give the piano a cleaner and less cluttered look. There’s also less voice options when compared to other models—only 2 grand pianos, 2 electric pianos, 2 organs, 2 harpsichords, 1 strings and 1 vibraphone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The users considered this to be beneficial, since most pianos would have a ridiculously large variety of extra tunes rarely used. Most pianists will likely toggle between the acoustic piano, electric piano and organ. Even though it might be fun one or two times, you won’t need to play your piano with a tuba sound very often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another positive point of the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Yamaha-88-Key-Weighted-Digital-P45B/dp/B00UJ9LNDK/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=efb39a70206386fe095dc917afd29e46&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yamaha P-45B&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is that the speakers are facing down out of the bottom of the piano, instead of up, as is common in most designs. This allows for the sound to come out richer and less like it’s a plastic toy keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It comes with very useful functions, like a metronome, and customizable preferences for reverb type and depth. But perhaps the most wanted option is the two-person mode, which splits the keyboard in half and duplicates the octaves, each with their own sound. This is a great feature because it lets the user play a bass line with the left hand while playing chords and/or a melody with the other, all the while using different sounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also comes with a power adapter and sustain pedal. The latter is a particularly important thing to look for when searching for a digital piano or keyboard. Not every keyboard comes with one, and it might be a deal breaker for most pianist, as it is virtually impossible to play in modern styles without one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, despite some users commenting that the quality of the sound is not the best, most agree that even though it might sound not like a real piano, it gets really close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a full-size weighted-hammer action keyboard, this is a really good option considering that similar keyboards can cost well over $1000. So, if you’re looking for a good-quality keyboard that’s also low-budget, the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Yamaha-88-Key-Weighted-Digital-P45B/dp/B00UJ9LNDK/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;linkId=efb39a70206386fe095dc917afd29e46&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yamaha P-45B&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will meet all your needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;OneJS=1&amp;amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;source=ss&amp;amp;ref=as_ss_li_til&amp;amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;amp;tracking_id=mrpowerscript-20&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;amp;region=US&amp;amp;placement=B00UJ9LNDK&amp;amp;asins=B00UJ9LNDK&amp;amp;linkId=5311f18d385181f51a641f8641da4a0a&amp;amp;show_border=true&amp;amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Victoria Blanco</name></author><category term="ReviewHuntr" /><category term="Product Reviews" /><category term="Reviews" /><category term="Review Website" /><summary type="html">Whether you’re just taking your first steps into the music world, or you already own a keyboard but you’re considering upgrading to a better one… there are some things you might want to consider before purchasing a new digital piano. First, the size of the keyboard, or more precisely, the number of keys. This will determine the higher and lower notes you’ll be able to reach. If you’re a beginner, you might be tempted to buy a small one, thinking you won’t be reading notes way above or below the middle staff. However, you’ll soon find yourself somewhat limited if your keyboard has less than five full octaves.</summary></entry></feed>