<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-24T18:12:44+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Destroy the Amazon rainforest for charity with Amazonian wood clothing - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/amazon-wood-clothing-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Destroy the Amazon rainforest for charity with Amazonian wood clothing - Review" /><published>2019-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/-amazon-wood-clothing-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/amazon-wood-clothing-review/">&lt;p&gt;After a hard time trying to figure out a way to help save the amazon following weeks of insane deforestation and colossal fires, this new line of clothes entirely made out of Amazonian wood wants to make a big entrance into the ecological design market -and they did it-.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From wooden pants to vine shoes and leaf-made t-shirts, entrepreneur and designer William Treecut explained his proposal to save the amazon rainforest: “I got tired of seeing all those Instagram influencers, only sending their thoughts and prayers after those alarming fires. So I thought ‘well, maybe the lungs of the planet need some big-ass bucks to finally catch some breath’. Then I started to create a profitable business out of this, where we allow people to finally give their money to something that will help rebuild the amazon, while also looking amazing for their crying pictures. 95% of our earnings go to the countless ONGs that are seeking funds to recover the rainforest, and 5% to repair the chainsaws that get damaged while extracting the product to make our finest clothing”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their system is simple: cut down the trees, make awesome clothes, then donate the funds to plant more trees. At first, the idea seemed a little bit unethical, and many ONGs and Instagram celebrities —like Rudy Bega— Immediately expressed their skepticism about the whole initiative. As Mr. Bega explained, “I don’t know if this will help the amazon at all, but if I can get a taste of this product for free, I’ll probably promote it as well. Please check my new video”. But as Hare O’Daiorama, president of Greenpeace explained: “it was literally the only decent proposal”. He praised the projections made out by Treecut, specifically stating that “the cost-benefit graphic had a lot of ecologic green color on its design -so it had to be a sustainable idea”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We approached the company and bought a whole lot of new outfits to test their quality. The wooden pants were the first choice: although their design was a little old-fashioned —which was the main intention, as the design can easily pass as the pants of a Victorian armor—, we found that having little mobility and itchy crotches weren’t something we could get used to. A similar thing happened with the leaf t-shirt: the leafs caused an allergic reaction on our team, wreaking havoc all across the newsroom. Surprisingly, the premium line of oak and pine tree t-shirts and pants felt comfy, and its hipster design stood up for the enormous expectations that we had with this clothing line (and its price. We ran out of money to afford a writer for this article).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we know, hipster-culture is a fusion of several preferences, such as dressing in vintage clothing, holding pacifist and green views, and having a desire of moral superiority on most of the current topics of modern society. And this clothing line seems to have everything in its favor to shake the grounds of society. As Treecut explained, “there’s no more vintage thing than using designs inspired in the 1600’s era or something more pacifist than the sound of a chainsaw in the middle of the Amazon”. The company is also exploring other options to please the needs of a public that is hungry for justice: a honey bee pure, a new line of white shark teeth’s kitchen knives, and a very interesting product: a brand-new line of shoes made out of the skin of endangered species, that will certainly create consciousness about animal hunting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our verdict: the oak and pine tree t-shirts and pants were stylish, but not very useful for runners. We’ll wait for the honey bee puré and the shark teeth kitchen knives to see if things can get more interesting.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Julio Alfonzo</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">After a hard time trying to figure out a way to help save the amazon following weeks of insane deforestation and colossal fires, this new line of clothes entirely made out of Amazonian wood wants to make a big entrance into the ecological design market -and they did it-.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Canon EOS Rebel T6 Digital SLR Camera Kit with EF-S 18-55mm f/3.5-5.6 IS II Lens (Black) - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/canon-eos-rebel-t6-digital-slr-camera-kit-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Canon EOS Rebel T6 Digital SLR Camera Kit with EF-S 18-55mm f/3.5-5.6 IS II Lens (Black) - Review" /><published>2019-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/canon-eos-rebel-t6-digital-slr-camera-kit-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/canon-eos-rebel-t6-digital-slr-camera-kit-review/">&lt;p&gt;Have you ever considered indulging in photography? Once a person has mastered the basics, it is something that pays off in the long run. You can capture memories beautifully and re-visit them over again. However, you may have found yourself overwhelmed with all the choices out there. These days, there are so many options for the average everyday user and it gets harder to decide what to pick. Once you decide to check out the options, you might find your enthusiasm waning due to confusion about what to buy. I thought I’d make it easier for you by reviewing one of the most beginner-friendly cameras out there, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01CO2JPYS/ref=dp_cr_wdg_tit_nw_mr&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Canon EOS Rebel T6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rebel T6 has a plastic body and is one of the more lightweight models available, with a weight of no more than 3lbs. According to Amazon reviews, customers were surprised to find out how small in size the &lt;em&gt;T6&lt;/em&gt; is, with it being described as “one of the smallest you can buy among DSLRs”. This is positive feedback for people who would not want to lug around a heavy camera around their neck or shoulder for trips to the mountains or the beach. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01CO2JPYS/ref=dp_cr_wdg_tit_nw_mr&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Canon EOS Rebel T6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, unlike its predecessor &lt;em&gt;T5&lt;/em&gt;, comes with WiFi connectivity and a Digic 4+ processor, a step up from the basic Digic 4 processor and lack of WiFi connectivity. There are all the basic beginner modes available, like landscape, portrait and sports. For people looking to have more creative control, there are manual settings you can fiddle with, like aperture and shutter. The T6 is on the cheaper side of the DSLR range, costing around $550. The camera has been described by Amazon buyers as “very user friendly” and the added extra of WiFi connectivity is great for the people who want to upload their pictures to social media on the go. Hence, as an everyday camera, it is a good option to consider. For events and trips, automatic mode is reported to be good enough to do the job. If you plan on practising, there is a wide range of manual settings and modes provided. In the back, there is an LCD screen which has been described by buyers as having a better resolution than the previous model. For newbies, there is an added feature to help out in manual mode. When one wants to fiddle with the DSLR in manual mode, a brief description will show up on screen for guidance and information. This helpful feature can also be turned off in case you have been watching too many Youtube tutorials. This aspect of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01CO2JPYS/ref=dp_cr_wdg_tit_nw_mr&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Canon EOS Rebel T6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has been well appreciated among Amazon reviewers. The camera is part of a kit which also includes 2 basic entry-level lenses for a variety of photographic needs. If you own any existing lenses, buyers have found that majority of lenses are compatible with this camera. You will need to buy your own SD card for storage of pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we talk about some of the cons, the lack of touch-screen on the LCD panel on the back of the camera left some buyers frustrated. Another problem customers found off-putting was the fact that the LCD screen is fixed and cannot be flipped back. For photographers who are not entirely new to the DSLR scene, they will be disappointed to know that the ISO feature is automatic and you cannot change it even in manual mode. If you change other manual settings, the camera will set its own ISO. Some users shared that the camera’s shutter speed was a bit slower than average, taking up to 5 seconds to capture a photo. Others were disappointed to find that the camera did not perform up to par at capturing high-speed events, even in sports mode. One of the most shared sentiment about this camera, as reported by Amazon buyers, was that it was not as excellent in the video department, compared to photograph only. Issues with autofocus was a major complaint. The camera frequently beeped which meant it could not focus adequately on the subject and therefore, would not capture. If you want a camera for vlogging, this is not a good option for you as there is no jack for an external microphone. An in-depth user manual is also not provided in the box, and users have had to go searching online for instructions. Other major negative setbacks reported among users is that the camera’s WiFi will not work if the cable is attached to the computer. Apart from that, it was reported by some customers that WiFi will connect to users’ smartphones, but not laptops or computers. Make of that what you will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overwhelmingly, users were quite pleased with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01CO2JPYS/ref=dp_cr_wdg_tit_nw_mr&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Canon EOS Rebel T6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; regarding its functionality and price tag. For beginners, this is a highly recommended DSLR that does not require one to shell out big bucks. It is viewed as a very good choice for someone who wants to dabble in the field of photography as a hobby. It is also a good piece of equipment to learn the basics on. The Canon T6 won’t burn a hole in your pocket, is simple to use and easy to learn, and takes great photos as shared by Amazon buyers. Overall, it is viewed as great value for your money, user-friendly and a nice entry level option.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Lisa</name></author><category term="Cameras" /><summary type="html">Have you ever considered indulging in photography? Once a person has mastered the basics, it is something that pays off in the long run. You can capture memories beautifully and re-visit them over again. However, you may have found yourself overwhelmed with all the choices out there. These days, there are so many options for the average everyday user and it gets harder to decide what to pick. Once you decide to check out the options, you might find your enthusiasm waning due to confusion about what to buy. I thought I’d make it easier for you by reviewing one of the most beginner-friendly cameras out there, the Canon EOS Rebel T6.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MSI GeForce GTX 1080 - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/msi-geforce-gtx-1080-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MSI GeForce GTX 1080 - Review" /><published>2019-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/msi-geforce-gtx-1080-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/msi-geforce-gtx-1080-review/">&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that every PC Gamer dreams of playing their favourite games at max settings, whilst having their computer barely break a sweat. This dream isn’t possible to realize without a graphics card that can push back against the rising demands of newer games. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the perfect card for any PC gamer, and with enough features to win anyone over, there’s no shock in its hefty 4.4 star rating on Amazon. It was voted best graphics card in the European Union in 2016 and has sold over 20 million units worldwide. You can’t argue with numbers like those!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; boasts two beefy fans connected to multiple copper heat pipes to keep it running cool. Users have expressed that the stock fan settings are insufficient, but this is an issue easily fixed using MSI’s own utility (MSI Afterburner). This card is outfitted with Torx 2.0, MSI’s newest cooling technology. Torx 2.0 manages to achieve 22% higher air pressure by utilizing software and hardware improvements. The fans use an innovative dispersion style that allows for air to better flow throughout the card. The fans are supported by double ball bearings to guarantee silent operation under any condition. If you don’t find the stock solutions up to your needs, you can always install a custom water loop to cool your computer. The card’s surface is covered in inky black paint with beautiful red accents that highlight cooling fins. LED lights are installed on this card which allows for users to match lighting effects with their builds colour. This card can blend aesthetically into any build. The cards general appearance and fans are received with an appraisal from most users as it offers more than just a plain card aesthetically speaking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performance is what truly matters, and this card packs enough for anyone. Its capable of high-resolution gaming, live streaming games, and even handling multiple security cameras feeds! On its stock settings this card runs at around 1750mhz, impressive but not something most people will be blown away by. However, when yous start overclocking this card, that’s when you really begin to feel its true power. Many users have managed to get this card near 2000hz, a beastly number. Cooling these behemoths is important, as without it they would throttle down and lower their clock speed. Again, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is well prepared. Its dual-fan setup allows for temperatures to stay in the 80s even at 100% usage. The fans focus on cooling the 6 large copper heat coils connected to the main GPU, so there is always cooling going to critical components. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; boasts an impressive 8 gigabytes of hyper-advanced GDDR5X graphics memory. This card’s performance was revered at its debut in 2016, yet it still easily contends with most major cards today. The general user consensus is that this card easily and reliably achieves its performance targets, whilst also having the ability to exceed them thanks to its overclocking software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; manages to easily overcome anything modern games can throw at it. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; manages to run nearly every modern at Ultra settings, but as technology moves forward, 4k is not the bleeding anymore. Modern gamers are now hard-pressed to get that exhilarating rush achieved only by running their favourite games at graphical levels nearing real life. This rush is now achieved by experiencing their favourite games in Virtual Reality. Virtual Reality is now the bleeding edge of video games and requires a beefy graphics card to avoid the all too common motion sickness when games arent run properly. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; easily meets and exceeds the requirements for virtual reality, and can run any virtual reality game on the market with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the card is definitely marketed towards gamers, with styling to match, it can do so much more. Video editors marvel at the cards rendering speed and optimization which makes video editing, in general, a breeze. This card fully supports SLI which allows for users to run to of these cards together, essentially doubling performance. Frequent driver updates and software support from MSI ensures that this card won’t fall behind. The card has lots of surprising uses, so it is sure to fit anyone’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MSI-GeForce-GTX-1080-GAMING/dp/B01HHBQBLG/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MSI Geforce GTX 1080&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a rock-solid all-around graphics card that can handle anything you throw at it with ease. It features innovative new technology to meet and exceed all your expectations. The performance is on par with many of today’s most innovative cards, and easily withstands the test of time. Coming in at just under 800$, its mostly meant for enthusiasts or high-performance users that need to squeeze every ounce of energy from their systems.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Hamza Tariq</name></author><category term="Computer Components" /><category term="Graphics Cards" /><summary type="html">It’s no secret that every PC Gamer dreams of playing their favourite games at max settings, whilst having their computer barely break a sweat. This dream isn’t possible to realize without a graphics card that can push back against the rising demands of newer games. The MSI Geforce GTX 1080 is the perfect card for any PC gamer, and with enough features to win anyone over, there’s no shock in its hefty 4.4 star rating on Amazon. It was voted best graphics card in the European Union in 2016 and has sold over 20 million units worldwide. You can’t argue with numbers like those!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Acer Predator Helios 300 Gaming Laptop – Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/acer-predator-helios-300-gaming-laptop-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Acer Predator Helios 300 Gaming Laptop – Review" /><published>2019-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/acer-predator-helios-300-gaming-laptop-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/acer-predator-helios-300-gaming-laptop-review/">&lt;p&gt;Computers have gradually become an essential part of our lives. Since their origins, they have allowed us to carry out significant processes capable of simplifying multiple tasks, and over time, these have even become a source of entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the exponential technological advances of recent years, and the emergence of different technologies, desktop computers are no longer the only option the market offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple professionals, students and day-to-day users have discovered how comfortable and efficient laptops can be, — in part because they can be transported from one place to another with ease moreover because they continue to improve by leaps and bounds —, to the point that some may even surpass several desktop models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are one of the many users who enjoy the advantages that a laptop can provide, this is an article for you, especially if you want to know various details related to a computer somewhat “powerful”; that you could use to spend long days playing demanding video games without sacrificing any performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a beginner and don’t know how specific components work, or how they can be superior to others, don’t worry, as I’ll, in detail, explain the elements that make the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/PH315-51-78NP-Acer-Predator-Helios/dp/B07CTHLX8C/ref=sr_1_7?__mk_es_US=%C3%85M%C3%85%C5%BD%C3%95%C3%91&amp;amp;crid=A23T4V16A9N7&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Acer Predator Helios 300 Gaming Laptop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; an excellent
choice for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/PH315-51-78NP-Acer-Predator-Helios/dp/B07CTHLX8C/ref=sr_1_7?__mk_es_US=%C3%85M%C3%85%C5%BD%C3%95%C3%91&amp;amp;crid=A23T4V16A9N7&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Acer Predator Helios 300 Gaming Laptop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; features a 15.6” FHD IPS screen with a refresh rate of 144Hz, an Intel i7-8750H processor, a GTX 1060 6GB GPU, 16GB DDR4 RAM, 256GB NVMe SSD, and Aeroblade Metal Fans PH315-51-78NP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the above makes this model an excellent choice. According to different reviews, it can be considered a high-performance laptop with outstanding performance concerning its price range. Despite having unique components, its price is around $1200, which makes it relatively accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pros&quot;&gt;Pros&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The powerful components in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/PH315-51-78NP-Acer-Predator-Helios/dp/B07CTHLX8C/ref=sr_1_7?__mk_es_US=%C3%85M%C3%85%C5%BD%C3%95%C3%91&amp;amp;crid=A23T4V16A9N7&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Acer Preditor helios 300 Gaming Laptop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is probably the laptops biggest draw. Let’s go through them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the screen, this model has a 15.6” FHD IPS screen that provides wide viewing angles and excellent color accuracy. The 144hz refresh rate ensures an incredibly smooth gameplay experience — although, to take full advantage of this functionality you’ll need to play at a high enough FPS which means that the performance could vary according to the game and the configurations applied to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Nvidia GeForce GTX 1060 might not be the latest and greatest (that title goes to the RTX 2080 Ti, which is more expensive than this entire laptop) but it’ll be more than enough for your gaming needs. No, you won’t be able to play the latest AAA titles with all settings maxed out in 4K and with 250 fps but, if you turn down the settings just a little you’ll be able to run them smoothly. As for competetive games like Overwatch, CS:GO, and Dota 2 you’ll have nothing to worry about, let the graphics shine and the frames be high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Intel i7-8750H will make sure you have all the processing power you’ll need. Whether you’re trying to render out a YouTube video, building a scene in Unity, or just editing a photo you’re laptop won’t slog. The 16 GB of DDR4 RAM will also help to make sure your experience is as fast and smooth as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of aesthetics, the laptop consists of plastic and metal parts and a non-mechanical keyboard - which, according to different buyers, is one of the best non-mechanical keyboards on the market - with different luminous gadgets that make it somewhat “unique”. Despite being a slightly heavy laptop — approximately 5.51 lbs — many users have defined it as a comfortable piece of equipment to carry and even state that it is relatively light compared to other gaming laptops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cons&quot;&gt;Cons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the pros there are some cons that have been frequently mentioned by users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The laptop has somewhat limited storage with it’s modest 256 GB. However, the laptop does support expandable storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The laptop has significant problems of overheating which will effect both the gaming experience and performance in general — as such, overheating brings with it a considerably decreased fps in demanding games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until now, multiple solutions have been proposed by different users, the most common being to purchase a cooling pad, make use of the cool boost function integrated in the laptop itself, or even undervolting the CPU to prevent it from overheating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite all the above and the significant problem of overheating, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/PH315-51-78NP-Acer-Predator-Helios/dp/B07CTHLX8C/ref=sr_1_7?__mk_es_US=%C3%85M%C3%85%C5%BD%C3%95%C3%91&amp;amp;crid=A23T4V16A9N7&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Acer Preditor helios 300 Gaming Laptop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a great laptop, and most users in their reviews have agreed that it has an excellent quality-price relationship that makes it an outstanding choice for those who want to get an incredible gaming laptop for a friendly sum of money concerning the quality of its components, because its small problems can be solved with a little extra investment that will not require a budget higher than $1300, while most of the laptop gaming in the market easily exceed that price.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Martín Juárez</name></author><category term="Laptops" /><summary type="html">Computers have gradually become an essential part of our lives. Since their origins, they have allowed us to carry out significant processes capable of simplifying multiple tasks, and over time, these have even become a source of entertainment.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2019 HP Premium HD Laptop - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/hp-premium-hd-laptop-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019 HP Premium HD Laptop - Review" /><published>2019-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/hp-premium-hd-laptop-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/hp-premium-hd-laptop-review/">&lt;p&gt;We’ve all heard of HP, it’s one of the most popular brands of office tech - especially in the computer world - that can deliver what you need when you need it. I own a Windows 10 HP PC myself - in fact, its the very one I’m using to write this review. But enough about the company brand itself, let’s talk about a certain product of theirs and dive into its features, quality, and general reception amongst buyers. Today, we’re reviewing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HP-15-6-inch-Dual-Core-MaxxAudio-Bluetooth/dp/B07QKWTZ4B/ref=sr_1_5&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2019 HP Premium HD Laptop.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Sold online at the very popular Amazon retail shopping website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Released on April 10, 2019, this personal laptop has managed to rank #60 in amazon’s “Computers and Accessories” category; as well as scoring #6 in Traditional Laptop Computers. It’s to say this tech tool is not under the radar - and one you won’t have trouble finding in Amazon’s search results. But, it is on the cheaper side of the competition. Selling for a measly $349.00, which does include free shipping. With that in mind, this laptop can be interpreted best as a “budget” product, with a “Get what you pay for” type of situation. So remember to keep that in mind before adding this to your laptop wishlist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for specs, it isn’t indecent. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HP-15-6-inch-Dual-Core-MaxxAudio-Bluetooth/dp/B07QKWTZ4B/ref=sr_1_5&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2019 HP Premium HD Laptop.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is lightweight, making it a better option for those who don’t like carrying around a heavy object in their backpack or briefcase. However, it is on the larger side in terms of screen-size - which is a solid 15.6 inches. Though, this does mean you won’t have to worry about a small-screen; especially if you hate squinting. Other notable specs would be its OS, which is running 64-bit Windows 10, the fact it supports both WIFI and Bluetooth connectivity, and that it a has useful 8GB of ram. Which on paper, makes it sound like a pretty good buy if you need a cheap laptop for school or work purposes. But before reading any further, let’s take a rain-check on that idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rated 3.7 out of 5 stars, and sitting at 116 total reviews. The consumer opinion of this device seems to be relatively positive, with a tad bit of negativity thrown in the mix. But, don’t let that fool you into making an impulsive decision. After reading through a multitude of more recent reviews, I seem to get the idea that this product is not all that it’s “cracked” up to be. Several reviewers have claimed that their device has arrived defective or not-working, such as this review by Katherine L. Others have included a sentiment of dissatisfaction with their experience, many claiming that their copy of the laptop had slow processing speeds, and consistent periods of delays and freezes; both of which can severely bother someone if their on a schedule. This review coincides with the report of delay, noting that the product has trouble with opening files and apps; something I would consider a bit of a turn-off when said product claims to have an 8 gig RAM. Amazon user ifrah comments that his 2019 HP HD is horrendous, making it almost impossible to get such simple tasks done such as browsing and basic homework needs. So far, the reviews seem to tell a different story than the advertised “premium” quality. But, that’s not to say there aren’t some positive reviews. Eric’s sentiment goes with my earlier statement of this laptop being a “budget” product. Once again starting with the recurring argument of lag and delay, he goes on to however say it works decently for basic word applications and streaming sites, and that you do get what you pay for; an opinion we seem to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the overall responses I’ve gathered about this product, many people seem to agree on one almost universal opinion. This laptop is a decent cheap buy for somebody who needs something basic, like a middle school or high school student. But other than that, it has some real issues that need to be addressed by the manufacturers. Especially if some of their shipments are arriving broken or defective to a portion of their customers. Quality over Quantity is a motto that everyone who hopes to be successful in this business should follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I rate this a personal 2.5 out of five stars, as it does have some neat features and long battery life. But if you’re looking for something fast and productive for long-term projects, or maybe just your everyday job. Then I would consider looking elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Henry</name></author><category term="Laptops" /><summary type="html">We’ve all heard of HP, it’s one of the most popular brands of office tech - especially in the computer world - that can deliver what you need when you need it. I own a Windows 10 HP PC myself - in fact, its the very one I’m using to write this review. But enough about the company brand itself, let’s talk about a certain product of theirs and dive into its features, quality, and general reception amongst buyers. Today, we’re reviewing the 2019 HP Premium HD Laptop. Sold online at the very popular Amazon retail shopping website.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Audeze LCD-3 Over Ear Headphones Fazor Elements MAPLE WOOD VERSION - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-3-over-the-ear-headphones-fazor-elements-maple-wood-version-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Audeze LCD-3 Over Ear Headphones Fazor Elements MAPLE WOOD VERSION - Review" /><published>2019-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-3-over-the-ear-headphones-fazor-elements-maple-wood-version-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-3-over-the-ear-headphones-fazor-elements-maple-wood-version-review/">&lt;p&gt;Audiophiles know that nothing may surpass good music. I know this for a fact. Not only do I regularly interact with self-identified audiophiles, I can easily claim to be one myself. I love immersing myself in music. I’d never be able to work out of an office that banned headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I may digress, but good music is to an audiophile what a good book is to a bookworm. If you find an artistic work that you like you can go back to it, again and again, to find new meaning in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By repeat listening sessions of their favorite music, audiophiles can identify notes and ranges that they weren’t able to discover before. Doing so brings about a feeling of accomplishment, exhilaration, and recreation. As such, it serves as a great way to unwind for music lovers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But to feel this profoundly enjoyable experience, you need listening equipment that is capable of bringing the best out of your music and highlight everything on the recording.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is the reason why high-end headphones remain extremely popular among the “music 1%” (those who truly believe in listening to music as a hobby). With specialized design, materials, and functions, these headphones could elevate your music experience, unlike other audio equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you think of these high-end headphones, the Audeze LCD line instantly comes to mind. With the best design, material, and function features, these headphones remain a class apart. One of the most popular models from the series, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3 Over Ear Headphones with Fazor Elements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, remains a prime example of excellence in audio equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from the company’s popular Fazor Elements, that claim to deliver soundwaves flawlessly, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; headphones come with ultra-thin yet large diaphragms. These diaphragms promise the delivery of powerful bass, clear top-end, and targeted midrange. The headphones also boast of double-sided magnetic arrays which claim to make distortion a thing of the past. The planar magnetic technology, on the other hand, aims to deliver a natural and accurate sound that highlights every single note on a recording.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users, all of these features make for a pair of headphones that deliver consistently compelling, clear, and flawless sound during each listening experience. Anyone who has used the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; cannot stop highlighting the astoundingly high quality of its sound — a factor that remains prevalent in all kinds of recordings and music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also note that this level of sound quality and consistency is possible due to the way that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headphones are handcrafted and promise superior building processes to complement their high-quality sound. Built using leather suspension headband and ear pads, sturdy steel frame, maple wood rings, and braided cable, the headphones give off the unmistakable air of luxury while also bringing in durability as one of their other prime characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides aesthetics and strength, this build also reflects on the overall sound quality that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; users rave about. Each earpiece on the headphones comprises of multiple layers of high-quality material, which aims to provide a superior listening experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For starters, the housing itself is made out of carefully picked and polished maple wood and durable steel. It is joined by Audeze’s lighter-than-air diaphragm, neodymium magnets, and Fazor Elements, before being topped off by the leather earpad. Users note that this results in headphones that come with the qualities of clarity, accuracy, and exceptional waveform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; headphones line comes with different types of wood rings. As mentioned above, this particular edition uses maple as the choice of wood, which looks exceptional against the jet black color of the main structure as well as the silver accents on top of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It looks as wonderful as it sounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who want to keep these premium headphones safe between use or who want to carry them around to use at their convenience, the headphones come with a sturdily-built travel case. This aspect ensures that whether you are traveling by bus or taking a personal car, your headphones remain safe from any impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users, this focus on material and safety reflects very well on the headphones’ build quality. The headphones are highly durable and built with the notion to last their owners for years. Users note that the headphones’ structure conveys this idea very clearly. This aspect also means that the headphones are fabulous for those who don’t want to shell out premium pricing for replacement headphones every couple of years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weighing just 1.4lbs, the headphones remain quite light as compared to other high-end models. A few users complain about only being able to wear them for a couple of hours a day, but others mention that they are comfortable to wear for the most part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; headphones come with a 1-year warranty on cosmetic parts and accessories, as well as a 3-year warranty on drivers. The hardware warranty is subject to manufacturer deficits. But as noted by users, the Audeze LCD-3 remains free of hardware issues and comes with a high-quality finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3 Over Ear Headphones with Fazor Elements and Maple Wood Rings&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are a fantastic addition to any audiophile’s music library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price tag might seem high, but its design and sound quality make them justify their cost quite quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in the market for a pair of headphones that are just as rich in sound quality as it is in its looks, then your search might end with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/AUDEZE-LCD-3-Headphone-Maple-Leather/dp/B07D9WWKTS/ref=sr_1_14?=1565963906&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Alan</name></author><category term="Headphones" /><summary type="html">Audiophiles know that nothing may surpass good music. I know this for a fact. Not only do I regularly interact with self-identified audiophiles, I can easily claim to be one myself. I love immersing myself in music. I’d never be able to work out of an office that banned headphones. I may digress, but good music is to an audiophile what a good book is to a bookworm. If you find an artistic work that you like you can go back to it, again and again, to find new meaning in it. By repeat listening sessions of their favorite music, audiophiles can identify notes and ranges that they weren’t able to discover before. Doing so brings about a feeling of accomplishment, exhilaration, and recreation. As such, it serves as a great way to unwind for music lovers. But to feel this profoundly enjoyable experience, you need listening equipment that is capable of bringing the best out of your music and highlight everything on the recording. That is the reason why high-end headphones remain extremely popular among the “music 1%” (those who truly believe in listening to music as a hobby). With specialized design, materials, and functions, these headphones could elevate your music experience, unlike other audio equipment. When you think of these high-end headphones, the Audeze LCD line instantly comes to mind. With the best design, material, and function features, these headphones remain a class apart. One of the most popular models from the series, the Audeze LCD-3 Over Ear Headphones with Fazor Elements, remains a prime example of excellence in audio equipment. Apart from the company’s popular Fazor Elements, that claim to deliver soundwaves flawlessly, the Audeze LCD-3 headphones come with ultra-thin yet large diaphragms. These diaphragms promise the delivery of powerful bass, clear top-end, and targeted midrange. The headphones also boast of double-sided magnetic arrays which claim to make distortion a thing of the past. The planar magnetic technology, on the other hand, aims to deliver a natural and accurate sound that highlights every single note on a recording. As noted by users, all of these features make for a pair of headphones that deliver consistently compelling, clear, and flawless sound during each listening experience. Anyone who has used the Audeze LCD-3 cannot stop highlighting the astoundingly high quality of its sound — a factor that remains prevalent in all kinds of recordings and music. Users also note that this level of sound quality and consistency is possible due to the way that the Audeze LCD-3 is made. The headphones are handcrafted and promise superior building processes to complement their high-quality sound. Built using leather suspension headband and ear pads, sturdy steel frame, maple wood rings, and braided cable, the headphones give off the unmistakable air of luxury while also bringing in durability as one of their other prime characteristics. Besides aesthetics and strength, this build also reflects on the overall sound quality that the Audeze LCD-3 users rave about. Each earpiece on the headphones comprises of multiple layers of high-quality material, which aims to provide a superior listening experience. For starters, the housing itself is made out of carefully picked and polished maple wood and durable steel. It is joined by Audeze’s lighter-than-air diaphragm, neodymium magnets, and Fazor Elements, before being topped off by the leather earpad. Users note that this results in headphones that come with the qualities of clarity, accuracy, and exceptional waveform. The Audeze LCD-3 headphones line comes with different types of wood rings. As mentioned above, this particular edition uses maple as the choice of wood, which looks exceptional against the jet black color of the main structure as well as the silver accents on top of it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">HIFIMAN HE1000 V2 Over Ear Headphones - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/hifiman-he1000-v2-over-ear-headphones-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HIFIMAN HE1000 V2 Over Ear Headphones - Review" /><published>2019-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/hifiman-he1000-v2-over-ear-headphones-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/hifiman-he1000-v2-over-ear-headphones-review/">&lt;p&gt;Real music enthusiasts want quality. It is not just a want. They desire phenomenal quality. As I have noticed in my own experiences, this holds true regardless of the type of person. The audiophile may be a working professional or a student who happens to love music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that no one could attend a live concert with exceptional sound quality every single day, the objective of a consistently astounding listening experience seems impossible to achieve. But as demonstrated by high-end headphones, it isn’t that difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless of the kind of music you like, a great pair of headphones could be the difference between drearily hearing a distorted song and thoroughly enjoying a crystal clear performance. By simply upgrading your listening equipment,  find new life in old songs. You may also discover fresh notes that you previously missed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not unveil the best parts of new music right from the get-go?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2 Headphones with Planar Magnetic Technology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; promises to check all of these boxes, and then some. They are pricey, alright. But the significant part about these headphones is that they undoubtedly fulfill their claims of delivering excellent sound quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boasting the use of the world’s first-nanometer diaphragm, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; also features an advanced asymmetrical magnetic circuit, a patented structure for natural soundstage, and manual craftsmanship for high-quality design. When combined, these features come together to offer sound quality that is natural and distortion-free. For those upgrading from lower-range headphones, it promises to turn their listening experience around for the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nanometer diaphragm in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is supposed to deliver faster response while keeping distortion at bay. As noted by those who have used these headphones, the thin diaphragm does its job impressively. The sound produced by these headphones delivers crisp, bright, and vibrant tunes at every session. No matter the genre of music, the headphones’ sound quality remains notably natural and reminiscent of a great live listening experience. This notion means that if you are one to enjoy music without the restriction of the genre, these headphones would be a perfect match for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advanced asymmetrical magnetic circuit, which uses a double-sided design, works together with the nanometer diaphragm to elevate the distortion-free listening experience even further. The feature also translates into real-world use effectively and provides users with a midrange that is free of any reflections or deflections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As noted by users, this is once again evident in the sound quality produced by the headphones. Whether you are a hardworking professional or an extremely busy student, a single listening session at the end of the day could certainly elevate your mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some users have also noted that the midrange is one of those aspects where the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; shines at its best. From highlighting vocals to shaping instrumentals, and from delivering a natural sound to elevating different notes in a song, the headphones elevate the overall listening experience quite impressively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that’s not all, especially when it comes to sound quality. The patented structure, dubbed as “Window Shade” comes with an open back design that is as comfortable to wear as it is effective in enhancing the listening experience. The strategic design has given the headphones such a shape that they steer clear of any troublesome vibrations. The design also eliminates any distortions that are caused due to a headphones’ structure, which is quite noticeable in most commonly used equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, this structural Window Shade design claims to deliver spectacular imaging with exceptional clarity. Users have noted that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; holds to this promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But even as everyone who has used the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; sings about its sound quality, most of the users mostly complain about the craftsmanship of these high-end headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headphone comes in a traditional design that comprises silver, gold, and black accents with a suspension headband. Even at being a conventional design, the style is modern and sleek. It is an excellent design in terms of aesthetics, and users don’t seem to have any complaints about the appearance. But they have a lot to say when it comes to the build and its quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headphones claim to be handcrafted and checked for quality – something that is supposed to be demonstrated in each pair. But according to users, this is not the case. Some users take issue with unwanted scratches on the pairs that they have received, while others speak of detached or poorly attached padding materials that should not be visible in high end headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall packaging and craftsmanship seem to be the only issue that is brought up with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. But it seems like a big problem for those who are spending a large amount on this equipment for the love of music. With that, not all users seem to complain about build quality. Those who have received perfectly crafted pairs have not had any complaints about the headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; somewhat justifies its high price point through superior sound quality. But it doesn’t do complete justice to its cost due to its build issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, the build issues have not been prevalent for most users. If you are looking for headphones that deliver exceptional sound, then you could certainly go for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/HIFIMAN-HE1000-V2-Magnetic-Headphone/dp/B01I50644C/ref=sr_1_13&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HIFIMAN HE1000 V2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Just make sure to contact the manufacturer for warranty and replacement information in case you might end up with a pair that has issues in its built.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Alan</name></author><category term="Headphones" /><summary type="html">Real music enthusiasts want quality. It is not just a want. They desire phenomenal quality. As I have noticed in my own experiences, this holds true regardless of the type of person. The audiophile may be a working professional or a student who happens to love music. Given that no one could attend a live concert with exceptional sound quality every single day, the objective of a consistently astounding listening experience seems impossible to achieve. But as demonstrated by high-end headphones, it isn’t that difficult. Regardless of the kind of music you like, a great pair of headphones could be the difference between drearily hearing a distorted song and thoroughly enjoying a crystal clear performance. By simply upgrading your listening equipment, find new life in old songs. You may also discover fresh notes that you previously missed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">iRobot Roomba 980 Robot Vacuum - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/irobot-roomba-980-robot-vacuum-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="iRobot Roomba 980 Robot Vacuum - Review" /><published>2019-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/irobot-roomba-980-robot-vacuum-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/irobot-roomba-980-robot-vacuum-review/">&lt;p&gt;Roomba is probably the first name that pops into peoples head when they think of robot vacuums. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;iRobot Roomba 980 Robot Vacuum&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is similar to the traditional Roomba, circular in shape with black edges and a sleek look that makes one feel like they’re living in the future. The specifications of the Roomba 980 include HEPA filtration, a diameter of 13.9 inches and 3.6 inches in height. It’s weight stands in at 8.7 pounds, and it has a built-in handle for carrying it around. On the front, there are three buttons: Home button present on the left, a large Clean button in the middle, and a “Spot Clean” button on the right side. This particular feature is for when you want to preserve the charge and make sure the Roomba cleans only when there’s something to be cleaned, like litter spills. You can set up an automatic time for it to start cleaning, however, the Roomba comes with an app on both iOS and Android so that you can take care of the Roomba’s schedule manually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above the Clean button, there are “indicator lights”, and a Wi-Fi symbol will light up to tell you the connectivity status. If something goes wrong, there will be a troubleshooting symbol, and the Roomba will announce an error number that one can Google. Coming to the battery indicator, it will light yellow if it needs to be charged, and the standard green once its ready to get to work. A red trash icon means the dustbin needs to be emptied. Under the Roomba, there are 6 cliff sensors. These “cliff sensors” are light detectors designed for the robot to stop and back away at stairs or places where it might fall off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re buying powers are influenced by ratings, Amazon users rated this product an average of 4.1 out of 5 stars. Generally, users reported that they prefer the ease of use of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, with it being a great option for daily routine cleaning, especially for families who have a lot of pets. A longer-than-average battery life was also reported to be a plus in favor of the newer model, with users mentioning how the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; can go on for 2 hours at a time without a recharge on “Eco-Mode”. With the carpet boost mode on, however, the battery life is almost cut in half, not viewed lightly by some Amazon users. It takes 90 minutes for it to fully recharge. When it does require a recharge, it leaves off cleaning to go to its dock, then goes back to clean where it left off. The biggest pro of this model as told by satisfied customers is that it is exceptional in performance when it comes to cleaning up debris and pet fur. This may be due to several factors. One factor most often mentioned was the addition of rubber extractors instead of traditional bristles or brushes. Another reason was the navigation system the robot uses. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; uses VSLAM technology, which is Visual Simultaneous Location and Mapping. That means the robot utilizes location and mapping to make a virtual map out of where it goes and refers back to it for future cleanings. The machine is very easy to clean up and doesn’t require a lot of time or effort, as well as cutting down considerably on your daily cleaning time. With the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, you can get away with vacuuming your house weekly, instead of daily. It also manages to get under hard-to-reach places via a regular vacuum, like under beds and cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app that the Roomba comes with was a highly touted plus, with ease of scheduling being the highlight. The clean button can also be pressed remotely in order to let the robot do its job. It also tells you if the bin needs to be emptied, and the robot will not clean if the bin isn’t emptied. Regular maintenanace requirements can also be checked from the app, like changing debris extractors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to cons, users mentioned that the circular shape of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a setback because it does not allow the robot to clean corners effectively. The cliff sensors also hinder its ability to clean carpets, as complained most frequently by customers. The robot mistakes darker colored carpets for a cliff drop because the dark color cannot reflect any IR light. So the robot avoids carpet cleaning, even those with dark colored patterns on them. Some buyers also feel it isn’t quite worth the higher price tag, as they feel that such a high price should have minimal to no cons. Users said that alternatives like taping up sensors so the robot would clean carpets, but risk it falling over stairs, was not worth it on a Roomba with such a price tag. One of the most frequent complains from dissatisfied users was the Roomba dying before it can reach the charging dock. Other reports included buggy Roombas saying the bin was full even after it had been emptied. Some people have complains that once you plan on cleaning, it requires a little bit of prep which means you will need to move any solid objects, wires, curtains and the like out of the way, which didn’t sit well with some buyers who couldn’t set up daily cleaning due to the initial prep required. Some upkeep is also needed in order to make sure the Roomba is efficient, where the bin needs to be cleaned regularly, usually after every cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overwhelmingly, buyers believe it is well worth the price and ultimately the pros far outweigh the cons. Most users have said that they are extremely happy and satisfied with their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/iRobot-Vacuum-Connected-Mapping-Carpets/dp/B013E9L4ZS/ref=sr_1_1?qid=1566150606&amp;amp;tag-reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roomba 980&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the quality of cleanliness it provides in a busy lifestyle, with people being frequently impressed by how the robot managed to pick up dirt and debris from places they had already cleaned beforehand with a regular vacuum.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Lisa</name></author><category term="Home Cleaning Appliance" /><summary type="html">Roomba is probably the first name that pops into peoples head when they think of robot vacuums. The iRobot Roomba 980 Robot Vacuum is similar to the traditional Roomba, circular in shape with black edges and a sleek look that makes one feel like they’re living in the future. The specifications of the Roomba 980 include HEPA filtration, a diameter of 13.9 inches and 3.6 inches in height. It’s weight stands in at 8.7 pounds, and it has a built-in handle for carrying it around. On the front, there are three buttons: Home button present on the left, a large Clean button in the middle, and a “Spot Clean” button on the right side. This particular feature is for when you want to preserve the charge and make sure the Roomba cleans only when there’s something to be cleaned, like litter spills. You can set up an automatic time for it to start cleaning, however, the Roomba comes with an app on both iOS and Android so that you can take care of the Roomba’s schedule manually.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Audeze LCD-4 Over Ear Headphones - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-4-over-the-ear-headphones-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Audeze LCD-4 Over Ear Headphones - Review" /><published>2019-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-4-over-the-ear-headphones-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/audeze-lcd-4-over-the-ear-headphones-review/">&lt;p&gt;The sound of music is one of the very few things in the world that could draw the favorable attention of anyone regardless of their age, gender, or social setting. Whether you are an entrepreneur or an entry-level professional, an ambitious student, or a hardworking artist, listening to some great music is never out of the question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all, the music is that one thing in the world that could very quickly make you feel a ton of emotions depending upon the genre. Only by choosing an artist or a type of music, would you feel relaxed, motivated, reflective, or soothed in an instant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This notion is all the more profound when your music is delivered free of distortion, latency, and muffled sounds. That is why you must choose hardware that provides you with superior sound quality, impressive imaging, and crystal clear notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4 Over Ear Headphones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; rise to the challenge with a promise to meet these requirements with ease. For the most part, these high-end headphones also succeed by an impressive margin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For starters, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; comes with one of a kind nano-scale diaphragm that is lighter than air. Yes, you read that right. The diaphragm is so thin and light that this level of excellence in diaphragm development is exclusive to Audeze. In real-world terms, it promises the most accurate bass response among any commercial headphones on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, the diaphragm also allows the headphones to provide better imaging during playtime. What’s even better is that these claims are strengthened by users’ reviews, who support Audeze’s superiority in sound delivery through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diaphragm’s abilities are further enhanced by the magnet array technology included in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;LCD-4&lt;/a&gt;. With Double Fluxor Magnet Arrays, the headphones provide exceptional magnetic flux to an astounding 1.5 Tesla. This concept translates into a fantastic performance by offering more excellent resolution and a massively improved transient response as compared to its counterparts. The quality that these features add to the sound delivery is heavily noted by those who use the headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What further adds to the nano-scale diaphragm and the magnet arrays of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is its Fazor Elements. The technology, which has been patented by Audeze, is proficient in guiding soundwaves to provide a clearer and accurate waveform. Users note that this translates to the headphones projecting the overall sound quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Made with ebony wood and leather ear pads, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; sport a sleek yet industrial design that makes the headphones a delight to behold. Each of the pair is meticulously handcrafted in Audeze’s California facility, with the proximity providing the company with full control over its manufacturing and quality assurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users note that these features add up to make these headphones “possibly the best in the world.” This notion is essential to note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moniker mentioned above comes from an audiophile who utilized the product and shared their two cents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sound produced by the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; remains incomparable to other headphones. A U.S. Army veteran, who utilized the headphones while going through a hearing disability, was awestruck to hear the clarity of the notes through the headphones. This comment stands as a testament to the overall results that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; can provide to its users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, the headphones do come at a massively high price tag. To say that they are a significant investment would be an understatement. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is worth it if you value quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with this, the headphones also require a high-quality amplifier to work optimally. Ideally, it should be a combo of an amp and DAC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Optimize for the full experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users also find an issue with the headphones’ weight and the overall comfort that it provides to the user. Some users think that the headphones are too heavy to wear for longer sessions, while others say that they have gotten used to the feeling. But in both cases, users praise the quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; comes with a cryogenically treated premium braided cable. With high quality, silver-plated OCC copper, enjoy uninterrupted sound that comes without any signal loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you love listening to high-quality music and luxury experiences, then getting the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is just right. But if budget is an issue, then looking at lower-end or less expensive models would be the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that, if you already have an amp or DAC setup or would like to go the whole nine yards with your audio experience, then the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Audeze-LCD-4-Headphone-Ebony-Leather/dp/B01DTQ6AMS/ref=sr_1_7?&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audeze LCD-4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; just might be a no brainer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Alan</name></author><category term="Headphones" /><summary type="html">The sound of music is one of the very few things in the world that could draw the favorable attention of anyone regardless of their age, gender, or social setting. Whether you are an entrepreneur or an entry-level professional, an ambitious student, or a hardworking artist, listening to some great music is never out of the question. After all, the music is that one thing in the world that could very quickly make you feel a ton of emotions depending upon the genre. Only by choosing an artist or a type of music, would you feel relaxed, motivated, reflective, or soothed in an instant.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MDMA Therapy Home Kit For Cat Depression - Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/mdma-cat-depression-therapy-home-kit-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MDMA Therapy Home Kit For Cat Depression - Review" /><published>2019-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/mdma-cat-depression-therapy-home-kit-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/mdma-cat-depression-therapy-home-kit-review/">&lt;p&gt;Depression has become a common topic of discussion for more and more people. In part because of revolutionary approaches to treating depression hitting the news. Various studies show that party drugs are currently in use for more than their traditional purposes. Helping people heal from past traumas, PTSD, depressions, and more. For example, the promising results from therapies using MDMA add a whole new hue to discussions regarding drug laws and medicine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But did you know people aren’t the only ones who suffer from depression? Your pets can become depressed as well. Especially if they’re living with someone who suffers from depression. Pet depression can be more difficult to spot because pets have difficulty communicating their thoughts and feelings with their people friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cats are one of the most common animals who suffer from depression, and there are several signs to look out for. Do you find your cat sleeping for long periods in the day? Are they restless at night? Do they avoid your attention, or even hide from you? These are all signs that you may have a cat suffering from depression. In years past your only options for treatment would be cute mice on a string, catnip, or feline Prozac. Now you have another option in this new age of medicine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MDMA cat therapy is the freshest trend rolling onto the scene. With veterinary clinics offering specialized services all over the country. The times are changing once again and you don’t have to leave the comfort of your own home to participate in this therapy for your depressed cat.  Meowtastic Treats is offering new MDMA cat therapy home kits to help you return the joy to all nine of your cat friends lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Dr. Felidae of the Hoof Art Education Center for Animal Wellness stresses that these treatments are still very new and many of the long term side effects are unknown. She goes on to suggest, “if you notice your cat is listening to electronic music or chasing lasers in excess it might be time to reduce the treatments”. She goes on to say that no treatments are purrrfect, and it’s important to continually monitor your cat throughout the treatments and report any strange behaviors to their vet. The type of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/s/ref=as_li_ss_tl?k=cat+food&amp;amp;crid=24QEGG45T0F6V&amp;amp;sprefix=cat+food,aps,313&amp;amp;ref=nb_sb_ss_i_1_8&amp;amp;linkCode=ll2&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=363b411717b7ff69cd50709e16e0a469&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;cat food&lt;/a&gt; your little Simba is eating can also have an impact on their well being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, despite concerns, many people are opting to try these home treatments with successful results. Vicky from Buffalo, New York, is ecstatic with the results so far. “He’s sooooo much more affectionate than he was before. He’s been rubbing against me for the past 8 hours. He only took one break to find a glowing neon collar. I’m still not quite sure where he found it. He’s a whole new cat, and I love him to pieces. The MDMA cat therapy home kit is exactly what he needed.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ReviewHuntr gathered cats from all walks of life to conduct our review. House cats living with depressed owners, and owners without depression. Cats that spend their day chasing rats who spend their day chasing cheese. And alley cats who ate trash every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Results varied across our subjects. The indoor cats saw the most benefit while alley cats saw marginal improvements. The cat who chased rats wasn’t interested in trying the treatment. But he’s always been kind of lame that way with his collar all tight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of all the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/s/ref=as_li_ss_tl?k=cat+supplies&amp;amp;crid=35RQI9TE6UTYQ&amp;amp;sprefix=cat+supplies,aps,236&amp;amp;ref=nb_sb_ss_i_1_12&amp;amp;linkCode=ll2&amp;amp;tag=reviewhuntr-20&amp;amp;linkId=a5ebc7efa4f80cf5260343db609ff2eb&amp;amp;language=en_US&quot;&gt;things you can supply your cat&lt;/a&gt; the most important one is happiness. While it still may be slightly controversial, MDMA therapy for cats has proven to be as effective as its human MDMA therapy trials. With home kits hitting the stores it’s a chance for you to share some happiness with the cats you love.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">Depression has become a common topic of discussion for more and more people. In part because of revolutionary approaches to treating depression hitting the news. Various studies show that party drugs are currently in use for more than their traditional purposes. Helping people heal from past traumas, PTSD, depressions, and more. For example, the promising results from therapies using MDMA add a whole new hue to discussions regarding drug laws and medicine.</summary></entry></feed>